<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Traffic</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Traffic</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 11:07:50 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Mason]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-mason/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Thomas Mason is an English singer-songwriter and guitarist from Worcester, who first found fame with the rock band Traffic. Over the course of his career, Mason has played and recorded with many notable pop and rock musicians, including Paul McCartney, George Harrison, the Rolling Stones, Jimi Hendrix, Eric Clapton, Michael Jackson, David Crosby, Graham Nash, Steve Winwood, Fleetwood Mac, Delaney & Bonnie, Leon Russell and Cass Elliot. One of Mason's best known songs is 'Feelin' Alright', recorded by Traffic in 1968 and later by many other performers, including Joe Cocker, whose version of the song was a hit in 1969. For Traffic, he also wrote 'Hole in My Shoe', a psychedelic pop song that became a hit in its own right. 'We Just Disagree', Mason's 1977 solo US hit, written by Jim Krueger, has become a staple of US classic hits and adult contemporary radio playlists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/DaveMason03.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-mason/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Winwood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-winwood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen Lawrence Winwood is an English singer, songwriter and musician whose genres include progressive rock, blue-eyed soul, rhythm and blues, blues rock, pop rock, and jazz. Though primarily a vocalist and keyboard player, Winwood also plays a wide variety of other instruments; on several of his solo albums he has played all instrumentation, including drums, mandolin, guitars, bass and saxophone.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/81/Steve_Winwood_scottfisher.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-winwood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>