<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Trip Hop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Trip Hop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:07:39 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Akira Yamaoka]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/akira-yamaoka/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Akira Yamaoka  is a Japanese video game music composer, sound designer, guitarist, and producer, best known for composing various games in the Silent Hill series by Konami. He also once worked as a producer on the series, as well as serving as a composer and producer of the Silent Hill film and its sequel. Since 2010, he has been the sound director at Grasshopper Manufacture.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/01/Akira_Yamaoka_-_Game_Developers_Conference_2010_-_Day_3_%283%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/akira-yamaoka/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Svetlana Surganova]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/svetlana-surganova/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Svetlana Yakovlevna Surganova is a Russian rock musician, singer and poet. She was a founding member of the popular Russian rock band Nochnye Snaipery, providing vocals and playing violin. Presently she is a founding member of 'Surganova i Orkestr' band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/74/Swetlana_Surganowa.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/svetlana-surganova/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lana-del-rey/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Elizabeth Woolridge Grant, known professionally as Lana Del Rey, is an American singer and songwriter. Her music has been noted by critics for its stylized cinematic quality; its preoccupation with themes of tragic romance, glamour, and melancholia; and its references to pop culture, particularly 1950s and 1960s Americana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f9/Lana_Del_Rey_at_KROQ_Weenie_Roast_2017_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lana-del-rey/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nikolai Noskov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nikolai-noskov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nikolai Ivanovich Noskov is a Russian singer and former vocalist of the hard rock band Gorky Park. Five-time winner of the Golden Gramophone. He was also a member of Москва (Moscow) ensemble in the early 1980s, in band Гран-при in 1988 just before joining Gorky Park, and much later in the 1990s in band Николай (Nikolai). Starting 1998 Noskov had a solo career releasing six solo albums. In 2015 he was jury in second season of reality TV series Glavnaya Stsena</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/32/%D0%9D%D0%B8%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%BB%D0%B0%D0%B9_%D0%9D%D0%BE%D1%81%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%B2_%D0%B2_2009_%284%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nikolai-noskov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Moby]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/moby/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Melville Hall, better known as Moby, is an American musician, songwriter, singer, producer, and animal rights activist. He has sold 20 million records worldwide. AllMusic considers him to be 'among the most important dance music figures of the early 1990s, helping bring dance music to a mainstream audience both in the United Kingdom and the United States'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6b/Moby_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/moby/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>