<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Art Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Art Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:32:12 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Serj Tankian]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Serj Tankian is an Armenian-American musician, singer, songwriter, record producer, and political activist. He is best known as the lead vocalist, primary lyricist, keyboardist, and occasional rhythm guitarist of heavy metal band System of a Down, which was formed in 1994.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3e/Serj_Tankian_in_Artsakh_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roy Wood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-wood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0f/Roy_Wood_TopPop.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-wood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Neil Finn]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-finn/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/64/Neil_Finn_with_Split_Enz.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-finn/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Maureen Tucker]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/maureen-tucker/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fa/The_Moe_Tucker_Band_%282%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/maureen-tucker/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roger Waters]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roger-waters/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>George Roger Waters is an English songwriter, singer, bassist, and composer. In 1965, he co-founded the progressive rock band Pink Floyd. Waters initially served solely as the bassist, but following the departure of singer-songwriter Syd Barrett in 1968, he also became their lyricist, co-lead vocalist, and conceptual leader.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/03/Roger_Waters%2C_May_18_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roger-waters/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vyacheslav Butusov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vyacheslav-butusov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vyacheslav Gennadievich Butusov, is a Russian singer and songwriter. He was the lead singer of Nautilus Pompilius and U-Piter. He also has his own solo career as a singer and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e1/Vyacheslav_Butusov_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vyacheslav-butusov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Bowie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-bowie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Robert Jones, known professionally as David Bowie, was an English singer-songwriter and actor. He was a leading figure in the music industry and is regarded as one of the most influential musicians of the 20th century. He was acclaimed by critics and musicians, particularly for his innovative work during the 1970s. His career was marked by reinvention and visual presentation, with his music and stagecraft having a significant impact on popular music. During his lifetime, his record sales, estimated at over 100 million records worldwide, made him one of the best-selling music artists of all time. In the UK, he was awarded ten platinum album certifications, eleven gold and eight silver, and released eleven number-one albums. In the US, he received five platinum and nine gold certifications. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1996. Rolling Stone placed him among its list of the 100 Greatest Artists of All Time and named him the 'Greatest Rock Star Ever' following his death in 2016.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e8/David-Bowie_Chicago_2002-08-08_photoby_Adam-Bielawski-cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-bowie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Entwistle]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-entwistle/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Alec Entwistle was an English bass guitarist, singer, songwriter, film and music producer. In a music career that spanned more than 40 years, Entwistle was best known as the original bass guitarist, backing and occasional lead vocalist for the English rock band the Who. He was the only member of the band to have formal musical training. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Who in 1990.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f5/John_Entwistle_in_1967_with_The_Who.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-entwistle/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ed O'Brien]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ed-o'brien/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Edward John O'Brien is an English guitarist and member of the rock band Radiohead. O'Brien attended Abingdon School in Oxfordshire, England, where he met the other members of Radiohead. O'Brien makes extensive use of effects units to create atmospheric sounds and textures, and provides backing vocals. His first solo album, Earth, was released in 2020, under the name EOB.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a8/Ed-obrien2006-05Radiohead.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ed-o'brien/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joni Mitchell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joni-mitchell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roberta Joan 'Joni' Mitchell is a Canadian singer-songwriter. Drawing from folk, pop, rock, and jazz, Mitchell's songs often reflect social and environmental ideals as well as her feelings about romance, confusion, disillusionment, and joy. She has received many accolades, including nine Grammy Awards and induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1997. Rolling Stone called her 'one of the greatest songwriters ever', and AllMusic has stated, 'When the dust settles, Joni Mitchell may stand as the most important and influential female recording artist of the late 20th century'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9f/2013_Joni_Mitchell_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joni-mitchell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>