<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Darkthrone</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Darkthrone</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:48:48 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Fenriz]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fenriz/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gylve Fenris Nagell, better known as Fenriz, is a Norwegian musician and politician who is best known as being one half of the metal duo Darkthrone, alongside Nocturno Culto. Although primarily a drummer, he has also performed bass, guitar, and vocals for Darkthrone and a number of other metal bands. Fenriz is known for his encyclopedic knowledge of many different forms of music, his eager support of other underground bands, and his lack of interest in the mainstream music business in general. Fenriz has had multiple solo projects, including the folk black metal project Isengard, the dark ambient project Neptune Towers and the doom metal project Valhall.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/67/Fenriz.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fenriz/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nocturno Culto]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nocturno-culto/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ted Skjellum, also known by the stage name Nocturno Culto, is a Norwegian musician best known as the vocalist, lead guitarist, and partial bassist of the influential black metal band Darkthrone. He has been with the band since 1988. He is also the vocalist of the band Sarke, and has a solo project called Gift of Gods. He currently works in Norway as a school teacher, and has a son and a daughter. He has also released a documentary film called The Misanthrope in which he deals with black metal music and life in Norway.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/48/Nocturno_Culto.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nocturno-culto/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>