<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Deep Purple</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Deep Purple</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:08:37 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Morse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-morse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steve Morse is an American guitarist and composer, best known as the founder of the Dixie Dregs; and since 1994, the guitar player of Deep Purple. Morse's career has encompassed rock, country, funk, jazz, classical, and fusion of these musical genres. In addition to his successful solo career, he was briefly a member of Kansas in the mid-1980s. Most recently, Morse became a member of the supergroup Flying Colors alongside long-time bandmate Dave LaRue.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1b/Steve_Morse_2005.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-morse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nick Simper]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nick-simper/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nicholas John Simper is an English bass guitarist, who was a co-founding member of Deep Purple and Warhorse. In the 1960s, he began his professional career in bands such as Johnny Kidd & the Pirates, The Flower Pot Men, and Lord Sutch's Savages.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/02/Nick_Simper.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nick-simper/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tommy Bolin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tommy-bolin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Richard Bolin was an American guitarist and songwriter who played with Zephyr, James Gang, and Deep Purple, in addition to maintaining a notable career as a solo artist and session musician. Much of his discography was either unreleased at the time of recording, or had gone out of print and was not released again until years after his death by drug overdose at age 25.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/01/Rock_guitarist_Tommy_Bolin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tommy-bolin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>