<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » New Age Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » New Age Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:48:48 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[George Winston]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-winston/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>George Winston is an American pianist who was born in Michigan and grew up mainly in Montana, as well as Mississippi and Florida. He is best known for his solo piano recordings; several of his albums from the early 1980s have sold millions of copies each. He plays in three styles: the melodic approach he developed that he calls 'rural folk piano'; stride piano, primarily inspired by Thomas 'Fats' Waller and Teddy Wilson; and his primary interest, New Orleans R&B piano, influenced by James Booker, Professor Longhair, and Henry Butler.</p>]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-winston/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stephan Micus]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stephan-micus/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stephan Micus is a German classical and world musician and composer whose musical style is heavily influenced by his study of traditional instruments and musical techniques from Japan, India, South America, and other countries around the world. With the exception of his album The Music of Stones (1989), he plays all of the instruments on his recordings, combining styles from different countries and using the instruments in unprecedented ways in each of his pieces. He often uses layers of a single instrument to create unusual combinations of sounds. He is one of the only ECM Records artists whose records are not produced by Manfred Eicher. He has mixed instruments from around the world, or used whatever was at hand: stones, ordinary flowerpots tuned with water, and his voice—singing improvised syllables over ten years before others made this approach fashionable.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f1/Stephan_Micus.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stephan-micus/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sting]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sting/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gordon Matthew Thomas Sumner, known as Sting, is an English musician and actor. He was the principal songwriter, lead singer, and bassist for the new wave rock band the Police from 1977 to 1984, and launched a solo career in 1985. He has included elements of rock, jazz, reggae, classical, new-age and worldbeat in his music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Sting_-_Deutscher_Radiopreis_Hamburg_2016_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sting/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Arkenstone]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-arkenstone/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Arkenstone is an American composer and performer. His music is primarily instrumental, with occasional vocalizations. Most of Arkenstone's music falls into new age category; however, he also worked in other genres, including even a heavy metal soundtrack for Emperor: Battle for Dune video game. His music has been described as 'soundtracks for the imagination'. Throughout his career, Arkenstone released over 50 albums and composed music for video games, including World of Warcraft, and for television, including NBC's Kentucky Derby. David was nominated for Grammy Award three times.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f0/David-Arkenstone-Portrait.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-arkenstone/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ritchie Blackmore]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ritchie-blackmore/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Hugh Blackmore is an English guitarist and songwriter. He was one of the founding members of Deep Purple in 1968, playing jam-style hard rock music which mixed guitar riffs and organ sounds.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/78/Ritchie_Blackmore_-_Barcelona.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ritchie-blackmore/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>