<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Gospel Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Gospel Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 15:23:51 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ruthie Foster]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ruthie-foster/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ruthie Cecelia Foster is an American singer-songwriter of blues and folk music. She mixes a wide palette of American song forms, from gospel and blues to jazz, folk and soul. She has often been compared to Bonnie Raitt and Aretha Franklin.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/65/Ruthie_Foster3_-_1-24-07_-_Photo_by_Anthony_Pepitone.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ruthie-foster/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jeff Buckley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeff-buckley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jeffrey Scott Buckley, raised as Scott Moorhead, was an American singer, songwriter and guitarist. After a decade as a session guitarist in Los Angeles, Buckley amassed a following in the early 1990s by playing cover songs at venues in Manhattan's East Village such as Sin-é, gradually focusing more on his own material. After rebuffing much interest from record labels and Herb Cohen, the manager of his father, singer Tim Buckley, he signed with Columbia, recruited a band, and recorded what would be his only studio album, Grace, in 1994.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f9/%D0%93%D1%80%D0%B0%D1%84%D1%84%D0%B8%D1%82%D1%82%D0%B8_Jeff_Buckley._Revisited._%D0%A0%D0%BE%D1%81%D1%81%D0%B8%D1%8F%2C_%D0%9E%D0%BA%D1%82%D1%8F%D0%B1%D1%80%D1%8C%D1%81%D0%BA%D0%B8%D0%B9%2C_2015.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeff-buckley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Johnny Cash]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/johnny-cash/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John R. Cash, commonly known as Johnny Cash, was an American singer, songwriter, musician, and actor. Much of Cash's music contained themes of sorrow, moral tribulation, and redemption, especially in the later stages of his career. He was known for his deep, calm bass-baritone voice, the distinctive sound of his Tennessee Three backing band characterized by train-like chugging guitar rhythms, a rebelliousness coupled with an increasingly somber and humble demeanor, free prison concerts, and a trademark all-black stage wardrobe which earned him the nickname 'The Man in Black'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/be/Johnny_Cash_%281964%29.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/johnny-cash/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[James Brown]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-brown/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Joseph Brown was an American singer, songwriter, dancer, musician, record producer and bandleader. A progenitor of funk music and a major figure of 20th century music and dance, he is often referred to by the honorific nicknames 'Godfather of Soul', 'Mr. Dynamite', and 'Soul Brother No. 1'. In a career that lasted over 50 years, he influenced the development of several music genres. Brown was one of the first ten inductees into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame at its inaugural induction dinner in New York on January 23, 1986.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5d/Jamesbrown4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-brown/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Crystal Bowersox]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/crystal-bowersox/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Crystal Lynn Bowersox is an American singer, songwriter and actress who was the runner-up on the ninth season of American Idol. She was the first female finalist in three years.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b3/Crystal_Bowersox.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/crystal-bowersox/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Glen Campbell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glen-campbell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Glen Travis Campbell was an American singer, guitarist, songwriter, television host, and actor. He was best known for a series of hit songs in the 1960s and 1970s, and for hosting The Glen Campbell Goodtime Hour on CBS television from 1969 until 1972. He released 64 albums in a career that spanned five decades, selling over 45 million records worldwide, including twelve gold albums, four platinum albums, and one double-platinum album.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/65/Campbell1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glen-campbell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Doc Watson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/doc-watson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Arthel Lane 'Doc' Watson was an American guitarist, songwriter, and singer of bluegrass, folk, country, blues, and gospel music. Watson won seven Grammy awards as well as a Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award. Watson's fingerstyle and flatpicking skills, as well as his knowledge of traditional American music, were highly regarded. Blind from a young age, he performed with his son, guitarist Merle Watson, for over 15 years until Merle's death in 1985 in an accident on the family farm.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/ba/Doc_Watson_Sugar_Grove.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/doc-watson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Katy Perry]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/katy-perry/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Katheryn Elizabeth Hudson, known professionally as Katy Perry, is an American singer, songwriter, and television judge. After singing in church during her childhood, she pursued a career in gospel music as a teenager. Perry signed with Red Hill Records and released her debut studio album Katy Hudson under her birth name in 2001, which was commercially unsuccessful. She moved to Los Angeles the following year to venture into secular music after Red Hill ceased operations and she subsequently began working with producers Glen Ballard, Dr. Luke, and Max Martin. After adopting the stage name Katy Perry and being dropped by The Island Def Jam Music Group and Columbia Records, she signed a recording contract with Capitol Records in April 2007.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/91/Katy_Perry_2019_by_Glenn_Francis_%28cropped_2%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/katy-perry/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Charlie Daniels]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/charlie-daniels/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Charles Edward Daniels was an American singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist known for his contributions to Southern rock, country, and bluegrass music. He was best known for his number-one country hit 'The Devil Went Down to Georgia'. Much of his output, including all but one of his eight Billboard Hot 100 charting singles, was credited to the Charlie Daniels Band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/36/Charlie_Daniels_at_Louisville_Waterfront_Park%2C_Kentucky%2C_April_29%2C_2009.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/charlie-daniels/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Emmylou Harris]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emmylou-harris/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Emmylou Harris is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. She has released dozens of albums and singles over the course of her career and has won 14 Grammys, the Polar Music Prize, and numerous other honors, including induction into the Country Music Hall of Fame. In 2018 she was presented the Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/55/Emmylou_Harris_with_guitar.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emmylou-harris/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>