<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Gospel Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Gospel Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:38:12 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Elvis Presley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elvis-presley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Elvis Aaron Presley, also known mononymously as Elvis, was an American singer and actor. Regarded as one of the most significant cultural icons of the 20th century, he is often referred to as the 'King of Rock and Roll' or simply 'the King'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2d/PresleyPromo1954PhotoOnly.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elvis-presley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Johnny Cash]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/johnny-cash/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John R. 'Johnny' Cash was an American singer-songwriter, guitarist, actor, and author. He is one of the best-selling music artists of all time, having sold more than 90 million records worldwide. His genre-spanning songs and sound embraced country music, rock and roll, rockabilly, blues, folk, and gospel. This crossover appeal won Cash the rare honor of being inducted into the Country Music, Rock and Roll, and Gospel Music Halls of Fame.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/be/Johnny_Cash_%281964%29.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/johnny-cash/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[James Brown]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-brown/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Joseph Brown was an American singer, songwriter, dancer, musician, record producer and bandleader. A progenitor of funk music and a major figure of 20th-century music and dance, he is often referred to as the 'Godfather of Soul' and 'Soul Brother No. 1'. In a career that lasted over 50 years, he influenced the development of several music genres.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5d/Jamesbrown4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-brown/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Crystal Bowersox]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/crystal-bowersox/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Crystal Lynn Bowersox is an American singer, songwriter and actress who was the runner-up on the ninth season of American Idol. She was the first female finalist in three years.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b3/Crystal_Bowersox.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/crystal-bowersox/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Glen Campbell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glen-campbell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Glen Travis Campbell was an American singer, guitarist, songwriter, television host, and actor. He was best known for a series of hit songs in the 1960s and 1970s, and for hosting a music and comedy variety show called The Glen Campbell Goodtime Hour on CBS television, from January 1969 until June 1972. He released over 70 albums in a career that spanned five decades, selling over 45 million records worldwide, including twelve gold albums, four platinum albums, and one double-platinum album.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/65/Campbell1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glen-campbell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:11 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Emmylou Harris]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emmylou-harris/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Emmylou Harris is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. She has released dozens of albums and singles over the course of her career and won 14 Grammys, the Polar Music Prize, and numerous other honors, including induction into the Country Music Hall of Fame. In 2018 she was presented the Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/55/Emmylou_Harris_with_guitar.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emmylou-harris/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:11 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Doc Watson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/doc-watson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Arthel Lane 'Doc' Watson was an American guitarist, songwriter, and singer of bluegrass, folk, country, blues, and gospel music. Watson won seven Grammy awards as well as a Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award. Watson's fingerstyle guitar and flatpicking skills, as well as his knowledge of traditional American music, were highly regarded. He performed with his son, guitarist Merle Watson, for over 15 years until Merle's death in 1985 in an accident on the family farm.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/ba/Doc_Watson_Sugar_Grove.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/doc-watson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:11 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dolly Parton]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dolly-parton/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dolly Rebecca Parton is an American singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, actress, author, businesswoman, and humanitarian, known primarily for her work in country music. After achieving success as a songwriter for others, Parton made her album debut in 1967 with Hello, I'm Dolly. With steady success during the remainder of the 1960s, her sales and chart peak came during the 1970s and continued into the 1980s. Parton's albums in the 1990s did not sell as well, but she achieved commercial success again in the new millennium and has released albums on various independent labels since 2000, including her own label, Dolly Records.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d8/Dolly_Parton_accepting_Liseberg_Applause_Award_2010_portrait.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dolly-parton/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:11 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Wanda Jackson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wanda-jackson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Wanda Lavonne Jackson is a retired American singer, songwriter, pianist and guitarist who had success in the mid-1950s and 1960s as one of the first popular female rockabilly singers, and a pioneering rock-and-roll artist. She is known to many as the 'Queen of Rockabilly' or the 'First Lady of Rockabilly'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/20/Wanda_Jackson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wanda-jackson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:10 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lonnie Mack]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lonnie-mack/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Singer-guitarist Lonnie McIntosh, known by his stage name Lonnie Mack, was an influential American pioneer of blues-rock music and rock guitar soloing.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/74/LonnieMackRisingSun.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lonnie-mack/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:10 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>