<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Electropop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Electropop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 11:07:50 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shantel]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shantel/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stefan Hantel, better known by his stage name Shantel, is a German DJ and producer based in Frankfurt. He is known for his work with gypsy brass orchestras, DJing and remixing traditional Balkan music with electronic beats.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1c/Shantel_Bukovina-Orkestar_Wien2008a.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shantel/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ellie Goulding]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ellie-goulding/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Elena Jane Goulding is an English singer and songwriter. Her career began when she met record producers Starsmith and Frankmusik, and she was later spotted by Jamie Lillywhite, who later became her manager and A&R. After signing to Polydor Records in July 2009, Goulding released her debut extended play, An Introduction to Ellie Goulding later that year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/71/Goulding%2C_Staples_Center%2C_Los_Angeles%2C_8th_April_2016_%2843%29-cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ellie-goulding/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[AJ Michalka]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/aj-michalka/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amanda Joy Michalka is an American actress, voice actress, singer-songwriter, and musician. She was a model before becoming an actress and is best known as one half of the duo Aly and AJ with her sister Aly Michalka. AJ recorded the theme song and accompanying music video for the film Secretariat, titled 'It's Who You Are'. She also issued a single and video called 'All I've Ever Needed' from her 2013 film Grace Unplugged. She has had a successful acting career and had the recurring role of Lainey Lewis on the ABC sitcom The Goldbergs for the first, second, and fifth season, and she was promoted to a regular role on the series for the third and fourth seasons. She has starred with her Goldbergs colleagues Tim Meadows and Bryan Callen in the spin-off Schooled since January 2019. Michalka also has a lead role in the Netflix series She-Ra and the Princesses of Power, in which she voices Catra, the former best friend-turned-rival to She-Ra. She voices the character Stevonnie in Steven Universe, a fusion of the protagonist Steven and his best friend-turned-girlfriend Connie.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e5/AJ_Michalka_-_portrait_2019.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/aj-michalka/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tom Kaulitz]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-kaulitz/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/67/Tom_Kaulitz.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-kaulitz/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Katy Perry]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/katy-perry/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Katheryn Elizabeth Hudson, known professionally as Katy Perry, is an American singer, songwriter, and television judge. After singing in church during her childhood, she pursued a career in gospel music as a teenager. Perry signed with Red Hill Records and released her debut studio album Katy Hudson under her birth name in 2001, which was commercially unsuccessful. She moved to Los Angeles the following year to venture into secular music after Red Hill ceased operations and she subsequently began working with producers Glen Ballard, Dr. Luke, and Max Martin. After adopting the stage name Katy Perry and being dropped by The Island Def Jam Music Group and Columbia Records, she signed a recording contract with Capitol Records in April 2007.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/91/Katy_Perry_2019_by_Glenn_Francis_%28cropped_2%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/katy-perry/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Carole Facal]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/carole-facal/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Carole Facal is a Canadian singer-songwriter from Quebec who writes and performs in both English and French under the stage name Caracol.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/59/Caracol_at_Summerfolk.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/carole-facal/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>