<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » American Folk Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » American Folk Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 19:48:27 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tracy Chapman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tracy-chapman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tracy Chapman is an American singer-songwriter, known for her hits 'Fast Car' and 'Give Me One Reason', along with other singles 'Talkin' 'bout a Revolution', 'Baby Can I Hold You', 'Crossroads', 'New Beginning', and 'Telling Stories'. She is a multi-platinum and four-time Grammy Award–winning artist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/ba/Tracy_Chapman.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tracy-chapman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Woody Guthrie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/woody-guthrie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Woodrow Wilson Guthrie was an American singer-songwriter, one of the most significant figures in American folk music; his music, including songs, such as 'This Land Is Your Land', has inspired several generations both politically and musically. He wrote hundreds of political, folk, and children's songs, along with ballads and improvised works. His album of songs about the Dust Bowl period, Dust Bowl Ballads, is included on Mojo magazine's list of 100 Records That Changed The World. Many of his recorded songs are archived in the Library of Congress. Songwriters such as Bob Dylan, Phil Ochs, Johnny Cash, Bruce Springsteen, Robert Hunter, Harry Chapin, John Mellencamp, Pete Seeger, Andy Irvine, Joe Strummer, Billy Bragg, Jerry Garcia, Jay Farrar, Bob Weir, Jeff Tweedy, Bob Childers, Sammy Walker, Tom Paxton, AJJ, Brian Fallon, and Sixto Rodríguez have acknowledged Guthrie as a major influence. He frequently performed with the slogan 'This machine kills fascists' displayed on his guitar.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/25/Woody_Guthrie.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/woody-guthrie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dustin Kensrue]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dustin-kensrue/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dustin Michael Kensrue is a musician, songwriter and former worship leader. He is the lead vocalist and rhythm guitarist in the rock band Thrice, as well as a solo artist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/60/Dustin_Kensrue.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dustin-kensrue/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bob Dylan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-dylan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bob Dylan is an American singer-songwriter, author, and visual artist who has been a major figure in popular culture for more than fifty years. Much of his most celebrated work dates from the 1960s, when songs such as 'Blowin' in the Wind' (1963) and 'The Times They Are a-Changin'' (1964) became anthems for the civil rights movement and anti-war movement. His lyrics during this period incorporated a wide range of political, social, philosophical, and literary influences, defied pop-music conventions and appealed to the burgeoning counterculture.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/28/Joan_Baez_Bob_Dylan_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-dylan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>