<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Traveling Wilburys</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Traveling Wilburys</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:57:44 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roy Orbison]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-orbison/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roy Kelton Orbison was an American singer, songwriter, and musician known for his impassioned singing style, complex song structures, and dark, emotional ballads. His music was described by critics as operatic, earning him the nicknames 'the Caruso of Rock' and 'the Big O'. Many of Orbison's songs conveyed vulnerability at a time when most male rock-and-roll performers chose to project defiant masculinity. He performed while standing motionless and wearing black clothes to match his dyed black hair and dark sunglasses, which he wore to counter his shyness and stage fright.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0e/Roy_Orbinson_ontving_gouden_plaat_voor_Pretty_Woman_in_Singel_concertzaal%2C_Roy%2C_Bestanddeelnr_917-5752.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-orbison/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jeff Lynne]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeff-lynne/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jeffrey Lynne is an English singer, songwriter, record producer, and multi-instrumentalist who co-founded the rock band Electric Light Orchestra (ELO). The group formed in 1970 as an offshoot of the Move, of which Lynne was also a member. Following the departure of Roy Wood in 1972, Lynne assumed sole leadership of the band and wrote, arranged and produced virtually all of its subsequent records. Previously, Lynne had been involved with the Idle Race as a founding member and principal songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/89/Jeff_Lynne_April_2016.jpeg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeff-lynne/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tom Petty]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-petty/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Earl Petty was an American singer, songwriter, musician, record producer, and actor. He was the lead vocalist and guitarist of Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers, formed in 1976. He previously led the band Mudcrutch, and was also a member of the late 1980s supergroup the Traveling Wilburys.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cd/Tom_Petty_Live_in_Horsens.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-petty/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bob Dylan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-dylan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bob Dylan is an American singer-songwriter, author and visual artist. Often regarded as one of the greatest songwriters of all time, Dylan has been a major figure in popular culture during a career spanning nearly 60 years. Much of his most celebrated work dates from the 1960s, when songs such as 'Blowin' in the Wind' (1963) and 'The Times They Are a-Changin'' (1964) became anthems for the civil rights and anti-war movements. His lyrics during this period incorporated a range of political, social, philosophical, and literary influences, defying pop music conventions and appealing to the burgeoning counterculture.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/28/Joan_Baez_Bob_Dylan_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-dylan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[George Harrison]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-harrison/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>George Harrison was an English musician, singer-songwriter, and music and film producer who achieved international fame as the lead guitarist of the Beatles. Sometimes called 'the quiet Beatle', Harrison embraced Indian culture and helped broaden the scope of popular music through his incorporation of Indian instrumentation and Hindu-aligned spirituality in the Beatles' work. Although the majority of the band's songs were written by John Lennon and Paul McCartney, most Beatles albums from 1965 onwards contained at least two Harrison compositions. His songs for the group include 'Taxman', 'Within You Without You', 'While My Guitar Gently Weeps', 'Here Comes the Sun' and 'Something'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/45/George_Harrison_1974_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-harrison/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>