<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Traveling Wilburys</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Traveling Wilburys</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:46:53 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jeff Lynne]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeff-lynne/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jeffrey Lynne is an English songwriter, singer, record producer, and multi-instrumentalist who co-founded the rock band Electric Light Orchestra (ELO). The group formed in 1970 as an offshoot of the Move, of which Lynne was also a member. Following the departure of Roy Wood in 1972, Lynne assumed sole leadership of the band and wrote, arranged and produced virtually all of its subsequent records. Before, Lynne was also involved with the Idle Race as a founding member and principal songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/89/Jeff_Lynne_April_2016.jpeg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeff-lynne/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roy Orbison]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-orbison/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roy Kelton Orbison was an American singer, songwriter, and musician known for his impassioned singing style, complex song structures, and dark, emotional ballads. Many critics described his music as operatic, nicknaming him 'the Caruso of Rock' and 'the Big O'. While most male rock-and-roll performers in the 1950s and 1960s projected a defiant masculinity, many of Orbison's songs conveyed vulnerability. He performed standing still, wearing black clothes to match his dyed black hair and dark sunglasses.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d9/Roy_Orbison_1965.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-orbison/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tom Petty]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-petty/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Earl Petty was an American singer-songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, and actor. He was the lead singer of Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers, formed in 1976. He previously led the band Mudcrutch, and was also a member of the late 1980s supergroup the Traveling Wilburys.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cd/Tom_Petty_Live_in_Horsens.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-petty/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bob Dylan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-dylan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bob Dylan is an American singer-songwriter, author, and visual artist who has been a major figure in popular culture for more than fifty years. Much of his most celebrated work dates from the 1960s, when songs such as 'Blowin' in the Wind' (1963) and 'The Times They Are a-Changin'' (1964) became anthems for the civil rights movement and anti-war movement. His lyrics during this period incorporated a wide range of political, social, philosophical, and literary influences, defied pop-music conventions and appealed to the burgeoning counterculture.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/28/Joan_Baez_Bob_Dylan_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-dylan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[George Harrison]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-harrison/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>George Harrison was an English musician, singer-songwriter, and music and film producer who achieved international fame as the lead guitarist of the Beatles. Sometimes called 'the quiet Beatle', Harrison embraced Indian culture and helped broaden the scope of popular music through his incorporation of Indian instrumentation and Hindu-aligned spirituality in the Beatles' work. Although the majority of the band's songs were written by John Lennon and Paul McCartney, most Beatles albums from 1965 onwards contained at least two Harrison compositions. His songs for the group included 'Taxman', 'Within You Without You', 'While My Guitar Gently Weeps', 'Here Comes the Sun' and 'Something'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/42/George_Harrison_1974.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-harrison/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>