<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Progressive Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Progressive Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 01:44:48 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Arjen Anthony Lucassen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/arjen-anthony-lucassen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Arjen Anthony Lucassen is a Dutch singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist musician and record producer best known for his long-running progressive metal/rock opera project Ayreon.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4b/Arjen_Anthony_Lucassen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/arjen-anthony-lucassen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anneke van Giersbergen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anneke-van-giersbergen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Anna Maria van Giersbergen, known artistically as Anneke van Giersbergen, is a Dutch singer, songwriter, guitarist and pianist who became known worldwide as the lead singer and songwriter for the Dutch band The Gathering, between 1994 and 2007. 
She also has a solo career. The project was originally called Agua de Annique, but now goes by her own name.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/30/Gathering_anneke.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anneke-van-giersbergen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jason Newsted]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-newsted/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jason Curtis Newsted is an American metal musician, known for being the bassist of the band Metallica from October 1986 until his sudden departure in January 2001.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/68/13-06-09_RaR_Newsted_10.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-newsted/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Richard Henshall]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-henshall/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard 'Hen' Henshall is a British progressive metal multi-instrumentalist. He is best known for being the guitarist and keyboardist for the bands To-Mera, Haken and Opinaut. He has released one album, Earthbound, with To-Mera; five with Haken and one solo album [The Cocoon]. EP releases are Oxygen (Opinaut) and Restoration. Henshall was classically trained on the piano from the age 7. By 11-12, he started playing the guitar on a self-taught basis. He also had drums and clarinet classes.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Richard-henshall-1361087590.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-henshall/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Satriani]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-satriani/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Satriani is an American musician, composer, songwriter, and guitar teacher. Early in his career, Satriani worked as a guitar instructor, with many of his former students achieving fame, such as Steve Vai, Larry LaLonde, Rick Hunolt, Kirk Hammett, Andy Timmons, Charlie Hunter, Kevin Cadogan, and Alex Skolnick; he then went on to have a successful solo music career. He is a 15-time Grammy Award nominee and has sold over 10 million albums, making him the biggest-selling instrumental rock guitarist of all time.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/24/Satriani_2010_13_12_1112.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-satriani/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chuck Schuldiner]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chuck-schuldiner/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Charles Michael 'Chuck' Schuldiner was an American singer, songwriter, and guitarist. He founded the band Death in 1983 and was their lead vocalist until his death in 2001. His obituary in the January 5, 2002 issue of UK's Kerrang! magazine said that 'Chuck Schuldiner was one of the most significant figures in the history of metal.' Schuldiner was ranked No. 10 in Joel McIver's book The 100 Greatest Metal Guitarists in 2009 and No. 20 in March 2004 Guitar World's 'The 100 Greatest Metal Guitarists'. Schuldiner founded the publishing company Mutilation Music in 1987, affiliated with performance rights organization BMI. Schuldiner died in 2001 after a two-year battle with glioma.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/aa/Chuck_Schuldiner.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chuck-schuldiner/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jim Matheos]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jim-matheos/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jim Matheos is an American guitarist and the primary songwriter for the progressive metal band Fates Warning, in which he has been the only consistent member since the group's beginning. Matheos also plays in OSI alongside Kevin Moore, as well as making other appearances with many different bands and artists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b6/Jim_Matheos_%28Fates_Warning%292.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jim-matheos/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steven Wilson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steven-wilson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steven John Wilson is an English musician, singer, songwriter and record producer, most closely associated with the progressive rock genre. Currently a solo artist, he became known as the founder, lead guitarist, lead vocalist and songwriter of the band Porcupine Tree, as well as being a member of several other bands.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/Steven_Wilson_%28ZMF_2016%29_jm13763_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steven-wilson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ihsahn]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ihsahn/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ihsahn is a Norwegian composer, multi-instrumentalist, and vocalist. He is best known for his work with the Norwegian black metal band Emperor. Tveitan is also a founding member of Thou Shalt Suffer, where he played guitar and keyboard in addition to vocal duties, and Peccatum, a project in collaboration with his wife and fellow musician Heidi Solberg Tveitan, also known as Starofash. Since 2006, Tveitan has primarily devoted himself to solo albums and occasional guest appearances.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8e/Ihsahn_live.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ihsahn/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Buckethead]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Patrick Carroll, known professionally as Buckethead, is an American multi-instrumental musician who has received critical acclaim for his innovative electric guitar playing. His music spans many genres, including progressive metal, funk, blues, bluegrass, ambient, and avant-garde music. He performs primarily as a solo artist, though he has collaborated extensively with a wide variety of high-profile artists such as Bill Laswell, Bootsy Collins, Bernie Worrell, Iggy Pop, Les Claypool, Serj Tankian, Bill Moseley, Mike Patton, Viggo Mortensen, That 1 Guy, Bassnectar, and was a member of Guns N' Roses from 2000 to 2004. He has released 306 studio albums, four special releases, and one EP. He has also performed on more than 50 other albums by other artists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Neumos_seattle_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>