<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Classical Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Classical Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:02:55 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Arjen Anthony Lucassen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/arjen-anthony-lucassen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Arjen Anthony Lucassen is a Dutch singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist musician and record producer best known for his long-running progressive metal/rock opera project Ayreon.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4b/Arjen_Anthony_Lucassen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/arjen-anthony-lucassen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sharon Isbin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sharon-isbin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sharon Isbin is an American classical guitarist and the founding director of the Guitar Department at Juilliard.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/Sharon_Isbin_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sharon-isbin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paco de Lucía]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paco-de-lucía/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Francisco Gustavo Sánchez Gomes, known as Paco de Lucía, was a Spanish virtuoso flamenco guitarist, composer, and record producer. A leading proponent of the new flamenco style, he was one of the first flamenco guitarists to branch into classical and jazz. Richard Chapman and Eric Clapton, authors of Guitar: Music, History, Players, describe de Lucía as a 'titanic figure in the world of flamenco guitar', and Dennis Koster, author of Guitar Atlas, Flamenco, has referred to de Lucía as 'one of history's greatest guitarists'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/01/Paco_de_Lucia_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paco-de-lucía/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marko Topchii]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marko-topchii/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Marko Topchii is a classical guitarist from Ukraine. Topchii has won more than 100 awards worldwide in the international classical guitar competitions in the professional category. Among them, 44 first places in the competitions in United States, Mexico, Australia, Japan, China, Taiwan, Singapore, South Korea, Indonesia, Germany, Switzerland, France, Spain, Italy, Portugal, Liechtenstein, Poland, Hungary, Serbia, Croatia, Bulgaria, Montenegro, and Ukraine.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ae/Marko_Topchii.jpeg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marko-topchii/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul McCartney]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir James Paul McCartney is an English singer, songwriter, musician, composer, and record and film producer who gained worldwide fame as co-lead vocalist and bassist for the Beatles. His songwriting partnership with John Lennon remains the most successful in history. After the group disbanded in 1970, he pursued a successful solo career and formed the band Wings with his first wife, Linda, and Denny Laine.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d6/Paul_McCartney_in_October_2018.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Liona Boyd]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/liona-boyd/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Liona Maria Carolynne Boyd, CM, O.Ont is a classical guitarist often referred to as the First Lady of the Guitar.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/48/LionaBoyd.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/liona-boyd/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Frank Zappa]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/frank-zappa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Frank Vincent Zappa was an American multi-instrumentalist musician, composer, and bandleader. His work is characterized by nonconformity, free-form improvisation, sound experiments, musical virtuosity, and satire of American culture. In a career spanning more than 30 years, Zappa composed rock, pop, jazz, jazz fusion, orchestral and musique concrète works, and produced almost all of the 60-plus albums that he released with his band the Mothers of Invention and as a solo artist. Zappa also directed feature-length films and music videos, and designed album covers. He is considered one of the most innovative and stylistically diverse rock musicians of his era.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c4/Zappa_16011977_01_300.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/frank-zappa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Thomas Zwijsen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/thomas-zwijsen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Zwijsen is a Dutch/Belgian (Flemish) classical acoustic and Heavy Metal guitarist. He is known for his arrangements of Iron Maiden songs for classical guitar both on YouTube since 2007 and with his 2013 and 2014 albums 'Nylon Maiden', 'Nylonized' and 'Nylon Maiden II'. Since 2011, he has worked closely with ex Iron Maiden & Wolfsbane frontman Blaze Bayley, co-composing Bayley's 2012 album The King of Metal and 2013 released Russian Holiday E.P. In 2015 he released an album in Flamenco/fusion style consisting entirely of his own compositions, entitled 'Divide & Unite'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/93/Thomas_Zwijsen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/thomas-zwijsen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Frank Bungarten]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/frank-bungarten/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Frank Bungarten is a classical guitarist from Germany. Born in Cologne in 1958, Bungarten had his early influence of Guitar music when he was a teenager. In 1981, he got noticed in the international guitar scene, when virtuoso guitarist Andrés Segovia honored him with the first prize at the Guitar Competition of Granada, combined with an extensive concert tour of Spain. To date, he has performed in more than 40 countries. Among his recordings, “J.S.Bach ~ Sonatas and Partitas for Violin solo”, got serious recognition. Although he is often regarded as a Bach expert on the Concert Guitar, Bungarten claims to love and play a wide & diverse repertoire.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f0/Frank_Bungarten_111.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/frank-bungarten/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Victor Smolski]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/victor-smolski/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Victor Dmitriyevich Smolski is a musician, producer, composer, teacher, author of one of the most successful German guitar learning DVDs, School of Metal. He was a member of the German heavy metal band Rage, from 1999 until 2015. The guitarist for the metal bands Almanac, Mind Odyssey and Lingua Mortis Orchestra (LMO). Jury member for several international music competitions. Worldwide representative and co-developer for companies in the music industry, such as Yamaha, ENGL, Shure, Cordial, Thomastik-Infeld, etc.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/Rage-Victor-Berlin-2010_Thomas_Huntke.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/victor-smolski/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>