<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Dance Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Dance Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 12:09:49 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Charo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/charo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>María Rosario Pilar Martínez Molina Baeza, professionally known by her stage name Charo, is a Spanish American actress, singer, comedian, and flamenco guitarist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d7/Charo_2013_ALMA_Awards.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/charo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Madonna]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/madonna/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Madonna Louise Ciccone is an American singer, songwriter, and actress. Referred to as the 'Queen of Pop', she is regarded as one of the most significant figures in popular culture. Madonna is noted for her continual reinvention and versatility in music production, songwriting, and visual presentation. She is also known for pushing the boundaries of artistic expression in mainstream music while remaining completely in charge of every aspect of her career. Her works, which incorporate social, political, sexual, and religious themes, have generated both critical acclaim and controversy. Madonna is often cited as an influence by other artists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Madonna_Rebel_Heart_Tour_2015_-_Stockholm_%2823051472299%29_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/madonna/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sven-Erik Magnusson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sven-erik-magnusson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Knut Sven-Erik Magnusson was a Swedish singer and musician known for being the lead singer of the band Sven-Ingvars that during their sixty-year history played many different types of popular music, and was at times regarded as a dansband. The band had its last tour during the summer of 2016 with their last show on 21 August that year in Blekinge.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/05/Sven-Erik_Magnusson_2016.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sven-erik-magnusson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Holly Johnson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/holly-johnson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William 'Holly' Johnson is an English artist, musician, and writer, best known as the lead vocalist of Frankie Goes to Hollywood, who achieved huge commercial success in the mid-1980s. Prior to that, in the late 1970s he was a bassist for the band Big in Japan. In 1989, Johnson's debut solo album, Blast, reached number one in the UK albums chart. Two singles from the album – 'Love Train' and 'Americanos' – reached the top 5 of the UK Singles Chart. In the 1990s, he also embarked on writing, painting, and printmaking careers.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7e/Holly_Johnson2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/holly-johnson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robbie Williams]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-williams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Peter Williams is an English singer-songwriter and entertainer. He found fame as a member of the pop group Take That from 1990 to 1995, but achieved greater commercial success with his solo career, beginning in 1996. Williams has released seven UK number one singles and eleven out of his twelve studio albums have reached number one in the UK. Six of his albums are among the top 100 biggest-selling albums in the United Kingdom–four albums in the top 60–and in 2006 he entered the Guinness Book of World Records for selling 1.6 million tickets of his Close Encounters Tour in a single day.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/Robbie_Williams.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-williams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shakira]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shakira Isabel Mebarak Ripoll is a Colombian singer and songwriter. Born and raised in Barranquilla, Shakira has been referred to as the Queen of Latin Music and is noted for her versatility in music. She made her recording debut under Sony Music Colombia at the age of 13. Following the commercial failure of her first two albums, Magia (1991) and Peligro (1993), she rose to prominence in Hispanic countries with her next albums, Pies Descalzos (1995) and Dónde Están los Ladrones? (1998). Shakira entered the English-language market with her fifth album, Laundry Service (2001), which sold over 13 million copies worldwide. Buoyed by the international number-one singles 'Whenever, Wherever' and 'Underneath Your Clothes', the album propelled her reputation as a leading crossover artist. The BMI, the largest music rights organization in the United States, described Shakira as a pioneer who extended the global reach of Latino singers.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/86/Shakira_%26_Chris_Martin_-_Global_Citizen_Festival_Hamburg_04_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Katy Perry]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/katy-perry/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Katheryn Elizabeth Hudson, known professionally as Katy Perry, is an American singer, songwriter, and television judge. After singing in church during her childhood, she pursued a career in gospel music as a teenager. Perry signed with Red Hill Records and released her debut studio album Katy Hudson under her birth name in 2001, which was commercially unsuccessful. She moved to Los Angeles the following year to venture into secular music after Red Hill ceased operations and she subsequently began working with producers Glen Ballard, Dr. Luke, and Max Martin. After adopting the stage name 'Katy Perry' and being dropped by The Island Def Jam Music Group and Columbia Records, she signed a recording contract with Capitol Records in April 2007.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/91/Katy_Perry_2019_by_Glenn_Francis_%28cropped_2%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/katy-perry/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Krzysztof Krawczyk]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/krzysztof-krawczyk/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Krzysztof January Krawczyk was a Polish baritone pop singer, guitarist and composer. He was the vocalist of a popular Polish band, Trubadurzy, from 1963 to 1973 when he started his solo career. His creative activity in the area of music was characterized by a combination of various music genres such as rock and roll, country music and rhythm & blues. His album To co w życiu ważne reached number one on the Polish Music Charts.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d0/Krawczyk_2019.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/krzysztof-krawczyk/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shahram Shabpareh]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shahram-shabpareh/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shahram Shabpareh is an Iranian Pop singer and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0e/Shahramshabpare.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shahram-shabpareh/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:37 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>