<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Dance Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Dance Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 19:07:34 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shakira]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shakira Isabel Mebarak Ripoll is a Colombian singer, songwriter, dancer, businesswoman, and philanthropist. Born and raised in Barranquilla, she made her recording debut under Sony Music Colombia at the age of 13. Following the commercial failure of her first two Colombian albums, Magia (1991) and Peligro (1993), she rose to prominence in Spanish-speaking countries with her next albums, Pies Descalzos (1995) and Dónde Están los Ladrones? (1998). Shakira entered the English-language market with her fifth album, Laundry Service (2001). It sold over 13 million copies and spawned the international number-one singles 'Whenever, Wherever' and 'Underneath Your Clothes'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/Shakira_in_Toronto_2018.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sven-Erik Magnusson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sven-erik-magnusson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Knut Sven-Erik Magnusson was a Swedish singer and musician known for being the lead singer of the band Sven-Ingvars that during their sixty-year history played many different types of popular music, and was at times regarded as a dansband. The band had its last tour during the summer of 2016 with their last show on 21 August that year in Blekinge.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/05/Sven-Erik_Magnusson_2016.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sven-erik-magnusson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Katy Perry]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/katy-perry/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Katheryn Elizabeth Hudson, known professionally as Katy Perry, is an American singer, songwriter and television judge. After singing in church during her childhood, she pursued a career in gospel music as a teenager. Perry signed with Red Hill Records and released her debut studio album Katy Hudson under her birth name in 2001, which was commercially unsuccessful. She moved to Los Angeles the following year to venture into secular music after Red Hill ceased operations and she subsequently began working with producers Glen Ballard, Dr. Luke, and Max Martin. After adopting the stage name Katy Perry and being dropped by The Island Def Jam Music Group and Columbia Records, she signed a recording contract with Capitol Records in April 2007.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Katy_Perry_2019_by_Glenn_Francis.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/katy-perry/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Holly Johnson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/holly-johnson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Holly Johnson, known professionally as Holly Johnson, is an English artist, musician, and writer, best known as the lead vocalist of Frankie Goes to Hollywood, who achieved huge commercial success in the mid-1980s. Prior to that, in the late 1970s he was a bassist for the band Big in Japan. In 1989, Johnson's debut solo album, Blast, reached number one in the UK albums chart. Two singles from the album – 'Love Train' and 'Americanos' – reached the top 5 of the UK Singles Chart. In the 1990s he also embarked on writing, painting, and printmaking careers.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7e/Holly_Johnson2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/holly-johnson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robbie Williams]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-williams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Peter Williams is an English singer-songwriter and entertainer. He found fame as a member of the pop group Take That from 1989 to 1995, but achieved greater commercial success with his solo career, beginning in 1997. Williams has released seven UK number one singles and ten out of his eleven studio albums have reached number one in the UK. He is the best-selling British solo artist in the United Kingdom and the best selling non-Latino artist in Latin America. Six of his albums are among the top 100 biggest-selling albums in the United Kingdom–four albums in the top 60–and in 2006 he entered the Guinness Book of World Records for selling 1.6 million tickets of his Close Encounters Tour in a single day.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/Robbie_Williams.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-williams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Charo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/charo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>María del Rosario Pilar Martínez Molina Baeza, professionally known simply by her stage name Charo, is a Spanish American actress, singer, comedian, and flamenco guitarist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d7/Charo_2013_ALMA_Awards.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/charo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shahram Shabpareh]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shahram-shabpareh/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shahram Shabpareh is an Iranian Pop singer and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0e/Shahramshabpare.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shahram-shabpareh/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>