<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Speed Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Speed Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:52 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jeff Hanneman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeff-hanneman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jeffrey John Hanneman was an American musician, best known as a founding member of the American thrash metal band Slayer. Hanneman contributed both lyrical and musical material to every Slayer album up until his death in 2013 and wrote the songs 'Raining Blood', 'War Ensemble,' 'South of Heaven,' 'Seasons in the Abyss,' and 'Angel of Death,' all of which have been played at almost every live Slayer performance after their respective compositions. He had his own signature guitar, the ESP Jeff Hanneman Signature model.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d4/Jeff_Hanneman_f9e_o.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeff-hanneman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[James Hetfield]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-hetfield/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Alan Hetfield is an American musician and songwriter best known for being the co-founder, lead vocalist/rhythm guitarist and main songwriter for the American heavy metal band Metallica. Hetfield is mainly known for his intricate rhythm playing, but occasionally performs lead guitar duties and solos, both live and in the studio. Hetfield co-founded Metallica in October 1981 after answering an advertisement by drummer Lars Ulrich in the Los Angeles newspaper The Recycler. Metallica has won nine Grammy Awards and released ten studio albums, three live albums, four extended plays and 24 singles.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fd/JamesHetfield2012.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-hetfield/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lemmy Kilmister]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lemmy/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ian Fraser 'Lemmy' Kilmister was an English singer, songwriter, and musician, best known as the founder, lead singer, bassist, and primary songwriter of the heavy metal band Motörhead.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/af/Motorhead-01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lemmy/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jeffrey Dunn]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeffrey-dunn/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jeff 'Mantas' Dunn is a British guitarist best known as one of the founder members of seminal thrash/speed metal band Venom, with which he played as a guitarist from 1979 to 1985 and 1989 to 2002.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1b/Mantas_in_London%2C_2014.02.19.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeffrey-dunn/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jim Root]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jim-root/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Donald Root, also known by his number #4, is an American musician, songwriter, and guitarist. He is one of two guitarists for the American heavy metal band Slipknot, and the former lead guitarist for the American alternative metal band Stone Sour.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6f/Orange-jim-root_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jim-root/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Mustaine]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-mustaine/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Scott Mustaine is an American guitarist, singer, songwriter, actor and author. He is best known as the co-founder, lead vocalist, guitarist and primary songwriter of the American heavy metal band Megadeth, as well as the original lead guitarist of the American band Metallica.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/41/Megadeth_performing_in_San_Antonio%2C_Texas_%2827420120171%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-mustaine/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marty Friedman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marty-friedman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Martin Adam 'Marty' Friedman is an American guitarist, known for his tenure as the lead guitarist for heavy metal band Megadeth which spanned nearly the full decade of the 1990s. He is also known for playing alongside Jason Becker in Cacophony until 1989, as well as his 13 solo albums and tours. Friedman has resided in Tokyo, Japan since 2003, where he has appeared on over 700 Japanese television programs such as Rock Fujiyama, Hebimeta-san, Kouhaku uta gassen and Jukebox English. He has released albums with several record labels, including Avex Trax, Universal, EMI, Prosthetic and Shrapnel Records.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/76/Marty_Friedman_13.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marty-friedman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>