<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Synthesizer</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Synthesizer</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:52:56 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Shinoda]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Kenji Shinoda is an American musician, singer, songwriter, rapper, record producer, and graphic designer. He co-founded Linkin Park in 1996 and is the band's rhythm guitarist, primary songwriter, keyboardist, producer, and co-lead vocalist. Shinoda later created a hip-hop-driven side project, Fort Minor, in 2004. He has also served as a producer for tracks and albums by Lupe Fiasco, Styles of Beyond and the X-Ecutioners.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/Mike_Shinoda_4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Scott Weiland]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-weiland/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Scott Richard Weiland was an American musician, singer and songwriter. During a career spanning three decades, Weiland was best known as the lead singer of the band Stone Temple Pilots from 1989 to 2002 and 2008 to 2013, making six records with them. He was also lead vocalist of supergroup Velvet Revolver from 2003 to 2008, recording two albums, and he recorded one album with another supergroup, Art of Anarchy. He also established himself as a solo artist, releasing three studio albums, two cover albums, and collaborations with several other musicians throughout his career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/Scott_Weiland_3.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-weiland/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Yuri Antonov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yuri-antonov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Yuri Mikhailovich Antonov is a Soviet and Russian composer, singer and musician, People's Artist of Russia (1997). He is also the Distinguished performer of arts of the Russian Federation (Russia) and the Distinguished artist of the Chechnya-Ingushetia ASSR (1983).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6d/Yuri_Antonov_%28musician%29_%282015-12-10%29_04.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yuri-antonov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>