<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Contemporary R&B</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Contemporary R&B</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 12:46:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Jonas]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-jonas/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Adam Jonas is an American singer, songwriter, actor, and dancer. He rose to fame as a member of the pop rock band the Jonas Brothers, alongside his brothers Kevin and Nick. The group released their debut studio album It's About Time through the Columbia label in 2006, which failed to achieve commercial success. After signing with Hollywood Records, the group released their self-titled second studio album in 2007, which became their breakthrough record. The band became prominent figures on the Disney Channel during this time, gaining a large following through the network: they appeared in the widely successful musical television film Camp Rock (2008) and its sequel Camp Rock 2: The Final Jam (2010) as well as two of their own series, Jonas Brothers: Living the Dream (2008–2010) and Jonas (2009–2010).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a8/Joe_Jonas_2012_%28Straighten_Crop%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-jonas/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Post Malone]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/post-malone/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Austin Richard Post, known professionally as Post Malone, is an American rapper, singer, songwriter, record producer, and actor. Known for his tattoos, introspective songwriting, and laconic vocal style, Malone has gained acclaim for blending a range of genres including hip hop, R&B, pop, trap, rap rock, and cloud rap. He first attained recognition in 2015 following the release of his debut single 'White Iverson'. He subsequently signed a recording contract with Republic Records. His stage name is derived from his last name and from a rap name generator.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/99/Post_Malone_in_Chicago_2020.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/post-malone/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Justin Bieber]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/justin-bieber/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Justin Drew Bieber is a Canadian singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. Discovered at age 13 by talent manager Scooter Braun after he had watched his YouTube cover song videos, Bieber was signed to RBMG Records in 2008. With Bieber's debut EP My World, released in late 2009, Bieber became the first artist to have seven songs from a debut record chart on the Billboard Hot 100.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/Justin_Bieber_in_2015.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/justin-bieber/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Madonna]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/madonna/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Madonna Louise Ciccone is an American singer, songwriter, and actress. Referred to as the 'Queen of Pop', she is regarded as one of the most significant figures in popular culture. Madonna is noted for her continual reinvention and versatility in music production, songwriting, and visual presentation. She is also known for pushing the boundaries of artistic expression in mainstream music while remaining completely in charge of every aspect of her career. Her works, which incorporate social, political, sexual, and religious themes, have generated both critical acclaim and controversy. Madonna is often cited as an influence by other artists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Madonna_Rebel_Heart_Tour_2015_-_Stockholm_%2823051472299%29_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/madonna/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Corinne Bailey Rae]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/corinne-bailey-rae/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Corinne Jacqueline Bailey Rae is a British singer and songwriter. She is best known for her 2006 single 'Put Your Records On'. Bailey Rae was named the number-one predicted breakthrough act of 2006 in an annual BBC poll of music critics, Sound of 2006. She released her debut album, Corinne Bailey Rae, in February 2006, and became the fourth female British act in history to have her first album debut at number one. In 2007, Bailey Rae was nominated for three Grammy Awards and three Brit Awards, and won two MOBO Awards. In 2008, she won a Grammy Award for Album of the Year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1a/Corinne_Bailey_Rae_at_Divan_du_Monde%2C_Jan_2009.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/corinne-bailey-rae/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Prince]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/prince/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Prince Rogers Nelson, known simply as Prince, or , was an American singer-songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, actor, and director. Widely regarded as one of the greatest musicians of his generation, he often played most or all instruments on his recordings. He was known for his flamboyant and androgynous persona, eclectic work, and wide vocal range, which included a far-reaching falsetto and high-pitched screams.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d6/Prince_at_Coachella_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/prince/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[D'Angelo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/d'angelo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Eugene Archer, better known by his stage name D'Angelo, is an American singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist and record producer. D'Angelo is associated with the neo soul movement, along with artists like Erykah Badu, Lauryn Hill, Maxwell, and collaborator Angie Stone.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1f/D%27Angelo_Pori_Jazz_2012.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/d'angelo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nelly Furtado]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nelly Kim Furtado is a Canadian singer and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5b/Nelly_Furtado_at_Radio_Regenbogen_Award_2017_%285%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Johnny Marr]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/johnny-marr/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Johnny Marr is an English musician, songwriter, and singer. He first achieved fame as the guitarist and co-songwriter of The Smiths, who were active from 1982 to 1987. He has since performed with numerous other bands and embarked on a solo career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/37/Johnny_Marr_University_of_Salford_2012_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/johnny-marr/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian McKnight]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-mcknight/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Kelly McKnight is an American singer, songwriter, actor, record producer, and multi-instrumentalist. McKnight is most recognized for his strong falsetto and belting range. His work has earned him 16 Grammy Awards nominations, third only to Zubin Mehta and Snoop Dogg for the record of most Grammy nominations without a win.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ac/Brian_McKnight.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-mcknight/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>