<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Post Grunge</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Post Grunge</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 01:11:11 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alanis Morissette]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alanis Nadine Morissette is a Canadian-American singer, songwriter, record producer, and actress. Known for her emotive mezzo-soprano voice, Morissette began her career in Canada in the early 1990s with two mildly successful dance-pop albums. Afterwards, as part of a recording deal, she moved to Holmby Hills, Los Angeles and in 1995 released Jagged Little Pill, a more rock-oriented album which sold more than 33 million copies globally and is her most critically acclaimed work. Her follow-up album, Supposed Former Infatuation Junkie, was released in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Alanis_Morissette_5-19-2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shannon Leto]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shannon-leto/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shannon Leto is an American musician and songwriter best known as the drummer of rock band Thirty Seconds to Mars. He co-founded the group in 1998 in Los Angeles, California, with his younger brother Jared. Their debut album, 30 Seconds to Mars (2002), was released to positive reviews but only to limited success. The band achieved worldwide fame with the release of their second album A Beautiful Lie (2005). Their following releases, This Is War (2009) and Love, Lust, Faith and Dreams (2013), received further critical and commercial success. As of September 2014, the band has sold over 15 million albums worldwide.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d0/Shannon_Leto_-_2009_Buzz_Bake_Sale.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shannon-leto/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jared Leto]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jared-leto/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jared Joseph Leto is an American actor and singer-songwriter. After starting his career with television appearances in the early 1990s, Leto achieved recognition for his role as Jordan Catalano on the television series My So-Called Life (1994). He made his film debut in How to Make an American Quilt (1995) and received critical praise for his performance in Prefontaine (1997). Leto played supporting roles in The Thin Red Line (1998), Fight Club (1999) and American Psycho (2000), as well as the lead role in Urban Legend (1998), and earned critical acclaim after portraying heroin addict Harry Goldfarb in Requiem for a Dream (2000). He later began focusing increasingly on his music career, returning to acting with Panic Room (2002), Alexander (2004), Lord of War (2005), Lonely Hearts (2006), Chapter 27 (2007), and Mr. Nobody (2009). In 2012, he directed the documentary film Artifact. He then appeared in Suicide Squad (2016) and Blade Runner 2049 (2017).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/00/Jared_Leto%2C_San_Diego_Comic_Con_2016_%282%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jared-leto/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roy Mayorga]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-mayorga/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roy Maurice Mayorga is an American musician, best known as the drummer for the American heavy metal bands Hellyeah and Stone Sour. He is of Ecuadorian and Cuban descent.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/dc/Roy_Mayorga_at_the_Rockstar_Uproar_Festival.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-mayorga/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jim Root]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jim-root/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Donald Root, also known by his number #4, is an American musician, songwriter, and guitarist. He is one of two guitarists for the American heavy metal band Slipknot, and the former lead guitarist for the American alternative metal band Stone Sour.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6f/Orange-jim-root_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jim-root/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Myles Kennedy]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/myles-kennedy/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Myles Richard Bass, known professionally as Myles Kennedy, is an American musician, singer, and songwriter, best known as the lead vocalist and rhythm guitarist of the rock band Alter Bridge, and as the lead vocalist in guitarist Slash's backing band, known as Myles Kennedy and the Conspirators. A former guitar instructor from Spokane, Washington, he has worked as a session musician and songwriter, making both studio and live appearances with several artists, and has been involved with several projects throughout his career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/88/20170615-079-Nova_Rock_2017-Alter_Bridge-Myles_Kennedy_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/myles-kennedy/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lacey Sturm]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lacey-sturm/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lacey Nicole Sturm is an American singer and songwriter born in Homestead, Florida and raised in Arlington, Texas. She is a co-founder and former lead vocalist of the hard rock band Flyleaf. In February 2016, Sturm became the first solo female to top the Billboard Hard Rock Albums chart with her debut release.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/12/Lacey_Sturm_%28Flyleaf%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lacey-sturm/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Wes Scantlin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wes-scantlin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Wesley Reid Scantlin is an American singer, songwriter, musician, and the only remaining founding member of the American post-grunge band Puddle of Mudd.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/86/Wes_Scantlin_Puddle_of_Mudd_2009.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wes-scantlin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shaun Morgan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shaun-morgan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shaun Morgan Welgemoed, known publicly as Shaun Morgan, is a South African musician. He is the singer, songwriter, and guitarist for South African rock band Seether.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/51/ShaunMorganInChicago.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shaun-morgan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>