<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Post Grunge</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Post Grunge</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 20:55:42 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lacey Sturm]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lacey-sturm/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lacey Nicole Sturm is an American singer and songwriter born in Homestead, Florida, and raised in Arlington, Texas. She is a co-founder and former lead vocalist of the hard rock band Flyleaf. In February 2016, Sturm became the first solo female artist to top the Billboard Hard Rock Albums chart with her debut release Life Screams.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/12/Lacey_Sturm_%28Flyleaf%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lacey-sturm/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Wes Scantlin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wes-scantlin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Wesley Reid Scantlin is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. He is best known as the lead vocalist, guitarist, and only constant member of rock band Puddle of Mudd. He was named one of the 'Top 100 Heavy Metal Vocalists' by Hit Parader.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/41/Wes_Scantlin_Puddle_of_Mudd_2009_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wes-scantlin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shannon Leto]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shannon-leto/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shannon Leto is an American musician and songwriter best known as the drummer of rock band Thirty Seconds to Mars. He co-founded the group in 1998 in Los Angeles, California, with his younger brother Jared. Their debut album, 30 Seconds to Mars (2002), was released to positive reviews but only to limited success. The band achieved worldwide fame with the release of their second album A Beautiful Lie (2005). Their following releases, This Is War (2009) and Love, Lust, Faith and Dreams (2013), received further critical and commercial success. As of September 2014, the band has sold over 15 million albums worldwide.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d0/Shannon_Leto_-_2009_Buzz_Bake_Sale.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shannon-leto/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dale Stewart]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dale-stewart/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dale William Stewart is a South African musician, best known as the bass guitarist for the South African rock band Seether.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/93/Dale_Stewart_at_Incirlik.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dale-stewart/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shaun Morgan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shaun-morgan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shaun Morgan Welgemoed, known publicly as Shaun Morgan, is a South African musician. He is the singer, songwriter, and guitarist for rock band Seether.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/51/ShaunMorganInChicago.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shaun-morgan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jared Leto]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jared-leto/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jared Joseph Leto is an American actor and musician. After starting his career with television appearances in the early 1990s, Leto achieved recognition for his role as Jordan Catalano on the television series My So-Called Life (1994). He made his film debut in How to Make an American Quilt (1995) and received critical praise for his performance in Prefontaine (1997).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/00/Jared_Leto%2C_San_Diego_Comic_Con_2016_%282%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jared-leto/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jim Root]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jim-root/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Donald Root, also known as #4, is an American guitarist and songwriter. He is one of two guitarists for heavy metal band Slipknot and the former lead guitarist for rock band Stone Sour.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6f/Orange-jim-root_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jim-root/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American singer, songwriter, and musician best known as the lead vocalist and rhythm guitarist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. He also had a solo career and contributed to soundtracks. Cornell was also the founder and frontman of Temple of the Dog, a one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/58/ChrisCornellTIFFSept2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Myles Kennedy]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/myles-kennedy/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Myles Richard Bass, known professionally as Myles Kennedy, is an American musician, singer, and songwriter, best known as the lead vocalist and rhythm guitarist of the rock band Alter Bridge, and as the lead vocalist in guitarist Slash's backing band, known as Myles Kennedy and the Conspirators. A former guitar instructor from Spokane, Washington, he has worked as a session musician and songwriter, making both studio and live appearances with several artists, and has been involved with several projects throughout his career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/88/20170615-079-Nova_Rock_2017-Alter_Bridge-Myles_Kennedy_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/myles-kennedy/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alanis Morissette]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alanis Nadine Morissette is a Canadian-American singer, songwriter, musician, and actress. Known for her emotive mezzo-soprano voice, Morissette began her career in Canada in the early 1990s with two mildly successful dance-pop albums. Afterward, as part of a recording deal, she moved to Holmby Hills, Los Angeles. In 1995, she released Jagged Little Pill, a more rock-oriented album which sold more than 33 million copies globally and is her most critically acclaimed work to date. This was made into a rock musical of the same name in 2017, which earned 15 Tony Award nominations including Best Musical. Her more experimental follow-up album, electronic-infused Supposed Former Infatuation Junkie, was released in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Alanis_Morissette_5-19-2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>