<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Appalachian Dulcimer</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Appalachian Dulcimer</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 19:07:34 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lewis Brian Hopkins Jones was an English musician, best known as the founder and original leader of the Rolling Stones. Initially a slide guitarist, Jones would go on to play a wide variety of instruments on Rolling Stones recordings and in concerts, such as rhythm and lead guitar, sitar, dulcimer, various keyboard instruments such as piano and mellotron, marimba, wind instruments such as harmonica, recorder, saxophone, as well as drums, vocals and numerous others.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6b/Brian_Jones%2C_Statesboro%2C_Georgia%2C_May_4%2C_1965_%28377872218%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joni Mitchell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joni-mitchell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roberta Joan 'Joni' Mitchell is a Canadian singer-songwriter. Drawing from folk, pop, rock, and jazz, Mitchell's songs often reflect social and environmental ideals as well as her feelings about romance, confusion, disillusionment, and joy. She has received many accolades, including nine Grammy Awards and induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1997. Rolling Stone called her 'one of the greatest songwriters ever', and AllMusic has stated, 'When the dust settles, Joni Mitchell may stand as the most important and influential female recording artist of the late 20th century'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a9/1974_Joni_Mitchell.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joni-mitchell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bert Jansch]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bert-jansch/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Herbert Jansch was a Scottish folk musician and founding member of the band Pentangle. He was born in Glasgow and came to prominence in London in the 1960s, as an acoustic guitarist, as well as a singer-songwriter. He recorded at least 25 albums and toured extensively from the 1960s to the 21st century.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b0/BertJansch.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bert-jansch/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Richard Thompson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-thompson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Thompson is an English singer, songwriter, and guitarist. He made his début as a recording artist as a member of Fairport Convention in September 1967. He continues to write and record new material regularly and frequently performs live at venues throughout the world.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/ce/Richard_Thompson_-_6-21-07_-_Photo_by_Anthony_Pepitone.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-thompson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Peter Buck]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-buck/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Peter Lawrence Buck is an American musician and songwriter who is best known as co-founder and lead guitarist of the alternative rock band R.E.M.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Peter_Buck_of_REM_in_looking_over_shoulder.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-buck/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Simon Nicol]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/simon-nicol/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Simon John Breckenridge Nicol is an English guitarist, singer, multi-instrumentalist and record producer. He was a founding member of British folk rock group Fairport Convention and is the only founding member still in the band. He has also been involved with the Albion Band and a wide range of musical projects, both as a collaborator, producer and as a solo artist. He has received several awards for his work and career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/33/Simon_Nicol.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/simon-nicol/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>