<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Space Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Space Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 20:40:49 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shannon Leto]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shannon-leto/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shannon Leto is an American musician and songwriter best known as the drummer of rock band Thirty Seconds to Mars. He co-founded the group in 1998 in Los Angeles, California, with his younger brother Jared. Their debut album, 30 Seconds to Mars (2002), was released to positive reviews but only to limited success. The band achieved worldwide fame with the release of their second album A Beautiful Lie (2005). Their following releases, This Is War (2009) and Love, Lust, Faith and Dreams (2013), received further critical and commercial success. As of September 2014, the band has sold over 15 million albums worldwide.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d0/Shannon_Leto_-_2009_Buzz_Bake_Sale.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shannon-leto/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Brock]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-brock/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Anthony Brock is an English singer-songwriter and musician. He plays electric guitar, keyboards, bass and oscillators. He is best known as being one of the founders and musical focus of the English space rock group Hawkwind. Brock is the only member of the group to have been a constant throughout the band's history. Brock was honoured with a lifetime achievement award at the annual Progressive Music Awards in 2013.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/64/Dave_Brock_Hawkwind.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-brock/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lemmy Kilmister]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lemmy/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ian Fraser 'Lemmy' Kilmister was an English singer, songwriter, and musician, best known as the founder, lead singer, bassist, and primary songwriter of the heavy metal band Motörhead.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/af/Motorhead-01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lemmy/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Syd Barrett]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/syd-barrett/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roger Keith 'Syd' Barrett was an English singer, songwriter, and musician who co-founded the rock band Pink Floyd in 1965. Characterised for his English-accented singing and free-form writing style, Barrett named the group and was their original lead singer, guitarist and principal songwriter. His innovative use of guitar techniques, such as dissonance, distortion and feedback, proved influential to many musicians.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Syd_barrett.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/syd-barrett/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>