<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Space Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Space Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 13:58:34 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shannon Leto]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shannon-leto/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shannon Leto is an American musician and songwriter best known as the drummer of rock band Thirty Seconds to Mars. He co-founded the group in 1998 in Los Angeles, California, with his younger brother Jared. Their debut album, 30 Seconds to Mars (2002), was released to positive reviews but only to limited success. The band achieved worldwide fame with the release of their second album A Beautiful Lie (2005). Their following releases, This Is War (2009) and Love, Lust, Faith and Dreams (2013), received further critical and commercial success. As of September 2014, the band has sold over 15 million albums worldwide.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d0/Shannon_Leto_-_2009_Buzz_Bake_Sale.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shannon-leto/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Richard Ashcroft]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-ashcroft/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Paul Ashcroft is an English singer and songwriter. He was the lead singer and occasional rhythm guitarist of the alternative rock band The Verve from their formation in 1990 until their original split in 1999. Songs he wrote for the band include 'Bitter Sweet Symphony', 'Lucky Man', and the UK number one 'The Drugs Don't Work'. He became a successful solo artist, releasing three UK top three solo albums. The Verve reformed in 2007 but again broke up by summer 2009. Ashcroft then founded a new band, RPA & The United Nations of Sound, and released a new album on 19 July 2010. Ashcroft released his fourth solo album, These People, on 20 May 2016.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/68/Richardashcroft.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-ashcroft/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lemmy]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lemmy/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ian Fraser Kilmister, better known as Lemmy, was a British singer, songwriter, and musician. He is best known as the founder, lead singer, bassist, primary songwriter and only continuous member of the British rock band Motörhead.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/af/Motorhead-01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lemmy/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Syd Barrett]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/syd-barrett/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roger Keith 'Syd' Barrett was an English singer, songwriter, musician and painter who co-founded the rock band Pink Floyd in 1965. Barrett was their original frontman and primary songwriter, becoming known for his whimsical take on psychedelia, English-accented singing, literary influences, and stream-of-consciousness writing style. As a guitarist, he was influential for his free-form playing and for employing dissonance, distortion, echo, feedback, and other studio effects.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Syd_barrett.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/syd-barrett/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Brock]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-brock/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/64/Dave_Brock_Hawkwind.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-brock/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:38 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>