<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Death Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Death Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 20:40:49 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Duplantier]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-duplantier/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Andrew Duplantier is a French musician best known as the rhythm guitarist and vocalist of metal band Gojira. He is also the former bassist of Cavalera Conspiracy, to which he was invited by Max Cavalera.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e0/W0840-Hellfest2013_Gojira_JosephDuplantier_71163.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-duplantier/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Piotr Wiwczarek]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/piotr-wiwczarek/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Piotr Paweł Wiwczarek, also known as Peter, is a Polish musician who is the vocalist and lead guitarist for the death metal band Vader, as the only constant member of the band since its inception. He has also collaborated with Kazimierz 'Para' Paraszczuk on his tribute album, Bandid Rockin', and is the producer of several of Vader's releases. He is also the founder and guitarist of a side-project, named Panzer X.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/65/Piotr_Wiwczarek.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/piotr-wiwczarek/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alex Webster]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alex-webster/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alex Webster is an American bass player, who is best known as a member of the death metal band Cannibal Corpse. He is one of two current members who were of the original lineup of the band, the other being drummer Paul Mazurkiewicz. He is also the bassist for the band Blotted Science and the supergroup Conquering Dystopia, and before Cannibal Corpse was formed he was part of Beyond Death.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/42/Alex_Webster_of_Cannibal_Corpse.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alex-webster/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mick Thomson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mick-thomson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Mickael Gordon 'Mick' Thomson is an American heavy metal musician. He is one of two guitarists in the band Slipknot, in which he is designated #7. Thomson originally met founding Slipknot members Anders Colsefni, Donnie Steele and Paul Gray through their mutual involvement in death metal band Body Pit, and later joined in early 1996. Following the departure of Joey Jordison in 2013, Thomson is now the third longest-serving member of Slipknot.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/41/Mick_Thomson_unmasked.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mick-thomson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul Gray]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-gray-(american-musician)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul Dedrick Gray also known as the Pig or by his number #2, was an American musician best known as the former bassist, backing vocalist, songwriter and one of the founding members of the Grammy Award-winning heavy metal band Slipknot.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0b/Paul_Gray_at_Mayhem.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-gray-(american-musician)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paulo Jr.]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paulo-jr./]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paulo Xisto Pinto Jr. is a Brazilian musician/bassist for heavy metal band Sepultura. Pinto joined Sepultura after 'Gato''s split in 1984, becoming Sepultura's second and only bassist ever and although no original members are left in Sepultura, Pinto is the longest remaining member of Sepultura.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/aa/20140613-016-Nova_Rock_2014-Sepultura-Paulo_Xisto_Pinto_Jr.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paulo-jr./]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Fenriz]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fenriz/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gylve Fenris Nagell, better known as Fenriz, is a Norwegian musician and politician who is best known as being one half of the metal duo Darkthrone, alongside Nocturno Culto. Although primarily a drummer, he has also performed bass, guitar, and vocals for Darkthrone and a number of other metal bands. Fenriz is known for his encyclopedic knowledge of many different forms of music, his eager support of other underground bands, and his lack of interest in the mainstream music business in general. Fenriz has had multiple solo projects, including the folk black metal project Isengard, the dark ambient project Neptune Towers and the doom metal project Valhall.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/67/Fenriz.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fenriz/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[James Murphy]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-murphy-(guitarist)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Franklin Murphy is an American guitarist. He is best known for his work in metal bands, Obituary, Death and Testament. He founded Disincarnate, an early death metal band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a2/James_Murphy_in_the_dressing_room_at_the_Nokia_Theater.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-murphy-(guitarist)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Phil Anselmo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/phil-anselmo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Philip Hansen Anselmo is an American heavy metal musician who is best known as the lead vocalist for Pantera, Down, and Superjoint Ritual. He is also the owner of Housecore Records and has been involved with several other bands.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f3/W0829-Hellfest2013_Down_PhilAnselmo_69245.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/phil-anselmo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Trevor Peres]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trevor-peres/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Trevor Peres is an American heavy metal musician best known as the guitarist, songwriter and one of the founding members of the death metal band Obituary.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/28/Trevor_Peres.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trevor-peres/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>