<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Fourplay</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Fourplay</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 23:07:06 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Larry Carlton]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/larry-carlton/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Larry Eugene Carlton is an American guitarist who built his career as a studio musician in the 1970s and '80s for acts such as Steely Dan and Joni Mitchell. He has participated in thousands of recording sessions, recorded on hundreds of albums in many genres, for television and movies, and on more than 100 gold records. He has been a member of the jazz fusion group the Crusaders, the smooth jazz band Fourplay, and has maintained a long solo career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b7/Larry_Carlton_Gibson_ES-335.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/larry-carlton/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nathan East]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nathan-east/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nathan Harrell East is an American jazz, R&B, and rock bass player and vocalist. With more than 2,000 recordings, East is considered one of the most recorded bass players in the history of music. East holds a Bachelor of Arts degree in Music from the University of California, San Diego (1978). He is a founding member of contemporary jazz quartet Fourplay and has recorded, performed, and co-written songs with performers such as Bobby Womack, Eric Clapton, Michael Jackson, Joe Satriani, Peter Gabriel, George Harrison, Ringo Starr, Phil Collins, Stevie Wonder, Toto, Kenny Loggins, Daft Punk, Chick Corea, and Herbie Hancock.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/NathanEast2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nathan-east/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>