<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Funk Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Funk Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 13:38:44 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lenny Kravitz]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lenny-kravitz/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Leonard Albert Kravitz is an American singer, songwriter, musician, record producer, and actor. His style incorporates elements of rock, blues, soul, R&B, funk, jazz, reggae, hard rock, psychedelic, pop, folk, and ballads.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ac/Lenny_Kravitz_by_Gage_Skidmore.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lenny-kravitz/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Prince]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/prince/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Prince Rogers Nelson, known simply as Prince, or , was an American singer-songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, actor, and director. Widely regarded as one of the greatest musicians of his generation, he often played most or all instruments on his recordings. He was known for his flamboyant and androgynous persona, eclectic work, and wide vocal range, which included a far-reaching falsetto and high-pitched screams.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d6/Prince_at_Coachella_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/prince/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Phil Collins]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/phil-collins/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Philip David Charles Collins is an English drummer, singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, and actor, best known as the drummer/singer of the rock band Genesis and for his solo career. Between 1982 and 1990, Collins scored three UK and seven US number-one singles in his solo career. When his work with Genesis, his work with other artists, as well as his solo career is totalled, he had more US Top 40 singles than any other artist during the 1980s. His most successful singles from the period include 'In the Air Tonight', 'Against All Odds ', 'One More Night', 'Sussudio', 'Two Hearts', 'A Groovy Kind of Love', 'I Wish It Would Rain Down', and 'Another Day in Paradise'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1a/Phil_Collins_Duesseldorf.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/phil-collins/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:38 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>