<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Funk Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Funk Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 01:03:46 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lenny Kravitz]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lenny-kravitz/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Leonard Albert Kravitz is an American singer, songwriter, actor, record producer, and multi-instrumentalist. His 'retro' style incorporates elements of rock, blues, soul, R&B, funk, jazz, reggae, hard rock, psychedelic, pop, folk, and ballads.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/28/Lenny_Kravitz_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lenny-kravitz/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anthony Kiedis]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anthony-kiedis/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Anthony Kiedis is an American musician, singer, songwriter, rapper, and actor. He is best known as a founding member and the lead vocalist of the Red Hot Chili Peppers and has appeared on every album released by the band. Kiedis and his fellow band members were inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 2012.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cd/2016_RiP_Red_Hot_Chili_Peppers_-_Anthony_Kiedis_-_by_2eight_-_DSC0349.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anthony-kiedis/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Phil Collins]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/phil-collins/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Philip David Charles Collins is an English drummer, singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, and actor. He was the drummer and later became singer of the rock band Genesis, and is also a solo artist. Between 1982 and 1989, Collins scored three UK and seven US number-one singles in his solo career. When his work with Genesis, his work with other artists, as well as his solo career is totalled, he had more US Top 40 singles than any other artist during the 1980s. His most successful singles from the period include 'In the Air Tonight', 'Against All Odds ', 'One More Night', 'Sussudio', 'Two Hearts' and 'Another Day in Paradise'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1a/Phil_Collins_Duesseldorf.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/phil-collins/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nikolai Noskov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nikolai-noskov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nikolai Ivanovich Noskov is a Russian singer and former vocalist of the hard rock band Gorky Park. Five-time winner of the Golden Gramophone. He was also a member of Москва (Moscow) ensemble in the early 1980s, in band Гран-при in 1988 just before joining Gorky Park, and much later in the 1990s in band Николай (Nikolai). Starting 1998 Noskov had a solo career releasing six solo albums. In 2015 he was jury in second season of reality TV series Glavnaya Stsena</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/32/%D0%9D%D0%B8%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%BB%D0%B0%D0%B9_%D0%9D%D0%BE%D1%81%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%B2_%D0%B2_2009_%284%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nikolai-noskov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>