<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Disco</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Disco</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:52:56 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Yuri Antonov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yuri-antonov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Yuri Mikhailovich Antonov is a Soviet and Russian composer, singer and musician, People's Artist of Russia (1997). He is also the Distinguished performer of arts of the Russian Federation (Russia) and the Distinguished artist of the Chechnya-Ingushetia ASSR (1983).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6d/Yuri_Antonov_%28musician%29_%282015-12-10%29_04.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yuri-antonov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Rick James]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rick-james/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Ambrose Johnson Jr., better known by his stage name Rick James, was an American singer-songwriter, multi-instrumentalist and producer. Born and raised in Buffalo, New York, James began his musical career in his teen years. He was in various bands before entering the U.S. Navy to avoid being drafted in the early 1960s. In 1964, James deserted to Toronto, Canada, where he formed the rock band the Mynah Birds, who eventually signed a recording deal with Motown Records in 1966. James' career with the group halted after military authorities discovered his whereabouts and eventually convicted James to a one-year prison term related to the draft charges. After being released, James moved to California where he started a variety of rock and funk groups in the late 1960s and early 1970s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4b/Rick_James_in_Lifestyles_of_the_Rich_1984.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rick-james/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>