<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Disco</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Disco</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 20:58:33 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bob Kulick]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-kulick/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/Bob_Kulick_2017.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-kulick/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kevin Parker]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kevin-parker/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kevin Richard Parker is an Australian singer, songwriter, musician, and record producer, best known for his musical project Tame Impala, for which he writes, performs, records, and produces the music. Parker has released four Tame Impala albums: Innerspeaker (2010), Lonerism (2012), Currents (2015), and The Slow Rush (2020). He has won 13 ARIA Music Awards, two APRA Awards, and a Brit Award, and has received four Grammy Award nominations.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/08/Tame_Impala_Performing_in_NYC_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kevin-parker/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Teena Marie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/teena-marie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Mary Christine Brockert, known professionally as Teena Marie, was an American singer-songwriter, musician, composer, arranger, and producer. She was known by her childhood nickname Tina before taking the stage name Teena Marie and later acquired the nickname Lady Tee, given to her by her collaborator and friend, Rick James.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/51/Teena_Marie.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/teena-marie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Norman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-norman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher Ward Norman is an English soft rock singer. Norman was the lead singer of Smokie, an English soft rock band which found success in Europe in the 1970s. 'Stumblin' In', a 1978 duet with Suzi Quatro, was a big US hit.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/63/Chris_norman_20081129.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-norman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Barry Gibb]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/barry-gibb/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir Barry Alan Crompton Gibb is a British-American musician, singer-songwriter and record producer who rose to worldwide fame as a co-founder of the group the Bee Gees, one of the most commercially successful groups in the history of popular music. With his younger brothers, twins Robin and Maurice Gibb, he formed a songwriting partnership beginning in 1955. He has lived in Britain, Australia, and the United States, holding dual UK–US citizenship.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f3/Barry_Gibb_in_2017-Glasto17-197_%2834744934874%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/barry-gibb/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Rick James]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rick-james/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Ambrose Johnson Jr., better known by his stage name Rick James, was an American singer-songwriter, multi-instrumentalist and record producer. Born and raised in Buffalo, New York, James began his musical career in his teen years. He was in various bands before entering the U.S. Navy to avoid being drafted into the army. In 1964, James deserted to Toronto, Canada, where he formed the rock band the Mynah Birds, who eventually signed a recording deal with Motown Records in 1966. James' career with the group halted after military authorities discovered his whereabouts and eventually convicted and sentenced James to a one-year prison term related to the desertion charges. After being released, James moved to California, where he started a variety of rock and funk groups in the late 1960s and early 1970s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4b/Rick_James_in_Lifestyles_of_the_Rich_1984.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rick-james/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Maurice Gibb]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/maurice-gibb/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Maurice Ernest Gibb was a British musician, singer, songwriter and record producer who achieved fame as a member of the Bee Gees. Although his elder brother Barry Gibb and fraternal twin brother Robin Gibb were the group's main lead singers, most of their albums included at least one or two songs featuring Maurice's lead vocals, including 'Lay It on Me', 'Country Woman' and 'On Time'. The Bee Gees were one of the most successful rock-pop groups of all time.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6b/Maurice_Gibb_2001.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/maurice-gibb/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Krzysztof Krawczyk]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/krzysztof-krawczyk/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Krzysztof January Krawczyk was a Polish baritone pop singer, guitarist and composer. He was the vocalist of a popular Polish band, Trubadurzy, from 1963 to 1973 when he started his solo career. His creative activity in the area of music was characterized by a combination of various music genres such as rock and roll, country music and rhythm & blues. His album To co w życiu ważne reached number one on the Polish Music Charts.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d0/Krawczyk_2019.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/krzysztof-krawczyk/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>