<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>RSS Feed</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>RSS Feed</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 23:54:38 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jimmy Rip]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jimmy-rip/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jimmy Rippetoe, better known by his stage name Jimmy Rip, is an American guitarist, songwriter and record producer, who is known for his work with Jerry Lee Lewis, Mick Jagger, Debbie Harry, Paul Collins & The Beat, Michael Monroe, Henry Lee Summer, Tom Verlaine and Television. Rip began playing guitar at the age of six.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Jimmy_Rip.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jimmy-rip/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Winehouse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Jade Winehouse was an English singer and songwriter. She was known for her deep, expressive contralto vocals and her eclectic mix of musical genres, including soul rhythm and blues, and jazz. Winehouse's debut album, Frank (2003), was a critical success in the UK and was nominated for the Mercury Prize. Her follow-up album, Back to Black (2006), led to five 2008 Grammy Awards, tying the then record for the most wins by a female artist in a single night, and made her the first British woman to win five Grammys, including three of the General Field 'Big Four' Grammy Awards: Best New Artist, Record of the Year and Song of the Year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Amy_Winehouse_f4962007_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gary Lachman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gary-lachman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gary Joseph Lachman, also known as Gary Valentine, is an American writer and musician.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6a/Blondie_%28Gary_Valentine_Lachman%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gary-lachman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Ford]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-ford/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David James Ford is an English singer-songwriter, guitarist and songwriter. He first achieved prominence with the indie rock group Easyworld, who released an independent mini-album, ...Better Ways to Self Destruct and two full-length albums on Jive Records before disbanding in 2004.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/67/David_Ford%2C_Toronto.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-ford/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roddy Radiation]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roddy-radiation/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roddy Radiation is an English musician who played lead guitar for The Specials, as well as many rockabilly bands such as the Bonediggers and the Tearjerkers. He wrote the Specials favourites 'Concrete Jungle', 'Rat Race' and 'Hey, Little Rich Girl', later covered by Amy Winehouse. Currently, Byers leads The Skabilly Rebels, a band that mixes ska rhythms with rockabilly.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a0/RoddyRadiationImage01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roddy-radiation/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jack Rose]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-rose-(guitarist)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack Rose was an American guitarist originally from Virginia and later based in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Rose is best known for his solo acoustic guitar work. He was also a member of the noise/drone band Pelt.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/01/Jack_Rose.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-rose-(guitarist)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[T-Bone Walker]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/t-bone-walker/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Aaron Thibeaux 'T-Bone' Walker was an American blues guitarist, singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist, who was a pioneer and innovator of the jump blues and electric blues sound. In 2018 Rolling Stone magazine ranked him number 37 on its list of 'The 100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ee/T-Bone_Walker_1972.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/t-bone-walker/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Axel Rudi Pell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/axel-rudi-pell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Axel Rudi Pell is a German heavy metal guitar player who currently works as a lead guitarist for an unnamed backing band he founded as a solo work. He started off with the band Steeler (1984–88) before leaving to start his solo career in 1989. During this time, he has played with such drummers as Jörg Michael and Mike Terrana, and singers Johnny Gioeli, Jeff Scott Soto, and Rob Rock.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/ca/Axel_Rudi_Pell.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/axel-rudi-pell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Howie Day]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/howie-day/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Howard Kern 'Howie' Day is an American singer-songwriter. Beginning his career as a solo artist in the late 1990s, Day became known for his extensive touring and in-concert use of samplers and effects pedals in order to accompany himself. He self-financed and self-released his first album, Australia, in 2000.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/30/Howiedaycrouching.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/howie-day/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Brown]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-brown-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Roger 'Joe' Brown, MBE is an English entertainer. He has worked as a rock and roll singer and guitarist for more than six decades. He was a stage and television performer in the late 1950s and has been a UK recording star since the early 1960s. He has made six films, presented specialist radio series for BBC Radio 2, appeared on the West End stage alongside Dame Anna Neagle and has written an autobiography. In recent years he has again concentrated on recording and performing music, playing two tours of around 100 shows every year and releasing an album almost every year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2d/Joe_Brown_On_Stage.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-brown-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>