<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Indie Pop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Indie Pop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:07:39 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Angelakos]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-angelakos/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael John Angelakos is an American musician of Greek descent, a singer, songwriter and record producer. He is best known as the frontman of the indie electronic band Passion Pit.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Flickr_-_moses_namkung_-_Passion_Pit_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-angelakos/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Rotheray]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-rotheray/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Rotheray is an English rock and pop musician, best known for being the lead guitarist for The Beautiful South.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c7/Drwiki.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-rotheray/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jack Antonoff]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-antonoff/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack Michael Antonoff is an American singer, songwriter and record producer. Antonoff is the lead singer of indie pop band Bleachers, and a guitarist and drummer in the indie rock band Fun. He was previously the lead singer of the indie rock band Steel Train. Aside from his work with Bleachers and Fun, Antonoff has worked as a songwriter and record producer with various artists, including Taylor Swift, Lorde, St. Vincent, Lana Del Rey, Kevin Abstract, Carly Rae Jepsen, and Troye Sivan. Antonoff has been nominated for a Golden Globe Award and won four Grammy Awards: two for his work with Fun, one for production on Taylor Swift's album 1989, and one with St. Vincent for writing the title track on Masseduction. He also started his own music festival, Shadow of The City, which takes place annually in New Jersey.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/75/Antonoff_at_Radio_Station.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-antonoff/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Macdonald]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-macdonald/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Elizabeth Macdonald is a Scottish singer-songwriter, guitarist, and musician. She has sold over 12 million records worldwide. Macdonald released her debut album This Is the Life in 2007. The singles 'Mr. Rock & Roll' and 'This Is the Life' from it were chart hits. The latter charted at number one in six countries, while reaching the top 10 in another 11 countries. The album reached number one in four European countries – the United Kingdom, Denmark, the Netherlands and Switzerland – and sold three million copies worldwide. Moderate success in the American music market followed in 2008. She was a guest on shows such as The Ellen DeGeneres Show and The Late Late Show with Craig Ferguson, where she performed two singles from the album, and This Is the Life reached number 92 on the Billboard 200.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6c/Amy_MacDonald-9546.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-macdonald/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Rachel Goswell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rachel-goswell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Rachel Ann Goswell is an English singer-songwriter and musician who rose to prominence as vocalist and guitarist of the shoegaze band Slowdive, which formed in 1989. Goswell, along with Neil Halstead, Ian McCutcheon and former Chapterhouse member Simon Rowe became Mojave 3 when Slowdive transitioned to a more country/folk rock style. She released a solo album in 2004, titled Waves Are Universal on 4AD Records.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/aa/2014_WGT_281_Slowdive.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rachel-goswell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nanna Bryndís Hilmarsdóttir]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nanna-bryndís-hilmarsdóttir/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nanna Bryndís Hilmarsdóttir is an Icelandic musician. She is the lead vocalist and guitarist, along with Ragnar 'Raggi' Þórhallsson, of the Icelandic indie folk band Of Monsters and Men.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/89/Nanna-Bryndis-Hilmarsdottir-01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nanna-bryndís-hilmarsdóttir/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dev Hynes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dev-hynes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Devonté Hynes, also known as Blood Orange and formerly Lightspeed Champion, is an English singer, songwriter, record producer and director. From 2004 to 2006, Hynes was a member of the band Test Icicles, playing guitar, synth, and occasionally performing vocals. They released one full-length album in 2005. Hynes went on to release two solo studio albums as Lightspeed Champion and subsequently four more as Blood Orange, between 2008 and 2018.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d9/Lightspeed_Champion_at_Primavera_Sound_Festival.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dev-hynes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lights]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lights/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lights Poxleitner-Bokan, known mononymously as Lights, is a Canadian musician, singer, songwriter, author, and illustrator. She is known for her gold-certified albums The Listening and Siberia as well as singles 'Drive My Soul', 'February Air', 'Ice', 'Second Go', 'Toes', and 'Up We Go'. She released her fourth studio album, Skin & Earth, in 2017 accompanied by a graphic novel of the same name.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/LIGHTS_IMG_6799_%2815999651243%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lights/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[St. Vincent]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/st.-vincent/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Anne Erin 'Annie' Clark, known professionally as St. Vincent, is an American singer-songwriter and record producer.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/47/St_Vincent_at_Roskilde_Festival_2015.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/st.-vincent/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ingrid Michaelson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ingrid-michaelson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ingrid Ellen Michaelson is an American singer-songwriter and actress. Her first album, Slow the Rain, was released in 2005, and she has since released eight more albums: Girls and Boys, Be OK, Everybody, Human Again, Lights Out, It Doesn't Have to Make Sense, Songs for the Season, and her most recent, Stranger Songs. Her two highest-charting singles are 'The Way I Am' (2007) and 'Girls Chase Boys' (2014), at No. 37 and No. 52 on the Billboard Hot 100, respectively.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d2/Ingrid_Michaelson%2C_2009_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ingrid-michaelson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>