<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Jonas Brothers</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Jonas Brothers</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:24:26 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Jonas]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-jonas/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Adam Jonas is an American singer, songwriter, and actor. He rose to fame as a member of the pop rock band the Jonas Brothers, alongside his brothers Kevin and Nick. The group released their debut studio album It's About Time through the Columbia label in 2006, which failed to achieve commercial success. After signing with Hollywood Records, the group released their self-titled second studio album in 2007, which became their breakthrough record. The band became prominent figures on the Disney Channel during this time, gaining a large following through the network: they appeared in the widely successful musical television film Camp Rock (2008) and its sequel Camp Rock 2: The Final Jam (2010) as well as two of their own series, Jonas Brothers: Living the Dream (2008–2010) and Jonas (2009–2010).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a8/Joe_Jonas_2012_%28Straighten_Crop%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-jonas/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nick Jonas]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nick-jonas/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nicholas Jerry Jonas is an American singer, songwriter and actor. Jonas began acting in theater at the age of seven, and released his debut single in 2002 which caught the attention of Columbia Records where Jonas formed a band with his older brothers, Joe and Kevin, known as the Jonas Brothers. The group released their debut studio album It's About Time through the Columbia label in 2006. After leaving Columbia Records and signing with Hollywood Records, the group released their self-titled second studio album in 2007, which became their breakthrough record. The band became prominent figures on the Disney Channel during this time, gaining a large following through the network and they appeared in the widely successful musical television film Camp Rock (2008) and its sequel Camp Rock 2: The Final Jam (2010) as well as two of their own series, Jonas Brothers: Living the Dream (2008–2010) and Jonas (2009–2010).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/Nick_Jonas_in_2017.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nick-jonas/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kevin Jonas]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kevin-jonas/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul Kevin Jonas II is an American musician, singer, songwriter, actor, contractor, dancer, and entrepreneur. He rose to fame as a member of the pop rock band, the Jonas Brothers, alongside his younger brothers Joe and Nick.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7e/Kevin_Jonas_2009.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kevin-jonas/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>