<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Fistful Of Mercy</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Fistful Of Mercy</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 22:06:16 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ben Harper]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ben-harper/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Benjamin Chase Harper is an American singer-songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. Harper plays an eclectic mix of blues, folk, soul, reggae, and rock music and is known for his guitar-playing skills, vocals, live performances, and activism. He has released twelve regular studio albums, mostly through Virgin Records and has toured internationally.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/42/Ben_Harper_FIJM_2003.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ben-harper/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dhani Harrison]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dhani-harrison/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dhani Harrison is a British musician, composer and singer-songwriter. He is the son of George and Olivia Arias Harrison. Dhani debuted as a professional musician assisting in recording his father's final album, Brainwashed, and completing it with the assistance of Jeff Lynne after his father's death in November 2001. Harrison formed his own band, thenewno2, in 2002 and has performed at festivals including Coachella where Spin magazine dubbed their performance as one of the 'best debut performances of the festival.' The band also played Lollapalooza three times with Harrison joining the festival's founder Perry Farrell on a cover of The Velvet Underground's 'Sweet Jane' at 2010's event. In 2017 Harrison released his debut solo album IN///PARALLEL. The 2019 film IN///PARALIVE, showcases the live version of his debut solo album and was recorded in the round at the legendary Henson Studios in Los Angeles. Harrison's latest single, 'Motorways ', was described by Rolling Stone as 'a psychedelic track with a robust beat'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7d/Dhani_Harrison.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dhani-harrison/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:38 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>