<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Garage Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Garage Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 19:07:34 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Dwyer]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-dwyer/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Dwyer is an American multi-instrumentalist, vocalist, songwriter, visual artist and record label owner. He is best known as the founding member and primary songwriter of the garage rock band Thee Oh Sees, with whom he has recorded 22 studio albums. In addition to his work with Thee Oh Sees, Dwyer records solo material under the name 'Damaged Bug', and is a former member of the garage rock acts, Coachwhips, Pink and Brown and The Hospitals.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/85/John_Dwyer_Musician_Oh_Sees.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-dwyer/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sergey Shnurov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sergey-shnurov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sergey Vladimirovich Shnurov is a Russian musician and songwriter, best known as Shnur, of the ska-punk band Leningrad which he formed in 1997 and was the frontman of till the end of 2008. In December 2008 the group disbanded, Shnur with some of its members forming Rubl.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6f/Sergei_Shnurov.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sergey-shnurov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dan Auerbach]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dan-auerbach/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Daniel Quine Auerbach is an American musician, singer-songwriter, and record producer, best known as the guitarist and vocalist of the Black Keys, a blues rock band from Akron, Ohio. As a member of the group, Auerbach has recorded and co-produced eleven studio albums with his bandmate Patrick Carney. Auerbach has also released two solo albums, Keep It Hid (2009) Waiting on a Song (2017), and formed a side project, the Arcs, which released the album Yours, Dreamily, in 2015.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/Dan_Auerbach_of_Black_Keys_at_Music_Midtown_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dan-auerbach/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Yegor Letov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yegor-letov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Igor Fedorovich 'Yegor' Letov was a Russian poet, musician, singer-songwriter, audio engineer and conceptual art painter, best known as the founder and leader of the post-punk/psychedelic rock band Grazhdanskaya Oborona. He was also the founder of the conceptual art avant-garde project Kommunizm and psychedelic rock outfit Egor i Opizdenevshie. Letov collaborated with singer-songwriter Yanka Dyagileva and other Siberian underground artists as a record engineer and producer.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2e/Egor_Letov_2000-11-04_Nuernberg.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yegor-letov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nicke Andersson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nicke-andersson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nicke Andersson, is a Swedish singer, guitarist, drummer, songwriter and composer most known for his work as the singer and guitarist of the successful Grammis award winning rock band The Hellacopters and drummer for Swedish death metal band Entombed. He has also done work as a producer as well as artwork for most the bands he has been involved with. Besides his work with the Hellacopters, Andersson is currently the drummer and songwriter in the soul band The Solution, the death metal band Death Breath, and the hard rock band Lucifer. Andersson has been involved in well over a hundred different official releases with different bands. He is currently touring with his new project, Imperial State Electric. Andersson was also the drummer of Tiamat in 1989, who were under the name of Treblinka, but he was no longer in the group by that year and he did not record any material with them.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b8/Nicke_Andersson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nicke-andersson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Patrick Carney]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/patrick-carney/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Patrick James Carney is an American musician and producer. Carney serves as the drummer for The Black Keys, a blues rock band from Akron, Ohio. He currently lives in Nashville, Tennessee.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/68/The_Black_Keys_at_MOG%2C_SXSW_2010.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/patrick-carney/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jay Reatard]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jay-reatard/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Lee Lindsey Jr., better known by the stage name Jay Reatard, was an American musician from Memphis, Tennessee. Lindsey was signed to Matador Records. He released recordings as a solo artist and as a member of the Reatards and Lost Sounds.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/09/Jayreatard.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jay-reatard/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sune Rose Wagner]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sune-rose-wagner/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sune Rose Wagner is a Danish songwriter, guitarist, and vocalist, playing in the rock group The Raveonettes.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/42/Sune_Rose_Wagner_by_David_Shankbone.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sune-rose-wagner/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dregen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dregen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dregen is a Swedish musician best known as the guitarist of The Hellacopters, as well as Backyard Babies. As of March 2014, Dregen has also served as the newest member of Michael Monroe's solo band, replacing Ginger as guitarist. He was formerly married to fellow Swedish singer Pernilla Andersson, who is also the mother of their first child, a son named Sixten. The couple officially announced their separation on 1 June 2015.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3d/Dregen%2C_Bokm%C3%A4ssan_2013_1_%28crop%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dregen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Hives - Hate to Say I Told You So]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/song/the-hives-hate-to-say-i-told-you-so/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hate to Say I Told You So is a cracking rock song by the Swedish band the Hives.</p><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Uz1Jwyxd4tE/mqdefault.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/song/the-hives-hate-to-say-i-told-you-so/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 21:56:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>