<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Dixie Chicks</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Dixie Chicks</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:06:55 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Emily Robison]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emily-robison/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Emily Burns Strayer is an American songwriter, singer, multi-instrumentalist, and a founding member of the country band the Dixie Chicks. Strayer plays banjo, dobro, guitar, lap steel, bass, mandolin, accordion, and sitar. Initially in her career with the Dixie Chicks, she limited her singing to harmony with backing vocals, but within her role in the Court Yard Hounds, she has taken on the role of lead vocalist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e9/Emily_Robison_with_dobro.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emily-robison/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Martie Maguire]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/martie-maguire/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Martha 'Martie' Elenor Maguire is an American musician who is a founding member of both the female alternative country band Dixie Chicks and country bluegrass duo Court Yard Hounds. She won awards in national fiddle championships while still a teenager. Erwin is accomplished on several other instruments, including the mandolin, viola, double bass and guitar. She has written and co-written a number of the band's songs, some of which have become chart-topping hits. She also contributes her skills in vocal harmony and backing vocals, as well as orchestrating string arrangements for the band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/24/Martie_Maguire_in_2010.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/martie-maguire/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>