<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Baroque Pop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Baroque Pop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 23:53:43 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Harry Nilsson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/harry-nilsson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Harry Edward Nilsson III, known mononymously as Nilsson, was an American singer-songwriter who achieved the peak of his commercial success in the early 1970s. His work is characterized by pioneering vocal overdub experiments, returns to the Great American Songbook, and fusions of Caribbean sounds. A tenor with a 3½ octave range, Nilsson was one of the few major pop-rock recording artists of his era to achieve significant commercial success without ever performing major public concerts or undertaking regular tours. The craft of his songs and the defiant attitude he projected remains a touchstone for later generations of indie rock musicians.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/71/Harry_Nilsson_%281972%29.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/harry-nilsson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Barry Gibb]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/barry-gibb/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir Barry Alan Crompton Gibb is a British-American singer, songwriter, musician and record producer who rose to worldwide fame as a co-founder of the group the Bee Gees, one of the most commercially successful groups in the history of popular music. With his younger brothers, twins Robin and Maurice Gibb, he formed a songwriting partnership beginning in 1955.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/17/Barry_Gibb_Hollywood_Bowl-0545_%2814365129281%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/barry-gibb/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nick Drake]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nick-drake/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nicholas Rodney 'Nick' Drake was an English singer-songwriter. Although his music did not find a wide audience during his lifetime, he gradually achieved wider recognition and is now considered among the most influential English singer-songwriters of the last 50 years. Drake signed to Island Records when he was 20 years old and released his debut album, Five Leaves Left, in 1969. By 1972, he had recorded two more albums: Bryter Layter and Pink Moon. Neither sold more than 5,000 copies on initial release.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/61/Nick_Drake_%281971%29.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nick-drake/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[St. Vincent]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/st.-vincent/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Anne Erin 'Annie' Clark, known professionally as St. Vincent, is an American singer-songwriter and record producer.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/47/St_Vincent_at_Roskilde_Festival_2015.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/st.-vincent/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lana-del-rey/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Elizabeth Woolridge Grant, known professionally as Lana Del Rey, is an American singer and songwriter. Her music has been noted by critics for its stylized cinematic quality; its preoccupation with themes of tragic romance, glamour, and melancholia; and its references to pop culture, particularly 1950s and 1960s Americana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f9/Lana_Del_Rey_at_KROQ_Weenie_Roast_2017_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lana-del-rey/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jónsi]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jónsi/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jón Þór 'Jónsi' Birgisson is an Icelandic musician; he is the vocalist and multi-instrumentalist for the Icelandic post-rock band Sigur Rós. He is known for his use of a cello bow on guitar and his falsetto or countertenor voice. He is blind in his right eye from birth as a result of a broken optic nerve from the brain. He is openly gay. Apart from Sigur Rós, Jónsi also performs together with his partner Alex Somers as an art collaboration called Jónsi & Alex. They released their self-titled first book in November 2006, which was an embossed hardcover limited to 1,000 copies. The two also released the album Riceboy Sleeps, in July 2009. 
On 1 December 2009, Jónsi's official website, jonsi.com, was launched in anticipation of his debut solo album, Go, which was released on 5 April 2010. After the release of the album, Jónsi promptly started a tour across North America and Europe, featuring songs from the album plus a few other selections, planning to tour from March to September.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6d/J%C3%B3n_%C3%9E%C3%B3r_Birgisson_at_the_Roskilde_Festival_in_2006.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jónsi/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>