<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Country Blues</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Country Blues</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 19:48:27 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mississippi John Hurt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mississippi-john-hurt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Smith Hurt, better known as Mississippi John Hurt, was an American country blues singer and guitarist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2e/M_John_Hurt.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mississippi-john-hurt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lightnin' Hopkins]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lightnin'-hopkins/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Samuel John 'Lightnin'' Hopkins was an American country blues singer, songwriter, guitarist and occasional pianist, from Centerville, Texas. Rolling Stone magazine ranked him number 71 on its list of the 100 greatest guitarists of all time.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bb/LightningHopkins.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lightnin'-hopkins/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Billy Ray Cyrus]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billy-ray-cyrus/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Billy Ray Cyrus is an American singer-songwriter and actor. He has released 16 studio albums and 53 singles since 1992, and is known for his number one single 'Achy Breaky Heart', which became the first single ever to achieve triple Platinum status in Australia. It was also the best-selling single in the same country in 1992. Due to the song's music video, the line dance rose in popularity.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4a/Billy_Ray_Cyrus_2009_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billy-ray-cyrus/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Odetta]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/odetta/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Odetta Holmes, known as Odetta, was an American singer, actress, guitarist, lyricist, and a civil and human rights activist, often referred to as 'The Voice of the Civil Rights Movement'. Her musical repertoire consisted largely of American folk music, blues, jazz, and spirituals. An important figure in the American folk music revival of the 1950s and 1960s, she influenced many of the key figures of the folk-revival of that time, including Bob Dylan, Joan Baez, Mavis Staples, and Janis Joplin. Time magazine included her recording of 'Take This Hammer' on its list of the 100 Greatest Popular Songs, stating that 'Rosa Parks was her No. 1 fan, and Martin Luther King Jr. called her the queen of American folk music.'</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bb/Odetta.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/odetta/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>