<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Industrial Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Industrial Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 20:55:42 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marilyn Manson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marilyn-manson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Hugh Warner, known professionally as Marilyn Manson, is an American singer, songwriter, record producer, actor, painter, and writer. He is known for his controversial stage personality and image as the lead singer of the band of the same name, which he co-founded with guitarist Daisy Berkowitz in 1989 and of which he remains the only constant member. Like the other founding members of the band, his stage name was formed by combining and juxtaposing the names of two opposing American cultural icons: a sex symbol and an infamous criminal; in Manson's case, actress Marilyn Monroe and cult leader Charles Manson.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Revolver_Golden_Gods_Awards.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marilyn-manson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jeordie White]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/twiggy-ramirez/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jeordie Osbourne White, once known professionally as Twiggy Ramirez, shortened to just Twiggy since 2008, and sometimes referred to by his real name, is an American musician, mostly known as the former bassist and guitarist of the band Marilyn Manson. Previously, he was the bassist for A Perfect Circle and a touring member of Nine Inch Nails, and is currently the vocalist for Goon Moon. He left Marilyn Manson in 2002, later rejoined the band in 2008, and was dismissed in 2017. He has been a principal songwriter for the band and has also contributed to some of the Desert Sessions recordings. He also hosts the Hour of Goon podcast with fellow musician Fred Sablan, on the Feral Audio network.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/Jeordie_White.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/twiggy-ramirez/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Trent Reznor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Trent Reznor is an American musician, singer, songwriter, record producer, and composer. He serves as the lead vocalist, multi-instrumentalist, and principal songwriter of the industrial rock band Nine Inch Nails, which he founded in 1988 and of which he was the sole official member until 2016. The first Nine Inch Nails album, Pretty Hate Machine (1989), was a commercial and critical success. Reznor has since released 11 more Nine Inch Nails studio albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c9/Trent_Reznor-FEB2008_%28cropped%2C_but_higher_quality%29_%282%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:37 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Vincent]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-vincent/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Justin Vincent, also known as Evil D, is an American musician who is best known as the former lead vocalist and bassist for the death metal band Morbid Angel as well as the bassist for Genitorturers. His early influences are Kiss and Alice Cooper. Vincent typically plays bass with a pick, though he occasionally uses his fingers.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/93/David_Vincent.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-vincent/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:37 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>