<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Industrial Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Industrial Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 01:44:48 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Trent Reznor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Trent Reznor is an American singer, songwriter, musician, record producer, and film score composer. He is the founder, lead vocalist, and principal songwriter of the industrial rock band Nine Inch Nails, which he founded in 1988 and of which he was the sole official member until adding long-time collaborator Atticus Ross as a permanent member in 2016. His first release under the Nine Inch Nails name, the 1989 album Pretty Hate Machine, was a commercial and critical success. He has since released nine Nine Inch Nails studio albums. He left Interscope Records in 2007 and was an independent recording artist until signing with Columbia Records in 2012.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d5/Trent_Reznor-FEB2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marilyn Manson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marilyn-manson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Hugh Warner, known professionally as Marilyn Manson, is an American singer, songwriter, record producer, actor, visual artist and music video director. He is known for his controversial stage personality and image as the lead singer of the band Marilyn Manson, which he co-founded with guitarist Daisy Berkowitz and of which he remains the only constant member. Like the other founding members of the band, his stage name was formed by combining and juxtaposing the names of two American pop cultural icons of the 1960s: actress Marilyn Monroe and criminal Charles Manson.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Revolver_Golden_Gods_Awards.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marilyn-manson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>