<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Grunge</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Grunge</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:52:56 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Scott Weiland]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-weiland/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Scott Richard Weiland was an American musician, singer and songwriter. During a career spanning three decades, Weiland was best known as the lead singer of the band Stone Temple Pilots from 1989 to 2002 and 2008 to 2013, making six records with them. He was also lead vocalist of supergroup Velvet Revolver from 2003 to 2008, recording two albums, and he recorded one album with another supergroup, Art of Anarchy. He also established himself as a solo artist, releasing three studio albums, two cover albums, and collaborations with several other musicians throughout his career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/Scott_Weiland_3.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-weiland/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Neil Young]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Neil Percival Young is a Canadian singer-songwriter. After embarking on a music career in the 1960s, he moved to Los Angeles, where he formed Buffalo Springfield with Stephen Stills, Richie Furay and others. Young had released two solo albums and three as a member of Buffalo Springfield by the time he joined Crosby, Stills & Nash in 1969. From his early solo albums and those with his backing band Crazy Horse, Young has recorded a steady stream of studio and live albums, sometimes warring with his recording company along the way.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bb/Neil_Young_-_Per_Ole_Hagen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nirvana - Smells Like Teen Spirit]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/song/nirvana-smells-like-teen-spirit/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Smells Like Teen Spirit is the opening track and lead single from Nirvana's second album, Nevermind released in 1991 on DGC Records.</p><img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/hTWKbfoikeg/mqdefault.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/song/nirvana-smells-like-teen-spirit/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 23:10:06 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>