<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Grunge</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Grunge</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:06:55 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Courtney Love]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/courtney-love/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Courtney Michelle Love is an American singer, songwriter and actress. A figure in the punk and grunge scenes of the 1990s, Love's career has spanned four decades. She rose to prominence as the lead vocalist of the alternative rock band Hole, which she formed in 1989. Love has drawn public attention for her uninhibited live performances and confrontational lyrics, as well as her highly publicized personal life following her marriage to Nirvana frontman Kurt Cobain.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fd/Life_Ball_2014_Courtney_Love_Crop.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/courtney-love/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dean DeLeo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dean-deleo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dean DeLeo is an American guitarist and songwriter known for his work with rock band Stone Temple Pilots. DeLeo is also known for his role in the short-lived bands Talk Show and Army of Anyone. He is the older brother of Robert DeLeo, who plays bass for Stone Temple Pilots.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/03/Dean_deleo_guitar_ottawa_2009_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dean-deleo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Krist Novoselic]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/krist-novoselic/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Krist Anthony Novoselic (; is an American musician and political activist, best known as the bassist and a founding member of the grunge band Nirvana. Nirvana achieved massive success, earning multiple gold and platinum awards and touring around the world at sold-out shows.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7d/Krist_Novoselic_15A.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/krist-novoselic/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kurt Cobain]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kurt-cobain/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kurt Donald Cobain was an American singer, songwriter, and musician, best known as the guitarist and frontman of the rock band Nirvana. He is remembered as one of the most iconic and influential rock musicians in the history of alternative music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/19/Nirvana_around_1992.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kurt-cobain/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Scott Weiland]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-weiland/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Scott Richard Weiland was an American musician, singer and songwriter. During a career spanning three decades, Weiland was best known as the lead singer of the band Stone Temple Pilots from 1989 to 2002 and 2008 to 2013, making six records with them. He was also lead vocalist of supergroup Velvet Revolver from 2003 to 2008, recording two albums, and he recorded one album with another supergroup, Art of Anarchy. He also established himself as a solo artist, releasing three studio albums, two cover albums, and collaborations with several other musicians throughout his career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/Scott_Weiland_3.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-weiland/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Neil Young]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Neil Percival Young is a Canadian singer-songwriter. After embarking on a music career in the 1960s, he moved to Los Angeles, where he formed Buffalo Springfield with Stephen Stills, Richie Furay and others. Young had released two solo albums and three as a member of Buffalo Springfield by the time he joined Crosby, Stills & Nash in 1969. From his early solo albums and those with his backing band Crazy Horse, Young has recorded a steady stream of studio and live albums, sometimes warring with his recording company along the way.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bb/Neil_Young_-_Per_Ole_Hagen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Taylor Momsen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/taylor-momsen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Taylor Michel Momsen is an American singer, songwriter, model, and former actress. She is known for portraying the character of Jenny Humphrey on The CW's teen drama series Gossip Girl (2007–2012) and Cindy Lou Who in the film How the Grinch Stole Christmas (2000).
After her retirement from acting, she became widely known for being the frontwoman of the American rock band The Pretty Reckless.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/01/The_Pretty_Reckless_Rockfest_2017_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/taylor-momsen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jack Endino]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-endino/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack Endino is an American producer and musician based in Seattle, United States. Long associated with Seattle label Sub Pop and the grunge movement, Endino worked on seminal albums from bands including Mudhoney, Soundgarden, and Nirvana. Endino was also the guitarist for the Seattle band Skin Yard which was active between 1985 and 1992. Endino currently manages a studio in Seattle called Soundhouse Recording.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/Jack_Endino_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-endino/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Wes Scantlin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wes-scantlin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Wesley Reid Scantlin is an American singer, songwriter, musician, and the only remaining founding member of the American post-grunge band Puddle of Mudd.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/86/Wes_Scantlin_Puddle_of_Mudd_2009.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wes-scantlin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>