<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Grunge</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Grunge</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 23:18:55 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Wes Scantlin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wes-scantlin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Wesley Reid Scantlin is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. He is best known as the lead vocalist, guitarist, and only constant member of rock band Puddle of Mudd. He was named one of the 'Top 100 Heavy Metal Vocalists' by Hit Parader.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/41/Wes_Scantlin_Puddle_of_Mudd_2009_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wes-scantlin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Krist Novoselic]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/krist-novoselic/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Krist Anthony Novoselic is an American musician and activist best known as the bassist and a founding member of the rock band Nirvana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7d/Krist_Novoselic_15A.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/krist-novoselic/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dean DeLeo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dean-deleo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dean DeLeo is an American guitarist and songwriter known for his work with rock band Stone Temple Pilots. DeLeo is also known for his role in the short-lived bands Talk Show and Army of Anyone. He is the older brother of Robert DeLeo, who plays bass for Stone Temple Pilots.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/03/Dean_deleo_guitar_ottawa_2009_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dean-deleo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kurt Cobain]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kurt-cobain/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kurt Donald Cobain was an American singer, songwriter and musician, best known as the guitarist, primary songwriter and frontman of the rock band Nirvana. Through his angst-fueled songwriting and anti-establishment persona, Cobain's compositions widened the thematic conventions of mainstream rock music. He was often heralded as a spokesman of Generation X and is considered to be one of the most influential musicians in the history of alternative rock.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/57/Kurt_Cobain_1991_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kurt-cobain/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Neil Young]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Neil Percival Young is a Canadian-American singer-songwriter, musician, and activist. After embarking on a music career in Winnipeg in the 1960s, Young moved to Los Angeles, joining Buffalo Springfield with Stephen Stills, Richie Furay and others. Since the beginning of his solo career with his backing band Crazy Horse, Young has released many critically acclaimed and important albums, such as After the Gold Rush, Everybody Knows This Is Nowhere, and Harvest.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bb/Neil_Young_-_Per_Ole_Hagen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American singer, songwriter, and musician best known as the lead vocalist and rhythm guitarist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. He also had a solo career and contributed to soundtracks. Cornell was also the founder and frontman of Temple of the Dog, a one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/58/ChrisCornellTIFFSept2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Courtney Love]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/courtney-love/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Courtney Michelle Love is an American singer, songwriter and actress. A figure in the alternative and grunge scenes of the 1990s, her career has spanned four decades. She rose to prominence as the lead vocalist of the alternative rock band Hole, which she formed in 1989. Love has drawn public attention for her uninhibited live performances and confrontational lyrics, as well as her highly publicized personal life following her marriage to Nirvana frontman Kurt Cobain. In 2020, NME named her 'one of the most influential singers in alternative culture of the last 30 years.'</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fd/Life_Ball_2014_Courtney_Love_Crop.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/courtney-love/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jack Endino]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-endino/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack Endino is an American producer and musician based in Seattle, Washington. Long associated with Seattle label Sub Pop and the grunge movement, Endino worked on seminal albums from bands including Mudhoney, Soundgarden and Nirvana. He was also the guitarist for Seattle band Skin Yard, which was active between 1985 and 1992. Endino currently manages a studio in Seattle called Soundhouse Recording.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/Jack_Endino_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-endino/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mark Lanegan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-lanegan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Mark William Lanegan is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. He released more than 10 studio albums and was the lead singer for Screaming Trees. He was also a member of Queens of the Stone Age.
Lanegan is known for his baritone voice, which has been described as being 'as scratchy as a three-day beard yet as supple and pliable as moccasin leather' and has been compared to Leonard Cohen and Tom Waits.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fb/Mark_Lanegan.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-lanegan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:38 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tom Dumont]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-dumont/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Martin Dumont is an American guitarist and producer. Dumont is a member of third wave ska band No Doubt, and during the band's hiatus, he began Invincible Overlord as a side project and produced Matt Costa's Songs We Sing.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9c/TomDumont.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-dumont/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:37 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>