<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Post Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Post Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:04:33 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tim Gane]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tim-gane/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Timothy John Gane is an English songwriter and guitarist who co-founded Stereolab with his former partner Lætitia Sadier.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/70/Stereolab_%281994%29_Tim_Gane_%281994%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tim-gane/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anneke van Giersbergen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anneke-van-giersbergen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Anna Maria van Giersbergen, known artistically as Anneke van Giersbergen, is a Dutch singer, songwriter, guitarist and pianist who became known worldwide as the lead singer and songwriter for the Dutch band The Gathering, between 1994 and 2007. 
She also has a solo career. The project was originally called Agua de Annique, but now goes by her own name.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/30/Gathering_anneke.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anneke-van-giersbergen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stuart Braithwaite]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stuart-braithwaite/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stuart Leslie Braithwaite is a Scottish multi-instrumentalist, singer and songwriter. He is the guitarist of post rock band Mogwai, with whom he has recorded nine studio albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/00/Stuart_braithwaite.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stuart-braithwaite/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lights]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lights/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lights Poxleitner-Bokan, known mononymously as Lights, is a Canadian musician, singer, songwriter, author, and illustrator. She is known for her gold-certified albums The Listening and Siberia as well as singles 'Drive My Soul', 'February Air', 'Ice', 'Second Go', 'Toes', and 'Up We Go'. She released her fourth studio album, Skin & Earth, in 2017 accompanied by a graphic novel of the same name.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/LIGHTS_IMG_6799_%2815999651243%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lights/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Lydon]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-lydon/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Joseph Lydon, also known by his stage name Johnny Rotten, is an English singer, songwriter and musician. He is best known as the lead singer of the late-1970s British punk band the Sex Pistols, which lasted from 1975 until 1978, and again for various revivals during the 1990s and 2000s. He is also the lead singer of post-punk band Public Image Ltd (PiL), which he founded and fronted from 1978 until 1993, and again since 2009. Since 2013, Lydon has held British, Irish and American citizenship.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6d/John_Lydon%2C_Primavera_Sound_Festival_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-lydon/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jónsi]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jónsi/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jón Þór 'Jónsi' Birgisson is an Icelandic musician; he is the vocalist and multi-instrumentalist for the Icelandic post-rock band Sigur Rós. He is known for his use of a cello bow on guitar and his falsetto or countertenor voice. He is blind in his right eye from birth as a result of a broken optic nerve from the brain. He is openly gay. Apart from Sigur Rós, Jónsi also performs together with his partner Alex Somers as an art collaboration called Jónsi & Alex. They released their self-titled first book in November 2006, which was an embossed hardcover limited to 1,000 copies. The two also released the album Riceboy Sleeps, in July 2009. 
On 1 December 2009, Jónsi's official website, jonsi.com, was launched in anticipation of his debut solo album, Go, which was released on 5 April 2010. After the release of the album, Jónsi promptly started a tour across North America and Europe, featuring songs from the album plus a few other selections, planning to tour from March to September.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6d/J%C3%B3n_%C3%9E%C3%B3r_Birgisson_at_the_Roskilde_Festival_in_2006.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jónsi/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kaki King]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kaki-king/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kaki King is an American guitarist and composer. King is known for her percussive and jazz-tinged melodies, energetic live shows, use of multiple tunings on acoustic and lap steel guitar, and her diverse range in different genres.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9b/WebsterHall2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kaki-king/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Buckethead]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Patrick Carroll, known professionally as Buckethead, is an American multi-instrumental musician who has received critical acclaim for his innovative electric guitar playing. His music spans many genres, including progressive metal, funk, blues, bluegrass, ambient, and avant-garde music. He performs primarily as a solo artist, though he has collaborated extensively with a wide variety of high-profile artists such as Bill Laswell, Bootsy Collins, Bernie Worrell, Iggy Pop, Les Claypool, Serj Tankian, Bill Moseley, Mike Patton, Viggo Mortensen, That 1 Guy, Bassnectar, and was a member of Guns N' Roses from 2000 to 2004. He has released 306 studio albums, four special releases, and one EP. He has also performed on more than 50 other albums by other artists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Neumos_seattle_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Efrim Menuck]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/efrim-menuck/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Efrim Manuel Menuck is a Canadian musician involved with a number of Montreal-based bands, most notably Godspeed You! Black Emperor and Thee Silver Mt. Zion Memorial Orchestra. Menuck is also a frequent record producer and engineer, working with musicians from Montreal and abroad.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/ba/Godspeed_You_Black_Emperor%21_-_London_Nov_20001.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/efrim-menuck/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>