<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Alternative Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Alternative Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:46:53 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Ford]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-ford/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David James Ford is an English singer-songwriter, guitarist and songwriter. He first achieved prominence with the indie rock group Easyworld, who released an independent mini-album, ...Better Ways to Self Destruct and two full-length albums on Jive Records before disbanding in 2004.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/67/David_Ford%2C_Toronto.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-ford/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Power]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-power/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Timothy Power is an English singer, songwriter and rhythm guitarist, best known as the frontman of Cast. He was previously the bassist and backing vocalist for the La's from 1986 to 1991. Following the dissolution of Cast in 2001, Power embarked on a solo career. In 2005, he briefly reunited with the La's, who split up again without releasing new material. Cast reformed in 2010, releasing the album Troubled Times in March 2012, followed by Kicking Up the Dust in April 2017. Power was born in Allerton, Liverpool.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/07/John_Timothy_Power.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-power/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ben Moody]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ben-moody/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Benjamin Robert 'Ben' Moody is an American musician, singer, songwriter, record producer, and actor. He is best known as co-founder, lead guitarist, and co-songwriter of rock band Evanescence from its inception in 1995 to his departure in October 2003. Since leaving Evanescence, Moody has collaborated with an array of performers vocally, instrumentally, and as a writer. He is currently a member of The Halo Method and We Are the Fallen.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Evanescence_2003_barcelona_ben_moody.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ben-moody/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Langhorne Slim]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/langhorne-slim/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Langhorne Slim is an American singer-songwriter,. He attended high school at Solebury School in New Hope, Pennsylvania, and graduated from the Conservatory of Music at Purchase College, part of the SUNY system.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d7/Langhorne_Slim%2C_Brooklyn.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/langhorne-slim/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Doughty]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-doughty/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Ross Doughty is an American singer-songwriter and author. He founded the band Soul Coughing in 1992, and as of The Heart Watches While the Brain Burns (2016), has released 18 studio albums, live albums, and EPs, all since 2000.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/68/Mike_Doughty_6.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-doughty/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jeff Ament]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeff-ament/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jeffrey Allen Ament is an American musician and songwriter who serves as the bassist for the American rock band Pearl Jam. He is considered to be one of the greatest rock bassists of all time.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b5/Jeff_Ament.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeff-ament/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gary Lightbody]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gary-lightbody/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gareth John Lightbody is a singer, songwriter, guitarist and multi-instrumentalist from Northern Ireland, best known as the lead singer and rhythm guitarist of the alternative rock band Snow Patrol. He has also founded the musical supergroups the Reindeer Section and Tired Pony.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/99/Gary_Lightbody_Copenhagen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gary-lightbody/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alanis Morissette]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alanis Nadine Morissette is a Canadian-American singer, songwriter, record producer, and actress. Known for her emotive mezzo-soprano voice, Morissette began her career in Canada in the early 1990s with two mildly successful dance-pop albums. Afterwards, as part of a recording deal, she moved to Holmby Hills, Los Angeles and in 1995 released Jagged Little Pill, a more rock-oriented album which sold more than 33 million copies globally and is her most critically acclaimed work. Her follow-up album, Supposed Former Infatuation Junkie, was released in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Alanis_Morissette_5-19-2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jeremy Enigk]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeremy-enigk/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jeremy Enigk is an American singer-songwriter, vocalist and guitarist / multi-instrumentalist. He is known as a solo artist, a film score composer, and as the lead vocalist, rhythm guitarist and keyboardist of the Seattle-based bands Sunny Day Real Estate and The Fire Theft.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e8/Jeremy_Enigk.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeremy-enigk/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[PJ Harvey]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pj-harvey/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Polly Jean Harvey is an English musician and singer-songwriter. Primarily known as a vocalist and guitarist, she is also proficient with a wide range of instruments.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/49/PJ_Harvey_in_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pj-harvey/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>