<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » E Street Band</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » E Street Band</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:12:56 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nils Lofgren]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nils-lofgren/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nils Hilmer Lofgren is an American rock musician, recording artist, songwriter, and multi-instrumentalist. Along with his work as a solo artist, he has been a member of Bruce Springsteen's E Street Band since 1984, a member of Crazy Horse, and founder/frontman of the band Grin. Lofgren was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the E Street Band in 2014.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/36/Nils_Lofgren_Olbrich.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nils-lofgren/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Patti Scialfa]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/patti-scialfa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vivienne Patricia Scialfa is an American singer-songwriter and guitarist. Scialfa has been a member of the E Street Band since 1984 and has been married to Bruce Springsteen since 1991. In 2014, Scialfa was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the E Street Band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f5/Patti_Scialfa_11022008.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/patti-scialfa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steven Van Zandt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steven-van-zandt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steven Van Zandt, also known as Little Steven or Miami Steve, is an American singer, songwriter, musician, producer, actor, and activist. He is best known as a member of Bruce Springsteen's E Street Band, in which he plays guitar and mandolin. He is also known for his roles on television drama series, such as Silvio Dante on The Sopranos (1999–2007) and Frank Tagliano on Lilyhammer (2012–2014). Van Zandt has his own solo band called Little Steven and The Disciples of Soul, active on and off since the 1980s. In 2014, he was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the E Street Band. Van Zandt has produced music, written songs, or had his own songs covered by Bruce Springsteen, Southside Johnny and the Asbury Jukes, Jackson Browne, Gary U.S. Bonds, Darlene Love, Ronnie Spector, Jimmy Barnes, Meat Loaf, Pearl Jam, and more.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fc/Smwknd-steven-van-zandt-3814.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steven-van-zandt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruce Springsteen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bruce-springsteen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bruce Frederick Joseph Springsteen is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. He has released twenty studio albums, many of which feature his backing band, the E Street Band. Originally from the Jersey Shore, he is one of the originators of the heartland rock style of music, combining mainstream rock musical style with narrative songs about working class American life. During a career that has spanned five decades, Springsteen has become known for his poetic, socially conscious lyrics and energetic stage performances, sometimes lasting up to four hours in length. He has been nicknamed 'The Boss'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d7/Bruce_Springsteen_Oslo_2019_193031.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bruce-springsteen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:38 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>