<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Post Bop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Post Bop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 22:24:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Charlie Hunter]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/charlie-hunter/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Charlie Hunter is an American guitarist, composer, and bandleader. First coming to prominence in the early 1990s, Hunter plays custom-made seven- and eight-string guitars on which he simultaneously plays bass lines, chords, and melodies. Critic Sean Westergaard described Hunter's technique as 'mind-boggling...he's an agile improviser with an ear for great tone, and always has excellent players alongside him in order to make great music, not to show off.' Hunter's technique is rooted in the styles of jazz guitarists Joe Pass and Tuck Andress, two of his biggest influences, who blended bass notes with melody in a way that created the illusion of two guitars.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/35/Charliehunter.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/charlie-hunter/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Biréli Lagrène]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/biréli-lagrène/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Biréli Lagrène is a French jazz guitarist who came to prominence in the 1980s for his Django Reinhardt–influenced style. He often performs in swing, jazz fusion, and post-bop styles.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/78/Bireli_aux_Granges_le_26.08.06.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/biréli-lagrène/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Lee Roth]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-lee-roth/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Lee Roth is an American rock musician, singer, songwriter, and former radio personality. He is best known for his wild, energetic stage persona, and as the lead singer of hard rock band Van Halen across three stints, from 1974 to 1985, in 1996, and again from 2006 to their disbandment in 2020. He was also known as a successful solo artist, releasing numerous RIAA-certified Gold and Platinum albums. After more than two decades apart, Roth re-joined Van Halen in 2006 for a North American tour that became the highest-grossing in the band's history and one of the highest-grossing of that year. In 2012, Roth and Van Halen released the comeback album A Different Kind of Truth. In 2007, he was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of Van Halen.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/07/David_Lee_Roth_2007-11-10_%281%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-lee-roth/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Larry Carlton]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/larry-carlton/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Larry Eugene Carlton is an American guitarist who built his career as a studio musician in the 1970s and '80s for acts such as Steely Dan and Joni Mitchell. He has participated in thousands of recording sessions, recorded on hundreds of albums in many genres, for television and movies, and on more than 100 gold records. He has been a member of the jazz fusion group the Crusaders, the smooth jazz band Fourplay, and has maintained a long solo career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b7/Larry_Carlton_Gibson_ES-335.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/larry-carlton/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nathan East]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nathan-east/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nathan Harrell East is an American jazz, R&B, and rock bass player and vocalist. With more than 2,000 recordings, East is considered one of the most recorded bass players in the history of music. East holds a Bachelor of Arts degree in Music from the University of California, San Diego (1978). He is a founding member of contemporary jazz quartet Fourplay and has recorded, performed, and co-written songs with performers such as Bobby Womack, Eric Clapton, Michael Jackson, Joe Satriani, Peter Gabriel, George Harrison, Ringo Starr, Phil Collins, Stevie Wonder, Toto, Kenny Loggins, Daft Punk, Chick Corea, and Herbie Hancock.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/NathanEast2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nathan-east/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bill Frisell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-frisell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Richard Frisell is an American guitarist, composer and arranger. Frisell came to prominence as a jazz guitarist at ECM Records in the 1980s, and went on to work in a variety of contexts, notably as a member of the New York City Downtown Scene where he formed a long partnership with John Zorn. He was also a longtime member of Paul Motian's groups from the early 1980s until Motian's death in 2011. Since 2000, Frisell's output as a bandleader has included folk, country music, and Americana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/46/Bill_wiki.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-frisell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Frank Gambale]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/frank-gambale/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Frank Gambale is an Australian jazz fusion guitarist. He has released twenty albums over a period of three decades, and is known for his use of the sweep picking and economy picking techniques.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e5/Frank_Gambale_in_Montr%C3%A9al.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/frank-gambale/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:37 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>