<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Post Bop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Post Bop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 11:07:50 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Larry Carlton]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/larry-carlton/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Larry Eugene Carlton is an American guitarist who built his career as a studio musician in the 1970s and '80s for acts such as Steely Dan and Joni Mitchell. He has participated in thousands of recording sessions, recorded on hundreds of albums in many genres, for television and movies, and on more than 100 gold records. He has been a member of the jazz fusion group the Crusaders, the smooth jazz band Fourplay, and has maintained a long solo career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b7/Larry_Carlton_Gibson_ES-335.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/larry-carlton/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bill Frisell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-frisell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Richard Frisell is an American guitarist, composer and arranger. One of the leading guitarists in jazz since the late 1980s, Frisell came to prominence as a stalwart for ECM Records. He went on to work in a variety of contexts, notably as a member of the New York City Downtown Scene where he formed a long partnership with John Zorn. He was also a longtime member of Paul Motian's groups from the early 1980s until Motian's death in 2011. Since 2000, Frisell's eclectic output as a bandleader has emphasized folk, country music, and Americana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/46/Bill_wiki.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-frisell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Frank Gambale]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/frank-gambale/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Frank Gambale is an Australian jazz fusion guitarist. He has released twenty albums over a period of three decades, and is known for his use of the sweep picking and economy picking techniques.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e5/Frank_Gambale_in_Montr%C3%A9al.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/frank-gambale/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>