<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Mandolin</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Mandolin</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 23:20:45 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[T-Bone Walker]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/t-bone-walker/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Aaron Thibeaux 'T-Bone' Walker was an American blues guitarist, singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist, who was a pioneer and innovator of the jump blues and electric blues sound. In 2018 Rolling Stone magazine ranked him number 37 on its list of 'The 100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ee/T-Bone_Walker_1972.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/t-bone-walker/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Brown]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-brown-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Roger 'Joe' Brown, MBE is an English entertainer. He has worked as a rock and roll singer and guitarist for more than six decades. He was a stage and television performer in the late 1950s and has been a UK recording star since the early 1960s. He has made six films, presented specialist radio series for BBC Radio 2, appeared on the West End stage alongside Dame Anna Neagle and has written an autobiography. In recent years he has again concentrated on recording and performing music, playing two tours of around 100 shows every year and releasing an album almost every year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2d/Joe_Brown_On_Stage.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-brown-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Fred Tackett]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fred-tackett/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Fred Tackett an American native of Arkansas, is an accomplished songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. Originally a session player on guitar, mandolin, and trumpet, he is best known as a member of the band Little Feat.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Fred_Tackett_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fred-tackett/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Davey Johnstone]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/davey-johnstone/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David William Logan 'Davey' Johnstone is a Scottish rock guitarist and vocalist, best known for his work with Elton John.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b3/Davey_Johnstone_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/davey-johnstone/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Paul Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-paul-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Baldwin, better known by his stage name John Paul Jones, is an English musician and record producer who was the bassist and keyboardist in the rock band Led Zeppelin. Prior to forming the band with Jimmy Page in 1968, he was a session musician and arranger. After the death of drummer John Bonham in 1980, Led Zeppelin disbanded, and Jones developed a solo career. He has collaborated with musicians across a variety of genres, including Josh Homme and Dave Grohl with the supergroup Them Crooked Vultures.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/78/John_Paul_Jones_-_2010.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-paul-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Rory Gallagher]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rory-gallagher/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Rory Gallagher was an Irish blues and rock multi-instrumentalist, songwriter, and producer. Born in Ballyshannon, County Donegal, and brought up in Cork, Gallagher recorded solo albums throughout the 1970s and 1980s, after forming the band Taste during the late 1960s. His albums have sold over 30 million copies worldwide.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2a/Rory_Gallagher_1982.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rory-gallagher/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ellie Goulding]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ellie-goulding/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Elena Jane Goulding is an English singer and songwriter. Her career began when she met record producers Starsmith and Frankmusik, and she was later spotted by Jamie Lillywhite, who later became her manager and A&R. After signing to Polydor Records in July 2009, Goulding released her debut extended play, An Introduction to Ellie Goulding later that year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/71/Ellie_Goulding_-_Global_Citizen_Festival_Hamburg_09.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ellie-goulding/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jimmy Page]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jimmy-page/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Patrick Page is an English musician, songwriter, and record producer who achieved international success as the guitarist and founder of the rock band Led Zeppelin.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9f/Jimmy_Page_at_the_Echo_music_award_2013.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jimmy-page/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Boli Joe Armstrong]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billie-joe-armstrong/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Billie Joe Armstrong is an American singer, songwriter, musician, record producer, and actor. Armstrong serves as the lead vocalist, primary songwriter, and lead guitarist of the punk rock band Green Day, co-founded with Mike Dirnt. He is also a guitarist and vocalist for the punk rock band Pinhead Gunpowder, and provides lead vocals for Green Day's side projects Foxboro Hot Tubs, The Network, and The Longshot.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/19/Billie_Joe_Armstrong_at_mic_in_Cardiff.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billie-joe-armstrong/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>