<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » One Direction</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » One Direction</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 01:03:45 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Niall Horan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/niall-horan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Niall James Horan is an Irish singer and songwriter. He rose to prominence as a member of the band One Direction. In 2010, Horan auditioned as a solo contestant for British singing competition The X Factor. After being eliminated as solo performers, Niall, Liam Payne, Louis Tomlinson, Zayn Malik, and Harry Styles were put together in a band. They went on to finish third in the competition beaten by season winner Matt Cardle. As a group, they have released five albums, embarked on four world tours, and won several awards.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e3/Niall_Horan_Portrait.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/niall-horan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Harry Styles]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/harry-styles/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Harry Edward Styles is an English singer, songwriter, and actor. His musical career began in 2010 when he auditioned for the British singing competition The X Factor. He was eliminated early on, but was brought back to form the boy band One Direction. The band finished in third place and signed with Syco. They earned four number-one studio albums on the Billboard 200, and earned four top-five singles on the Billboard Hot 100. They embarked on four world tours and won a number of accolades. The band went on an indefinite hiatus in 2016.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9e/Harry_Styles_November_2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/harry-styles/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>