<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Melodic Death Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Melodic Death Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 19:59:35 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Björn Gelotte]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/björn-gelotte/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Björn Gelotte is a songwriter and lead guitarist for the Swedish band In Flames. He joined the band as the drummer in 1995, and continued his position as drummer during The Jester Race (1996) and Whoracle (1997). Gelotte switched to his current position on lead guitar after Glenn Ljungström left the band, sharing lead/rhythm guitar work with now former In Flames guitarist Jesper Strömblad.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9c/2015_RiP_In_Flames_-_Bjoern_Gelotte_by_2eight_-_DSC5844.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/björn-gelotte/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anders Björler]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anders-björler/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Anders Björler is a musician and a songwriter from Sweden. He is best known as the former guitar player in The Haunted, At The Gates. Anders also has a twin brother; Jonas Björler, whom he has played with in both At The Gates and The Haunted.
Anders also released an instrumental solo album in November 2013 entitled 'Antikythera', which was inspired by progressive rock, post-rock, jazz and Italian film soundtracks.
In addition to his music career, Anders also directed, edited and produced music videos, documentaries and in-the-studio features for bands like At The Gates, The Haunted, In Flames, Dark Tranquillity & Meshuggah.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/01/Anders_Bj%C3%B6rler%2C_Stockholm_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anders-björler/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Petri Lindroos]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/petri-lindroos/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Petri Lindroos is a melodic death/folk metal guitarist and vocalist. He is currently the lead vocalist in Ensiferum and, prior to this, was a founder and lead vocalist for Norther.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/77/Petri_Lindroos.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/petri-lindroos/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Amott]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-amott/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Amott is a Swedish guitarist, songwriter, founding member of the bands Arch Enemy, Spiritual Beggars, and Carnage, as well as a former member of the extreme metal band Carcass. He is the older brother of Christopher Amott. Some major influences in his music have been Tony Iommi, Michael Schenker, Uli Jon Roth and Dave Mustaine.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/87/Arch_Enemy_%28M._Amott%29_02.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-amott/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Niclas Engelin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/niclas-engelin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Niclas Engelin is a Swedish heavy metal guitarist for In Flames, Drömriket, Passenger & Engel. Engelin was the lead guitarist for Gardenian, and has been in and out of In Flames on five different occasions.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/53/01_N_Engelin_JHB.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/niclas-engelin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Fredrik Åkesson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fredrik-åkesson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Karl Fredrik Henrik Åkesson is a Swedish heavy metal guitarist. He is a current member of Opeth. He is also active in Krux, Monsters of Metal and Talisman.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Opeth_~_Avalon%2C_Hollywood.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fredrik-åkesson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Logan Mader]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/logan-mader/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Logan Conrad Mader is a Canadian-American record producer and current guitarist in melodic death metal band Once Human, as well as former lead guitarist in groove metal band Machine Head, which was formed in Oakland, California in 1991.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/34/Logan_Mader.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/logan-mader/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alexi Laiho]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alexi-laiho/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alexi 'Wildchild' Laiho is a Finnish guitarist, composer, and vocalist. He is best known as the lead guitarist, lead vocalist and founding member of the melodic death metal band Children of Bodom, and is also the guitarist for Sinergy, The Local Band and Kylähullut. He has previously played with Thy Serpent and Impaled Nazarene on occasion, as well as Warmen and Hypocrisy.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d0/Alexi_Laiho_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alexi-laiho/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jari Mäenpää]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jari-mäenpää/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jari Mäenpää is a Finnish heavy metal multi-instrumentalist and songwriter. He is the founder of Wintersun for which he records all instruments. Before forming Wintersun, Mäenpää was best known for his role in the folk metal band Ensiferum, which he joined in 1996 after leaving his prior band named Immemorial. Wintersun was initially planned as a parallel project alongside Ensiferum, but in January, 2004 he was forced to leave Ensiferum due to clashes between their touring schedule and the studio recording time he had booked for Wintersun.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5a/Jari_M%C3%A4enp%C3%A4%C3%A4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jari-mäenpää/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Peter Tägtgren]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-tägtgren/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alf Peter Tägtgren is a Swedish musician, multi-instrumentalist and producer. He is the founder, main songwriter, lead vocalist, and guitarist of the death metal band Hypocrisy as well as the industrial metal band PAIN in which he is the only member. He is also the owner of The Abyss recording studio.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/40/Pain_Metalcamp07_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-tägtgren/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>