<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Pop Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Pop Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 15:23:51 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shakira]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shakira Isabel Mebarak Ripoll is a Colombian singer, songwriter, record producer, dancer, actress, and philanthropist. Born and raised in Barranquilla, Shakira has been referred to as the Queen of Latin Music and is noted for her versatility in music. She made her recording debut under Sony Music Colombia at the age of 13. Following the commercial failure of her first two Colombian albums, Magia (1991) and Peligro (1993), she rose to prominence in Hispanic countries with her next albums, Pies Descalzos (1995) and Dónde Están los Ladrones? (1998). Shakira entered the English-language market with her fifth album, Laundry Service (2001). It sold over 13 million copies, spawned the international number-one singles 'Whenever, Wherever' and 'Underneath Your Clothes', and propelled her reputation as a leading crossover artist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/86/Shakira_%26_Chris_Martin_-_Global_Citizen_Festival_Hamburg_04_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:49 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Oates]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-oates/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John William Oates is an American rock, R&B, and soul guitarist, singer, songwriter and record producer best known as half of the rock and soul duo, Hall & Oates.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/12/JohnOatesByPhilKonstantin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-oates/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roy Wood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-wood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0f/Roy_Wood_TopPop.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-wood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brendon Urie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brendon-urie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fb/Panic_at_the_Disco_Im_Park_2016_%2811_von_11%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brendon-urie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Madonna]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/madonna/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Madonna Louise Ciccone is an American singer-songwriter and actress. Referred to as the 'Queen of Pop', she is regarded as one of the most influential figures in popular culture. Madonna is noted for her continual reinvention and versatility in music production, songwriting, and visual presentation. Additionally she is recognized for pushing the boundaries of artistic expression in mainstream music while remaining completely in charge of every aspect of her career. Her works, which incorporate social, political, sexual, and religious themes, have generated both critical acclaim and controversy. Madonna is often cited as an influence by other artists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Madonna_Rebel_Heart_Tour_2015_-_Stockholm_%2823051472299%29_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/madonna/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Drake Bell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/drake-bell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jared Drake Bell, also known as Drake Campana, is an American actor, voice actor, singer, songwriter, and musician. Born in Newport Beach, California, he began his career as an actor in the early 1990s at the age of five with his first televised appearance on Home Improvement. Bell also appeared in several commercials, such as one for Pokémon Red and Blue, but is best known for his starring roles on Nickelodeon's The Amanda Show and Drake & Josh. Bell starred in a trilogy of The Fairly OddParents movies on Nickelodeon. Bell was the voice of Peter Parker / Spider-Man in the animated series Ultimate Spider-Man on Disney XD.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5d/Drake_Bell_2019_by_Glenn_Francis.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/drake-bell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Linda Ronstadt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/linda-ronstadt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Linda Maria Ronstadt is a retired American singer who performed and recorded in diverse genres including rock, country, light opera, and Latin. She has earned 10 Grammy Awards, three American Music Awards, two Academy of Country Music awards, an Emmy Award, and an ALMA Award. Many of her albums have been certified gold, platinum or multiplatinum in the United States and internationally. She has also earned nominations for a Tony Award and a Golden Globe award. She was awarded the Latin Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award by the Latin Recording Academy in 2011 and also awarded the Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award by the Recording Academy in 2016. She was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in April 2014. On July 28, 2014, she was awarded the National Medal of Arts and Humanities. In 2019, she received a star jointly with Dolly Parton and Emmylou Harris on the Hollywood Walk of Fame for their work as the group Trio. Ronstadt was among five honorees who received the 2019 Kennedy Center Honors for lifetime artistic achievements.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/50/LindaRonstadtPerforming.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/linda-ronstadt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[POL]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pol/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ab/Joe_King_%28guitarist%29.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pol/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alanis Morissette]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alanis Nadine Morissette is a Canadian-American singer, songwriter, record producer, and actress. Known for her emotive mezzo-soprano voice, Morissette began her career in Canada in the early 1990s with two mildly successful dance-pop albums. Afterward, as part of a recording deal, she moved to Holmby Hills, Los Angeles. In 1995, she released Jagged Little Pill, a more rock-oriented album which sold more than 33 million copies globally and is her most critically acclaimed work to date. This was made into a rock musical of the same name in 2017, which earned 15 Tony Award nominations including Best Musical. Her follow-up album, Supposed Former Infatuation Junkie, was released in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Alanis_Morissette_5-19-2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kenny Loggins]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kenny-loggins/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kenneth Clark Loggins is an American singer-songwriter and guitarist. His early songs were recorded with the Nitty Gritty Dirt Band in 1970, which led to seven albums recorded as Loggins and Messina from 1972 to 1977. His early soundtrack contributions date back to A Star Is Born in 1976, and he is known as the King of the Movie Soundtrack. As a solo artist, Loggins experienced a string of soundtrack successes, including an Academy Award nomination for 'Footloose' in 1984. Finally Home was released in 2013, shortly after Loggins formed the group Blue Sky Riders with Gary Burr and Georgia Middleman. He won a Daytime Emmy Award, two Grammy Awards, and was nominated for an Academy Award, a Tony Award, and a Golden Globe Award.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3e/Kenny_Loggins_1995.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kenny-loggins/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>