<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Pop Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Pop Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:04:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shakira]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shakira Isabel Mebarak Ripoll is a Colombian singer, songwriter, dancer, businesswoman, and philanthropist. Born and raised in Barranquilla, she made her recording debut under Sony Music Colombia at the age of 13. Following the commercial failure of her first two Colombian albums, Magia (1991) and Peligro (1993), she rose to prominence in Spanish-speaking countries with her next albums, Pies Descalzos (1995) and Dónde Están los Ladrones? (1998). Shakira entered the English-language market with her fifth album, Laundry Service (2001). It sold over 13 million copies and spawned the international number-one singles 'Whenever, Wherever' and 'Underneath Your Clothes'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/Shakira_in_Toronto_2018.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Linda Ronstadt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/linda-ronstadt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Linda Maria Ronstadt is a retired American popular music singer known for singing in a wide range of genres including rock, country, light opera, and Latin. She has earned 10 Grammy Awards, three American Music Awards, two Academy of Country Music awards, an Emmy Award, and an ALMA Award, and many of her albums have been certified gold, platinum or multiplatinum in the United States and internationally. She has also earned nominations for a Tony Award and a Golden Globe award. She was awarded the Latin Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award by The Latin Recording Academy in 2011 and also awarded the Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award by The Recording Academy in 2016. She was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in April 2014. On July 28, 2014, she was awarded the National Medal of Arts and Humanities. In 2019, she will receive a joint star with Dolly Parton and Emmylou Harris on the Hollywood Walk of Fame for their work as the group Trio.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/50/LindaRonstadtPerforming.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/linda-ronstadt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alanis Morissette]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alanis Nadine Morissette is a Canadian-American singer, songwriter, record producer, and actress. Known for her emotive mezzo-soprano voice, Morissette began her career in Canada in the early 1990s with two mildly successful dance-pop albums. Afterwards, as part of a recording deal, she moved to Holmby Hills, Los Angeles and in 1995 released Jagged Little Pill, a more rock-oriented album which sold more than 33 million copies globally and is her most critically acclaimed work. Her follow-up album, Supposed Former Infatuation Junkie, was released in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Alanis_Morissette_5-19-2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vasile Șeicaru]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vasile-șeicaru/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vasile Șeicaru is a Romanian folk musician. In the past he has worked with Cenaclul Flacăra.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a2/Vasile_%C8%98eicaru.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vasile-șeicaru/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Daniel Balavoine]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daniel-balavoine/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Daniel Balavoine was a French singer and songwriter. He was hugely popular in the French-speaking world, and inspired many singers in the 1980s, such as Jean-Jacques Goldman, Michel Berger, his closest friend, or the Japanese pop-rock group Crystal King; he was also a part of the original cast of the rock opera Starmania in 1978, which was written by Berger. He took part in French political life and is known for a 1980 televised verbal confrontation with then presidential candidate François Mitterrand.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/59/Daniel_Balavoine.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daniel-balavoine/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Neil Diamond]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-diamond/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Neil Leslie Diamond is an American singer-songwriter, musician and actor. With 38 songs in the Top 10 on the Billboard Adult Contemporary charts, Diamond has sold more than 100 million records worldwide, making him one of the best-selling musicians of all time. On the Hot 100 and Adult Contemporary charts, he has had ten No. 1 singles: 'Cracklin' Rosie', 'Song Sung Blue', 'Longfellow Serenade', 'I've Been This Way Before', 'If You Know What I Mean', 'Desirée', 'You Don't Bring Me Flowers', 'America', 'Yesterday's Songs', and 'Heartlight'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/17/Neil_Diamond_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-diamond/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Colbie Caillat]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/colbie-caillat/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Colbie Marie Caillat is an American singer-songwriter. Caillat rose to fame through social networking website Myspace. At that time, she was the number one unsigned artist of her genre. After signing with Universal Republic Records, she released her debut album, Coco, in July 2007. The album included the hit singles 'Bubbly' and 'Realize', and has sold 2,060,000 copies in the US, and is certified 2x Platinum. In 2008 she recorded a duet with Jason Mraz, 'Lucky', which won a Grammy Award. In August 2009 she released Breakthrough, her second album, which became her first album to debut at number one on the Billboard 200. It has been certified gold by the RIAA. Breakthrough was nominated for Best Pop Vocal Album at the 2010 Grammy Awards. She was also part of the group that won Album of the Year at the 2010 Grammy Awards for her background vocals and writing on Taylor Swift's Fearless album. In July 2011 she released her third studio album, All of You. In October 2012 she released her first Christmas album, Christmas in the Sand. Since 2018, she has been a member of the country music group Gone West.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/57/Colbie_Caillat_2009_American_Music_Award_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/colbie-caillat/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ringo Starr]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ringo-starr/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir Richard Starkey, known professionally as Ringo Starr, is an English musician, singer, songwriter and actor who gained worldwide fame as the drummer for the Beatles. He occasionally sang lead vocals with the group, usually for one song on each album, including 'With a Little Help from My Friends', 'Yellow Submarine', 'Good Night', 'Boys', and their cover of 'Act Naturally'. He also wrote and sang the Beatles' songs 'Don't Pass Me By' and 'Octopus's Garden', and is credited as a co-writer of others, including 'What Goes On'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Ringo_Starr_and_all_his_band_%288470866906%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ringo-starr/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hyde]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hyde/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hideto Takarai , known exclusively by his stage name Hyde, is a Japanese musician, singer, songwriter, producer, and actor. He is best known as lead vocalist of the rock band L'Arc-en-Ciel. He is also lead vocalist of Vamps and has a solo career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/Hyde_in_2013.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hyde/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tom Fletcher]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-fletcher/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Michael Fletcher is an English musician, singer, composer, author and YouTube vlogger. Among his accomplishments, he is one of the lead vocalists and the Rhythm guitarist of English pop rock band McFly, in addition to being the group's founder. He originally auditioned and was accepted into the band Busted before losing out on the place after the record label Island decided the band should be a trio rather than a four-piece. However, he still carried on writing with the band. In his thirteen-year career as a professional songwriter, Fletcher has penned ten UK number one singles and twenty-one top ten singles. He is credited as having written songs for bands including One Direction, Busted, the Vamps and 5 Seconds of Summer.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7e/ThomasMichaelFletcher.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-fletcher/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>