<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Pop Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Pop Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:46:53 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shakira]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shakira Isabel Mebarak Ripoll is a Colombian singer, songwriter, dancer, businesswoman, and philanthropist. Born and raised in Barranquilla, she made her recording debut under Sony Music Colombia at the age of 13. Following the commercial failure of her first two Colombian albums, Magia (1991) and Peligro (1993), she rose to prominence in Spanish-speaking countries with her next albums, Pies Descalzos (1995) and Dónde Están los Ladrones? (1998). Shakira entered the English-language market with her fifth album, Laundry Service (2001). It sold over 13 million copies and spawned the international number-one singles 'Whenever, Wherever' and 'Underneath Your Clothes'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/Shakira_in_Toronto_2018.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Linda Ronstadt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/linda-ronstadt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Linda Maria Ronstadt is a retired American popular music singer known for singing in a wide range of genres including rock, country, light opera, and Latin. She has earned 10 Grammy Awards, three American Music Awards, two Academy of Country Music awards, an Emmy Award, and an ALMA Award, and many of her albums have been certified gold, platinum or multiplatinum in the United States and internationally. She has also earned nominations for a Tony Award and a Golden Globe award. She was awarded the Latin Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award by The Latin Recording Academy in 2011 and also awarded the Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award by The Recording Academy in 2016. She was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in April 2014. On July 28, 2014, she was awarded the National Medal of Arts and Humanities. In 2019, she will receive a joint star with Dolly Parton and Emmylou Harris on the Hollywood Walk of Fame for their work as the group Trio.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/50/LindaRonstadtPerforming.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/linda-ronstadt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alanis Morissette]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alanis Nadine Morissette is a Canadian-American singer, songwriter, record producer, and actress. Known for her emotive mezzo-soprano voice, Morissette began her career in Canada in the early 1990s with two mildly successful dance-pop albums. Afterwards, as part of a recording deal, she moved to Holmby Hills, Los Angeles and in 1995 released Jagged Little Pill, a more rock-oriented album which sold more than 33 million copies globally and is her most critically acclaimed work. Her follow-up album, Supposed Former Infatuation Junkie, was released in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Alanis_Morissette_5-19-2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vasile Șeicaru]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vasile-șeicaru/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vasile Șeicaru is a Romanian folk musician. In the past he has worked with Cenaclul Flacăra.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a2/Vasile_%C8%98eicaru.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vasile-șeicaru/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Elvis Presley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elvis-presley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Elvis Aaron Presley, also known mononymously as Elvis, was an American singer and actor. Regarded as one of the most significant cultural icons of the 20th century, he is often referred to as the 'King of Rock and Roll' or simply 'the King'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2d/PresleyPromo1954PhotoOnly.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elvis-presley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Drake Bell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/drake-bell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jared Drake Bell is an American actor, voice actor, singer, songwriter, and musician. Born in Newport Beach, California, he began his career as an actor in the early 1990s at the age of five with his first televised appearance on Home Improvement. Bell also appeared in several commercials, such as one for Pokémon Red and Blue, but is best known for his starring roles on Nickelodeon's The Amanda Show and Drake & Josh. Bell starred in a trilogy of The Fairly OddParents movies on Nickelodeon. Bell was the voice of Peter Parker / Spider-Man in the animated series Ultimate Spider-Man on Disney XD.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5d/Drake_Bell_2019_by_Glenn_Francis.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/drake-bell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brendon Urie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brendon-urie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brendon Boyd Urie is an American singer, songwriter, and musician, best known as the lead vocalist of Panic! at the Disco, of which he is the only member remaining.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fb/Panic_at_the_Disco_Im_Park_2016_%2811_von_11%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brendon-urie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe King]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-king-(guitarist)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Adam King is an American musician who is the guitarist, backing vocalist, songwriter, and co-founder of Denver-based rock band The Fray.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ab/Joe_King_%28guitarist%29.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-king-(guitarist)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roy Wood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-wood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roy Wood is an English singer-songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. He was particularly successful in the 1960s and 1970s as member and co-founder of The Move, Electric Light Orchestra and Wizzard. As a songwriter, he contributed a number of hits to the repertoire of these bands. Collectively, hit records by The Move, Electric Light Orchestra, Wizzard, and Wood's own solo singles demonstrated an impressive chart run for an individual, both as composer and performer. Altogether he had more than 20 singles in the UK Singles Chart under various guises, including three UK No. 1 hits.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0f/Roy_Wood_TopPop.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-wood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Daniel Balavoine]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daniel-balavoine/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Daniel Balavoine was a French singer and songwriter. He was hugely popular in the French-speaking world, and inspired many singers in the 1980s, such as Jean-Jacques Goldman, Michel Berger, his closest friend, or the Japanese pop-rock group Crystal King; he was also a part of the original cast of the rock opera Starmania in 1978, which was written by Berger. He took part in French political life and is known for a 1980 televised verbal confrontation with then presidential candidate François Mitterrand.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/59/Daniel_Balavoine.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daniel-balavoine/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>