<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Psychedelic Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Psychedelic Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 14:32:18 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Angelakos]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-angelakos/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael John Angelakos is an American musician of Greek descent, a singer, songwriter and record producer. He is best known as the frontman of the indie electronic band Passion Pit.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Flickr_-_moses_namkung_-_Passion_Pit_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-angelakos/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roger Waters]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roger-waters/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>George Roger Waters is an English songwriter, singer, bassist, and composer. In 1965, he co-founded the progressive rock band Pink Floyd. Waters initially served solely as the bassist, but following the departure of singer-songwriter Syd Barrett in 1968, he also became their lyricist, co-lead vocalist, and conceptual leader.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/03/Roger_Waters%2C_May_18_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roger-waters/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jerry Garcia]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jerry-garcia/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jerome John 'Jerry' Garcia was an American singer-songwriter and guitarist, best known for his work as the lead guitarist and as a vocalist with the band the Grateful Dead, which came to prominence during the counterculture era in the 1960s. Although he disavowed the role, Garcia was viewed by many as the leader or 'spokesman' of the group.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e8/Grateful_Dead_-_Jerry_Garcia.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jerry-garcia/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul Kantner]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-kantner/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul Lorin Kantner was an American rock musician. He is best known as the co-founder, rhythm guitarist, and occasional vocalist of Jefferson Airplane, a leading psychedelic rock band of the counterculture era. He continued these roles as a member of Jefferson Starship, Jefferson Airplane's successor band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6a/Paul_Kantner_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-kantner/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robby Krieger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robby-krieger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Alan Krieger is an American guitarist and singer-songwriter best known as the guitarist of the rock band The Doors; as such he has been inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame. Krieger wrote or co-wrote many of the Doors' songs, including the hits 'Light My Fire', 'Love Me Two Times', 'Touch Me', and 'Love Her Madly'. After the Doors disbanded, Krieger continued his performing and recording career with other musicians including former Doors bandmates John Densmore and Ray Manzarek. He was listed by Rolling Stone as one of the 100 greatest guitarists of all time.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/63/Robby_III.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robby-krieger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Bowie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-bowie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Robert Jones, known professionally as David Bowie, was an English singer-songwriter and actor. He was a leading figure in the music industry and is considered one of the most influential musicians of the 20th century, acclaimed by critics and musicians, particularly for his innovative work during the 1970s. His career was marked by reinvention and visual presentation, with his music and stagecraft having a significant impact on popular music. During his lifetime, his record sales, estimated at 140 million albums worldwide, made him one of the world's best-selling music artists. In the UK, he was awarded ten platinum album certifications, eleven gold and eight silver, and released eleven number-one albums. In the US, he received five platinum and nine gold certifications. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1996.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e8/David-Bowie_Chicago_2002-08-08_photoby_Adam-Bielawski-cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-bowie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lewis Brian Hopkins Jones was an English musician, best known as the founder and original leader of the Rolling Stones. Initially a slide guitarist, Jones would go on to play a wide variety of instruments on Rolling Stones recordings and in concerts, such as rhythm and lead guitar, sitar, dulcimer, various keyboard instruments such as piano and mellotron, marimba, wind instruments such as harmonica, recorder, saxophone, as well as drums, vocals and numerous others.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6b/Brian_Jones%2C_Statesboro%2C_Georgia%2C_May_4%2C_1965_%28377872218%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bob Weir]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-weir/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Hall Weir is an American musician and songwriter best known as a founding member of the rock band Grateful Dead. After the Grateful Dead disbanded in 1995, Weir performed with The Other Ones, later known as The Dead, together with other former members of the Grateful Dead. Weir also founded and played in several other bands during and after his career with the Grateful Dead, including Kingfish, the Bob Weir Band, Bobby and the Midnites, Scaring the Children, RatDog, and Furthur, which he co-led with former Grateful Dead bassist Phil Lesh. In 2015, Weir, along with former Grateful Dead members Mickey Hart and Bill Kreutzmann, joined with Grammy-winning singer/guitarist John Mayer to form the band Dead & Company. The band remains active.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/81/Bob_Weir.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-weir/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Janis Joplin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/janis-joplin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Janis Lyn Joplin was an American rock, soul and blues singer-songwriter, and one of the most successful and widely known rock stars of her era. After releasing three albums, she died of a heroin overdose at the age of 27. A fourth album, Pearl, was released in January 1971, just over three months after her death. It reached number one on the Billboard charts.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/79/Janis_Joplin_in_1969_%28cropped%29.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/janis-joplin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Barry Gibb]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/barry-gibb/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir Barry Alan Crompton Gibb is a British-American singer, songwriter, musician and record producer who rose to worldwide fame as a co-founder of the group the Bee Gees, one of the most commercially successful groups in the history of popular music. With his younger brothers, twins Robin and Maurice Gibb, he formed a songwriting partnership beginning in 1955.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/17/Barry_Gibb_Hollywood_Bowl-0545_%2814365129281%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/barry-gibb/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>