<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » New Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » New Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:25:04 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Serj Tankian]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Serj Tankian is an Armenian-American musician, singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, poet and political activist. He is best known as the lead vocalist, songwriter, keyboardist, and occasional live rhythm guitarist of the band System of a Down, formed in 1994.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/69/Serj_Tankian_Spirit_of_Burgas_Bulgaria_2010_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Shinoda]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Kenji Shinoda is an American musician, singer, songwriter, rapper, record producer, and graphic designer. He co-founded Linkin Park in 1996 and is the band's rhythm guitarist, primary songwriter, keyboardist, producer, and co-lead vocalist. Shinoda later created a hip-hop-driven side project, Fort Minor, in 2004. He has also served as a producer for tracks and albums by Lupe Fiasco, Styles of Beyond and the X-Ecutioners.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/Mike_Shinoda_4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brad Delson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brad-delson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bradford Phillip Delson is an American musician and record producer, best known as the lead guitarist and one of the founding members of the American rock band Linkin Park.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/17/Brad_Delson_playing_at_Smirnoff_Music_Centre.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brad-delson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Fred Durst]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fred-durst/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Frederick Durst is an American vocalist, actor and film director. He is best known as the frontman of the rap rock band Limp Bizkit, formed in 1994, with whom he released six studio albums. He started making money playing in several Jacksonville, Florida bands, mowing lawns and drawing tattoos.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1a/Fred_Durst_at_the_2008_Tribeca_Film_Festival.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fred-durst/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Corey Taylor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/corey-taylor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Corey Todd Taylor is an American singer, songwriter, actor and author and publisher. He is known as the lead vocalist and lyricist of the bands Slipknot and Stone Sour.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/df/CoreyTaylorTrezzo.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/corey-taylor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roy Mayorga]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-mayorga/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roy Maurice Mayorga is an American musician, best known as the drummer for the American heavy metal bands Hellyeah and Stone Sour. He is of Ecuadorian and Cuban descent.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/dc/Roy_Mayorga_at_the_Rockstar_Uproar_Festival.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-mayorga/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tommy Lee]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tommy-lee/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Lee Bass is an American musician and founding member of Mötley Crüe. As well as being the band's long-term drummer, Lee founded rap-metal band Methods of Mayhem, and has pursued solo musical projects.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/24/Tommy_Lee_2012.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tommy-lee/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Wes Borland]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wes-borland/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Wesley Louden Borland is an American rock musician and artist. He is best known as the current guitarist and backing vocalist of the American rap rock band Limp Bizkit and as the lead vocalist and guitarist of the alternative and industrial rock band Black Light Burns and the metal band Big Dumb Face.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/07/13-06-07_RaR_LB_Wes_Borland_05.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wes-borland/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joey Jordison]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joey-jordison/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nathan Jonas 'Joey' Jordison, is an American musician, songwriter, record producer and multi-instrumentalist, best known for his work as the former drummer and co-songwriter for the American heavy metal band Slipknot as well as guitarist in the American horror punk band Murderdolls. Jordison played in Slipknot since their formation in 1995 until his departure from the band in December 2013. He was the drummer and founder of the American heavy metal band Scar the Martyr, which formed in 2013 and disbanded in 2016. He grew up in Waukee, Iowa with his parents and two sisters, and was given his first drum kit at the age of 8. He performed in several bands until joining in the summer of 1995 with the group The Pale Ones, which would later change their name to Slipknot. Of Slipknot's nine-member lineup, which lasted from 1999–2010, Joey was the third to join the band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/20/Joey_Jordison_at_Mayhem.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joey-jordison/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>