<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Alternative Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Alternative Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 23:44:25 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Daron Malakian]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daron-malakian/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Daron Vartan Malakian is an Armenian-American musician, singer, songwriter, and record producer. He is best known as the guitarist, songwriter and second vocalist of metal band System of a Down, and as the lead vocalist, lead guitarist, multi-instrumentalist, and songwriter of Scars on Broadway. Malakian is known for his distinctive playing and is ranked 14th in Loudwire's list of 'Top 50 Hard Rock + Metal Guitarists of All Time' and number 11 in MusicRadar's poll 'The 20 Greatest Metal Guitarists Ever'. He is placed 30th in Guitar World's list of 'The 100 Greatest Heavy Metal Guitarists of All Time'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/DM-photo.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daron-malakian/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paulo Jr.]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paulo-jr./]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paulo Xisto Pinto Júnior is a Brazilian musician best known as the bassist for heavy metal band Sepultura. He joined Sepultura after Roberto Raffan left the band in 1984, becoming Sepultura's second bassist. Although no original members are left in Sepultura, Pinto is the longest remaining member of Sepultura despite never performing on any album until Chaos A.D. (1993).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c4/Nova_Rock_2014_-_Paulo_Xisto_Pinto_Jr..JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paulo-jr./]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lacey Sturm]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lacey-sturm/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lacey Nicole Sturm is an American singer and songwriter born in Homestead, Florida, and raised in Arlington, Texas. She is a co-founder and former lead vocalist of the hard rock band Flyleaf. In February 2016, Sturm became the first solo female artist to top the Billboard Hard Rock Albums chart with her debut release Life Screams.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/12/Lacey_Sturm_%28Flyleaf%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lacey-sturm/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Wes Scantlin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wes-scantlin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Wesley Reid Scantlin is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. He is best known as the lead vocalist, guitarist, and only constant member of rock band Puddle of Mudd. He was named one of the 'Top 100 Heavy Metal Vocalists' by Hit Parader.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/41/Wes_Scantlin_Puddle_of_Mudd_2009_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wes-scantlin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stephen Carpenter]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stephen-carpenter/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e9/Stephen_Carpenter.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stephen-carpenter/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Troy McLawhorn]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/troy-mclawhorn/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Troy McLawhorn is an American musician, songwriter, and record producer who has been a guitarist, backing vocalist, and songwriting partner in the bands Evanescence, Seether, Dark New Day, doubleDrive, Still Rain, and Gibraltar.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ee/USMC-090526-M-2664B-104.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/troy-mclawhorn/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Lee]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-lee/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Lynn Hartzler is an American singer, songwriter, and pianist. She is the co-founder and lead vocalist of the rock band Evanescence. Alongside her contributions with the band, Lee has also participated on other musical projects including Nightmare Revisited and Muppets: The Green Album from Walt Disney Records. She has performed collaborations with artists such as Korn, Seether, and David Hodges. Lee composed the soundtrack to the films War Story (2014) and Indigo Grey: The Passage (2015) with cellist Dave Eggar, and the song 'Speak to Me' for the film Voice from the Stone (2017). She possesses a mezzo-soprano vocal range.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0e/Amy_Lynn_Lee_in_2015.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-lee/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Shinoda]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Kenji Shinoda is an American musician, rapper, singer, songwriter, record producer, and graphic designer. He co-founded Linkin Park in 1996 and is the band's lead vocalist, as well as rhythm guitarist, keyboardist, primary songwriter and producer. Shinoda later created a hip-hop-driven side project, Fort Minor, in 2004. He has also served as a producer for tracks and albums by Lupe Fiasco, Styles of Beyond and the X-Ecutioners.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/Mike_Shinoda_4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Page Hamilton]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/page-hamilton/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Page Hamilton is an American guitarist, singer, songwriter and record producer, mostly noted for his work with alternative metal band Helmet. Most of his work has been in the hard rock and alternative metal styles, though he trained in jazz guitar and has substantial connections with avant-garde music and film soundtrack composition.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/ba/Helmet_-_Page_Hamilton_%286819476974%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/page-hamilton/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Corey Taylor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/corey-taylor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Corey Todd Taylor is an American singer, musician and songwriter. He is known as the lead vocalist and lyricist of the bands Slipknot and Stone Sour.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/df/CoreyTaylorTrezzo.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/corey-taylor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>