<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Alternative Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Alternative Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:04:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Shinoda]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Kenji Shinoda is an American musician, singer, songwriter, rapper, record producer, and graphic designer. He co-founded Linkin Park in 1996 and is the band's rhythm guitarist, primary songwriter, keyboardist, producer, and co-lead vocalist. Shinoda later created a hip-hop-driven side project, Fort Minor, in 2004. He has also served as a producer for tracks and albums by Lupe Fiasco, Styles of Beyond and the X-Ecutioners.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/Mike_Shinoda_4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tom Morello]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-morello/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Baptiste Morello is an American musician, singer, songwriter, actor and political activist. He is best known for his tenure with the band Rage Against the Machine and then with Audioslave. As of 2016, Morello is a member of the supergroup Prophets of Rage. Morello was also a touring musician with Bruce Springsteen and the E Street Band. He is also known for his acoustic solo act, the Nightwatchman, and Street Sweeper Social Club. Morello also co-founded Axis of Justice, which airs a monthly program on Pacifica Radio station KPFK in Los Angeles.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ae/Day_28_Occupy_Wall_Street_Tom_Morello_2011_Shankbone_7.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-morello/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Lee]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-lee/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Lynn Hartzler, known professionally as Amy Lee, is an American singer, songwriter, and pianist. She is the co-founder and lead vocalist of the rock band Evanescence. Along with her contributions with the band, Lee has also participated on other musical projects including Walt Disney Records' Nightmare Revisited and Muppets: The Green Album. She has performed collaborations with artists such as Korn, Seether, and David Hodges. Lee composed the soundtrack to the films War Story (2014) and Indigo Grey: The Passage (2015) with cellist Dave Eggar, and the song 'Speak to Me' for the film Voice from the Stone (2017). She possesses a mezzo-soprano vocal range.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/22/AmyLee2003BillboardAwards.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-lee/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Corey Taylor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/corey-taylor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Corey Todd Taylor is an American singer, songwriter, actor and author and publisher. He is known as the lead vocalist and lyricist of the bands Slipknot and Stone Sour.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/df/CoreyTaylorTrezzo.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/corey-taylor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marilyn Manson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marilyn-manson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Hugh Warner, known professionally as Marilyn Manson, is an American singer, songwriter, record producer, actor, visual artist and music video director. He is known for his controversial stage personality and image as the lead singer of the band Marilyn Manson, which he co-founded with guitarist Daisy Berkowitz and of which he remains the only constant member. Like the other founding members of the band, his stage name was formed by combining and juxtaposing the names of two American pop cultural icons of the 1960s: actress Marilyn Monroe and criminal Charles Manson.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Revolver_Golden_Gods_Awards.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marilyn-manson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Myles Kennedy]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/myles-kennedy/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Myles Richard Bass, known professionally as Myles Kennedy, is an American musician, singer, and songwriter, best known as the lead vocalist and rhythm guitarist of the rock band Alter Bridge, and as the lead vocalist in guitarist Slash's backing band, known as Myles Kennedy and the Conspirators. A former guitar instructor from Spokane, Washington, he has worked as a session musician and songwriter, making both studio and live appearances with several artists, and has been involved with several projects throughout his career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/88/20170615-079-Nova_Rock_2017-Alter_Bridge-Myles_Kennedy_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/myles-kennedy/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>