<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Alternative Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Alternative Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 22:26:45 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Serj Tankian]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Serj Tankian is an Armenian-American musician, singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, poet and political activist. He is best known as the lead vocalist, songwriter, keyboardist, and occasional live rhythm guitarist of the band System of a Down, formed in 1994.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/69/Serj_Tankian_Spirit_of_Burgas_Bulgaria_2010_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Shinoda]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Kenji Shinoda is an American musician, singer, songwriter, rapper, record producer, and graphic designer. He co-founded Linkin Park in 1996 and is the band's rhythm guitarist, primary songwriter, keyboardist, producer, and co-lead vocalist. Shinoda later created a hip-hop-driven side project, Fort Minor, in 2004. He has also served as a producer for tracks and albums by Lupe Fiasco, Styles of Beyond and the X-Ecutioners.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/Mike_Shinoda_4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tom Morello]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-morello/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Baptiste Morello is an American musician, singer, songwriter, actor and political activist. He is best known for his tenure with the band Rage Against the Machine and then with Audioslave. As of 2016, Morello is a member of the supergroup Prophets of Rage. Morello was also a touring musician with Bruce Springsteen and the E Street Band. He is also known for his acoustic solo act, the Nightwatchman, and Street Sweeper Social Club. Morello also co-founded Axis of Justice, which airs a monthly program on Pacifica Radio station KPFK in Los Angeles.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ae/Day_28_Occupy_Wall_Street_Tom_Morello_2011_Shankbone_7.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-morello/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Billy Gould]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billy-gould/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William David 'Billy' Gould is an American musician and producer. He is best known as the bassist of Faith No More.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ed/Bill_Gould_from_Faith_No_More_-_cropped_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billy-gould/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Lee]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-lee/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Lynn Hartzler, known professionally as Amy Lee, is an American singer, songwriter, and pianist. She is the co-founder and lead vocalist of the rock band Evanescence. Along with her contributions with the band, Lee has also participated on other musical projects including Walt Disney Records' Nightmare Revisited and Muppets: The Green Album. She has performed collaborations with artists such as Korn, Seether, and David Hodges. Lee composed the soundtrack to the films War Story (2014) and Indigo Grey: The Passage (2015) with cellist Dave Eggar, and the song 'Speak to Me' for the film Voice from the Stone (2017). She possesses a mezzo-soprano vocal range.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/22/AmyLee2003BillboardAwards.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-lee/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chino Moreno]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chino-moreno/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Camilo Wong 'Chino' Moreno is an American singer, songwriter and musician who is best known as the lead vocalist and contributing guitarist of Deftones. He is also a member of the side-project groups Team Sleep, Crosses, Saudade and Palms.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6e/Chino_Moreno.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chino-moreno/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mick Thomson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mick-thomson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Mickael Gordon 'Mick' Thomson is an American heavy metal musician. He is one of two guitarists in the band Slipknot, in which he is designated #7. Thomson originally met founding Slipknot members Anders Colsefni, Donnie Steele and Paul Gray through their mutual involvement in death metal band Body Pit, and later joined in early 1996. Following the departure of Joey Jordison in 2013, Thomson is now the third longest-serving member of Slipknot.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/41/Mick_Thomson_unmasked.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mick-thomson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brad Delson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brad-delson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bradford Phillip Delson is an American musician and record producer, best known as the lead guitarist and one of the founding members of the American rock band Linkin Park.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/17/Brad_Delson_playing_at_Smirnoff_Music_Centre.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brad-delson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paulo Jr.]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paulo-jr./]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paulo Xisto Pinto Jr. is a Brazilian musician/bassist for heavy metal band Sepultura. Pinto joined Sepultura after 'Gato''s split in 1984, becoming Sepultura's second and only bassist ever and although no original members are left in Sepultura, Pinto is the longest remaining member of Sepultura.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/aa/20140613-016-Nova_Rock_2014-Sepultura-Paulo_Xisto_Pinto_Jr.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paulo-jr./]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>