<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Dark Ambient</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Dark Ambient</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 13:13:14 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Buckethead]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Patrick Carroll, known professionally as Buckethead, is an American musician, songwriter, and multi-instrumentalist. He received critical acclaim for his innovative electric guitar playing. His music spans genres, including progressive metal, funk, blues, bluegrass, ambient, and avant-garde music. He performs primarily as a solo artist, although he collaborated with a wide variety of artists such as Bill Laswell, Bootsy Collins, Bernie Worrell, Iggy Pop, Les Claypool, Serj Tankian, Bill Moseley, Mike Patton, Viggo Mortensen, That 1 Guy, Bassnectar, and Skating Polly. He was also a member of Guns N' Roses from 2000 to 2004. He has 315 studio albums, four special releases, and one EP. He performed on more than fifty albums by other artists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Neumos_seattle_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Maurice de Jong]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/maurice-de-jong/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Maurice de Jong, known by his moniker Mories, is a Dutch composer and musician. He is best recognized for his multiple music projects, namely Gnaw Their Tongues, Seirom, Aderlating, Cloak of Altering and De Magia Veterum. His compositions are informed by ambient music, black metal, drone music, electronic music and the avant-garde. His interests lie in invoking a disquieting and nightmarish atmosphere with his music, which often utilizes distortion and dissonance. Lauded as a most prolific composer, de Jong has recorded an upwards of three albums per year since 2007.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Gnaw_Their_Tongues_%40_Roadburn_Festival_2017_05.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/maurice-de-jong/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:37 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Akira Yamaoka]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/akira-yamaoka/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/01/Akira_Yamaoka_-_Game_Developers_Conference_2010_-_Day_3_%283%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/akira-yamaoka/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:36 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>