<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Rockabilly</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Rockabilly</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 01:03:45 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roddy Radiation]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roddy-radiation/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roddy Radiation is an English musician who played lead guitar for The Specials, as well as many rockabilly bands such as the Bonediggers and the Tearjerkers. He wrote the Specials favourites 'Concrete Jungle', 'Rat Race' and 'Hey, Little Rich Girl', later covered by Amy Winehouse. Currently, Byers leads The Skabilly Rebels, a band that mixes ska rhythms with rockabilly.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a0/RoddyRadiationImage01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roddy-radiation/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Alvin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Albert Alvin is an American singer-songwriter, guitarist, music producer and poet. He is a former and founding member of the roots rock band the Blasters. Alvin has recorded and performed as a solo artist since the late 1980s and has been involved in various side projects and collaborations. He has had brief stints as a member of the bands X and the Knitters.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Dave_Alvin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Carl Perkins]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/carl-perkins/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Carl Lee Perkins was an American singer-songwriter who recorded most notably at the Sun Studio, in Memphis, beginning in 1954. Amongst his best-known songs are 'Blue Suede Shoes', 'Matchbox' and 'Everybody's Trying to Be My Baby'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/79/Cavenaugh_Park_Walnut_Ridge_AR_2013-04-27_013.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/carl-perkins/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Elvis Presley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elvis-presley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Elvis Aaron Presley, also known mononymously as Elvis, was an American singer and actor. Regarded as one of the most significant cultural icons of the 20th century, he is often referred to as the 'King of Rock and Roll' or simply 'the King'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2d/PresleyPromo1954PhotoOnly.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elvis-presley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Johnny Cash]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/johnny-cash/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John R. 'Johnny' Cash was an American singer-songwriter, guitarist, actor, and author. He is one of the best-selling music artists of all time, having sold more than 90 million records worldwide. His genre-spanning songs and sound embraced country music, rock and roll, rockabilly, blues, folk, and gospel. This crossover appeal won Cash the rare honor of being inducted into the Country Music, Rock and Roll, and Gospel Music Halls of Fame.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/be/Johnny_Cash_%281964%29.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/johnny-cash/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Buddy Holly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buddy-holly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Charles Hardin Holley, known professionally as Buddy Holly, was an American musician and singer-songwriter who was a central and pioneering figure of mid-1950s rock and roll. He was born in Lubbock, Texas, to a musical family during the Great Depression, and learned to play guitar and sing alongside his siblings. His style was influenced by gospel music, country music, and rhythm and blues acts, which he performed in Lubbock with his friends from high school.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/14/Buddy_Holly_cropped.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buddy-holly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ricky Nelson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ricky-nelson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Eric Hilliard Nelson, known professionally as Ricky Nelson, was an American pop star, musician, and singer-songwriter. From age eight he starred alongside his family in the radio and television series The Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet. In 1957 he began a long and successful career as a popular recording artist. As one of the top 'teen idols' of the 1950s his fame led to a motion picture role co-starring alongside John Wayne and Dean Martin in Howard Hawks's western feature film Rio Bravo (1959). He placed 53 songs on the Billboard Hot 100, and its predecessors, between 1957 and 1973, including 'Poor Little Fool' in 1958, which was the first #1 song on Billboard magazine's then-newly created Hot 100 chart. He recorded 19 additional Top 10 hits and was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame on January 21, 1987. In 1996 Nelson was ranked #49 on TV Guide's 50 Greatest TV Stars of All Time.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/14/Ricky_Nelson_-_Modern_Screen%2C_Feb._1958.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ricky-nelson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gene Vincent]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gene-vincent/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vincent Eugene Craddock, known as Gene Vincent, was an American musician who pioneered the styles of rock and roll and rockabilly. His 1956 top ten hit with his Blue Caps, 'Be-Bop-A-Lula', is considered a significant early example of rockabilly. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and the Rockabilly Hall of Fame.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f0/Genevincent015e.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gene-vincent/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Boz Boorer]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/boz-boorer/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Martin James 'Boz' Boorer is an English guitarist and producer most known for his work founding the new wave rockabilly group, The Polecats, and later for his work as a co-writer, guitarist and musical director with Morrissey for which he is principally known today.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/86/Bozboorer.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/boz-boorer/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Setzer]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-setzer/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Robert Setzer is an American guitarist, singer, and songwriter. He found widespread success in the early 1980s with the 1950s-style rockabilly group Stray Cats, and revitalized his career in the early 1990s with his swing revival band, the Brian Setzer Orchestra.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7d/Brian_Salzburg_2006.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-setzer/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>