<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Rockabilly</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Rockabilly</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 11:07:50 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Alvin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Albert Alvin is an American singer-songwriter, guitarist, music producer and poet. He is a former and founding member of the roots rock band the Blasters. Alvin has recorded and performed as a solo artist since the late 1980s and has been involved in various side projects and collaborations. He has had brief stints as a member of the bands X and the Knitters.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Dave_Alvin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Johnny Cash]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/johnny-cash/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John R. Cash, commonly known as Johnny Cash, was an American singer, songwriter, musician, and actor. Much of Cash's music contained themes of sorrow, moral tribulation, and redemption, especially in the later stages of his career. He was known for his deep, calm bass-baritone voice, the distinctive sound of his Tennessee Three backing band characterized by train-like chugging guitar rhythms, a rebelliousness coupled with an increasingly somber and humble demeanor, free prison concerts, and a trademark all-black stage wardrobe which earned him the nickname 'The Man in Black'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/be/Johnny_Cash_%281964%29.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/johnny-cash/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Buddy Holly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buddy-holly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Charles Hardin Holley, known professionally as Buddy Holly, was an American singer-songwriter who was a central and pioneering figure of mid-1950s rock and roll. He was born in Lubbock, Texas, to a musical family during the Great Depression, and learned to play guitar and sing alongside his siblings. His style was influenced by gospel music, country music, and rhythm and blues acts, which he performed in Lubbock with his friends from high school.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/14/Buddy_Holly_cropped.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buddy-holly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Neil Young]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Neil Percival Young is a Canadian-American singer-songwriter, musician, and activist. After embarking on a music career in the 1960s, he moved to Los Angeles, joining Buffalo Springfield with Stephen Stills, Richie Furay and others. Since his early solo albums and those with his backing band Crazy Horse, Young has been prolific, recording a steady stream of studio and live albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bb/Neil_Young_-_Per_Ole_Hagen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ricky Nelson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ricky-nelson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Eric Hilliard Nelson, known professionally as Ricky Nelson until his 21st birthday when he officially dropped the 'y' and simply became Rick Nelson, was an American rock & roll star, pop pioneer, musician, and singer-songwriter. From age eight he starred alongside his family in the radio and television series The Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet. In 1957 he began a long and successful career as a popular recording artist. As one of the top 'teen idols' of the 1950s his fame led to a motion picture role co-starring alongside John Wayne and Dean Martin in Howard Hawks's western feature film Rio Bravo (1959). He placed 53 songs on the Billboard Hot 100, and its predecessors, between 1957 and 1973, including 'Poor Little Fool' in 1958, which was the first number 1 song on Billboard magazine's then-newly created Hot 100 chart. He recorded 19 additional Top 10 hits and was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame on January 21, 1987. In 1996 Nelson was ranked No. 49 on TV Guide's 50 Greatest TV Stars of All Time.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/14/Ricky_Nelson_-_Modern_Screen%2C_Feb._1958.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ricky-nelson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gene Vincent]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gene-vincent/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vincent Eugene Craddock, known as Gene Vincent, was an American musician who pioneered the styles of rock and roll and rockabilly. His 1956 top ten hit with his Blue Caps, 'Be-Bop-a-Lula', is considered a significant early example of rockabilly. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and the Rockabilly Hall of Fame. He is sometimes referred to by his somewhat unusual nickname/moniker The Screaming End.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f0/Genevincent015e.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gene-vincent/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Boz Boorer]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/boz-boorer/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/86/Bozboorer.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/boz-boorer/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Setzer]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-setzer/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Robert Setzer is an American guitarist, singer, and songwriter. He found widespread success in the early 1980s with the 1950s-style rockabilly group Stray Cats, and revitalized his career in the early 1990s with his swing revival band, the Brian Setzer Orchestra. In 1987, he made a cameo appearance as Eddie Cochran in the film “La Bamba”.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7d/Brian_Salzburg_2006.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-setzer/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Carl Smith]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/carl-smith/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6a/Carl_Smith_%281968%29.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/carl-smith/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lonnie Mack]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lonnie-mack/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/74/LonnieMackRisingSun.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lonnie-mack/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>