<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Chickenfoot</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Chickenfoot</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 19:00:48 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Satriani]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-satriani/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Satriani is an American guitarist, composer, songwriter, and guitar teacher. Early in his career, Satriani worked as a guitar instructor, with many of his former students achieving fame, including Steve Vai, Larry LaLonde, Rick Hunolt, Kirk Hammett, Andy Timmons, Charlie Hunter, Kevin Cadogan, and Alex Skolnick; he then went on to have a successful solo music career. He is a 15-time Grammy Award nominee and has sold over 10 million albums, making him the bestselling instrumental rock guitarist of all time.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f9/Joe_satriani_without_sunglasses_2004.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-satriani/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sammy Hagar]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sammy-hagar/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Samuel Roy Hagar, also known as The Red Rocker, is an American singer-songwriter, musician, and entrepreneur. Hagar came to prominence in the 1970s with the hard rock band Montrose. He then launched a successful solo career, scoring an enduring hit in 1984 with 'I Can't Drive 55'. He enjoyed commercial success when he replaced David Lee Roth as the lead singer of Van Halen in 1985, but left in 1996. He returned to the band for a two-year reunion from 2003 to 2005. On March 12, 2007, Hagar was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of Van Halen. His musical style primarily consists of hard rock, heavy metal, and glam metal.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/64/SammyHagar.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sammy-hagar/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:37 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>