<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Rock Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Rock Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:46:53 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Howie Day]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/howie-day/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Howard Kern 'Howie' Day is an American singer-songwriter. Beginning his career as a solo artist in the late 1990s, Day became known for his extensive touring and in-concert use of samplers and effects pedals in order to accompany himself. He self-financed and self-released his first album, Australia, in 2000.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/30/Howiedaycrouching.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/howie-day/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kelly Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kelly-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kelly Jones is a Welsh singer-songwriter. He is the lead singer and lead guitarist of the rock band Stereophonics.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fe/Kelly_jones_cardiff_2005.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kelly-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shakira]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shakira Isabel Mebarak Ripoll is a Colombian singer, songwriter, dancer, businesswoman, and philanthropist. Born and raised in Barranquilla, she made her recording debut under Sony Music Colombia at the age of 13. Following the commercial failure of her first two Colombian albums, Magia (1991) and Peligro (1993), she rose to prominence in Spanish-speaking countries with her next albums, Pies Descalzos (1995) and Dónde Están los Ladrones? (1998). Shakira entered the English-language market with her fifth album, Laundry Service (2001). It sold over 13 million copies and spawned the international number-one singles 'Whenever, Wherever' and 'Underneath Your Clothes'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/Shakira_in_Toronto_2018.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gail Ann Dorsey]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gail-ann-dorsey/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gail Ann Dorsey is an American musician. With a long career as a session musician mainly on bass guitar, she is perhaps best known for her lengthy residency in David Bowie's band, from 1995 to Bowie's death in 2016. Aside from playing bass, she sang lead vocals on live versions of 'Under Pressure' and dueted with Bowie on other songs, including 'The London Boys', 'Aladdin Sane (1913-1938-197?)', 'I Dig Everything', accompanying Bowie on clarinet, and a cover of Laurie Anderson's 'O Superman'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7e/Gail_Ann_Dorsey.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gail-ann-dorsey/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Inoran]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/inoran/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kiyonobu Inoue , better known exclusively by his stage name Inoran, is a Japanese musician, singer and songwriter. He is best known as the rhythm guitarist and co-founder of the rock band Luna Sea. He started his solo career in 1997. Luna Sea disbanded in 2000, and he formed Fake? with Oblivion Dust vocalist Ken Lloyd a year later. In 2005 he left Fake? and founded Tourbillon with Luna Sea vocalist Ryuichi Kawamura and Hiroaki Hayama. He rejoined Luna Sea when they reunited in 2010, and in 2012 formed Muddy Apes with bassist Taka Hirose and guitarist Dean Tidey, both from Feeder, and 8otto's vocalist Maeson.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/37/INORAN2013.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/inoran/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Willie Nelson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Willie Hugh Nelson is an American musician, actor, and activist. The critical success of the album Shotgun Willie (1973), combined with the critical and commercial success of Red Headed Stranger (1975) and Stardust (1978), made Nelson one of the most recognized artists in country music. He was one of the main figures of outlaw country, a subgenre of country music that developed in the late 1960s as a reaction to the conservative restrictions of the Nashville sound. Nelson has acted in over 30 films, co-authored several books, and has been involved in activism for the use of biofuels and the legalization of marijuana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/WillieNelson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sebastian]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sebastian-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Knud Torben Christensen, better known by his stage name Sebastian, is a Danish singer, guitarist and composer. 
Starting as a musician in the late 1960s he is still active and very popular. So far his career has spanned four decades.
Having worked in the folk genre, he has become one of the most prominent pop/rock musicians in Denmark and has scored numerous films and plays. Since the 1990s he has primarily worked with Danish musicals, with great success.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f8/Sebastian_%28Danish_artist%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sebastian-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Fred Tackett]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fred-tackett/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Fred Tackett an American native of Arkansas, is an accomplished songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. Originally a session player on guitar, mandolin, and trumpet, he is best known as a member of the band Little Feat.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Fred_Tackett_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fred-tackett/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Hackett]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-hackett/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen Richard Hackett is an English musician, songwriter, singer, and producer who gained prominence as the lead guitarist of the progressive rock band Genesis from 1971 to 1977. Hackett contributed to six Genesis studio albums, three live albums, seven singles and one EP before he left to pursue a solo career. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of Genesis in 2010.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c3/Steve_Hackett.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-hackett/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Carlos Santana]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/carlos-santana/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Carlos Santana audio (help·info) is a Mexican and American guitarist who rose to fame in the late 1960s and early 1970s with his band Santana, which pioneered a fusion of rock and roll and Latin American jazz. Its sound featured his melodic, blues-based lines set against Latin and African rhythms played on percussion instruments such as timbales and congas not generally heard in rock. Santana continued to work in these forms over the decades that followed. He experienced a resurgence of popularity and critical acclaim in the late 1990s. In 2015, Rolling Stone magazine listed Santana at number 20 on their list of the 100 Greatest Guitarists. He has won 10 Grammy Awards and three Latin Grammy Awards, and was inducted along with Santana into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/93/Carlos_Santana_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/carlos-santana/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>