<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Merchandise » Guitar</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Merchandise » Guitar</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 23:27:10 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Guitar Tuning Cheat Shirt Eddie Ate Dynamite Good Bye Eddie - Black Design]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/eddie-ate-dynamite-good-bye-eddie-180-black/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>The funny saying on this shirt is a mnemonic for the 6 guitar strings in standard tuning: EADGBE. Wear it and every time you glance down at it you will be reminded of the notes of the open strings. / This cheat shirt for guitarists shows &#8220;EDDIE ATE DYNAMITE GOOD BYE EDDIE&#8221; in a vertical layout over the 6 strings and the numbers used to refer to the strings. The design is rotated by 180 degree to help the guitar player wearing it. • Also buy this artwork on apparel.</p><img src="/img/preview/eddie-ate-dynamite-good-bye-eddie-180-black.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/eddie-ate-dynamite-good-bye-eddie-180-black/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Guitare Tuning Cheat Shirt Eddie Ate Dynamite Au revoir Eddie - Blanc Design]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/eddie-ate-dynamite-good-bye-eddie-180-white/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Le dicton drôle sur cette chemise est un moyen mnémotechnique pour les 6 cordes de guitare en accordage standard: EADGBE. Portez-le et chaque fois que vous y jetez un coup d&#39;œil, vous vous rappellerez les notes des cordes ouvertes. Cette chemise de triche pour les guitaristes montre &quot;EDDIE ATE DYNAMITE BON BYE EDDIE&quot; dans une disposition verticale sur les 6 cordes et les numéros utilisés pour se référer aux cordes. Le design est tourné de 180 degrés pour aider le guitariste à le porter. • Also buy this artwork on apparel.</p><img src="/img/preview/eddie-ate-dynamite-good-bye-eddie-180-white.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/eddie-ate-dynamite-good-bye-eddie-180-white/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Guitar Tuning Design Eddie Ate Dynamite Good Bye Eddie - White Graphic]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/eddie-ate-dynamite-good-bye-eddie-white/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>The funny saying on this design is a mnemonic for the 6 guitar strings in standard tuning: EADGBE. Wear it to help you and your guitar playing friends to remember the notes of the open strings more easily. / This design for guitarists shows &#8220;EDDIE ATE DYNAMITE GOOD BYE EDDIE&#8221; in a vertical layout over the 6 strings. At the top are the numbers used to refer to the strings. • Also buy this artwork on apparel, phone cases, home decor, and more.</p><img src="/img/preview/eddie-ate-dynamite-good-bye-eddie-white.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/eddie-ate-dynamite-good-bye-eddie-white/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Guitar Tuning Design Eddie Ate Dynamite Good Bye Eddie - Black Graphic]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/eddie-ate-dynamite-good-bye-eddie-black/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>The funny saying on this design is a mnemonic for the 6 guitar strings in standard tuning: EADGBE. Wear it to help you and your guitar playing friends to remember the notes of the open strings more easily. / This design for guitarists shows &#8220;EDDIE ATE DYNAMITE GOOD BYE EDDIE&#8221; in a vertical layout over the 6 strings. At the top are the numbers used to refer to the strings. • Also buy this artwork on apparel, stickers, phone cases, and more.</p><img src="/img/preview/eddie-ate-dynamite-good-bye-eddie-black.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/eddie-ate-dynamite-good-bye-eddie-black/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Choose Your Axe The Weapon of Guitarists - White Design]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/choose-your-axe-white/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Heavy metal and hard rock musicians love them, guitars that look like axes. Like the ones you see on this design that asks to choose your axe. / Is music your weapon of choice and do you love to rock out heavy on your axe? Then this is the right design to get on a t-shirt, hoodie or other product. It also makes for a rocking birthday or Christmas gift for guitar players. • Also buy this artwork on apparel, phone cases, home decor, and more.</p><img src="/img/preview/choose-your-axe-white.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/choose-your-axe-white/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Elige tu hacha The Weapon of Guitarists - Black Design]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/choose-your-axe-black/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>A los músicos de heavy metal y hard rock les encantan, guitarras que parecen hachas. Al igual que los que ves en este diseño que pide elegir tu hacha. ¿La música es tu arma favorita y te encanta pescar sobre tu hacha? Entonces este es el diseño correcto para ponerse una camiseta, sudadera con capucha u otro producto. También se convierte en un cumpleaños conmovedor o regalo de Navidad para guitarristas. • Also buy this artwork on apparel, stickers, phone cases y more.</p><img src="/img/preview/choose-your-axe-black.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/choose-your-axe-black/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Choose Wisely Design for Electric Guitar Players]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/choose-wisely-guitars/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>No matter whether you prefer black, dark red, blue, orange or golden wood as long as you choose to play the guitar everything is okay. A design for guitarists who love to rock out on the electric guitar and know they made the right choice with this awesome instrument. • Also buy this artwork on apparel, phone cases, home decor, and more.</p><img src="/img/preview/choose-wisely-guitars.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/choose-wisely-guitars/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gitarren Pick &amp; Headstock - Rot / Gelb Design für Gitarristen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/guitar-pick-headstock/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dieses Design besteht aus einem gelben Plektrum, das von einem roten Rand mit einem schwarzen Umriss und einem roten Kopfstock in der Mitte der Auswahl umgeben ist. Es ist für Gitarristen, die ihr Lieblingsinstrument so sehr lieben, dass sie es der Welt zeigen wollen. • Also buy this artwork on apparel, stickers, phone cases und more.</p><img src="/img/preview/guitar-pick-headstock.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/guitar-pick-headstock/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Acoustic Guitar T-Shirt - Brown/Golden Wood Guitarist Design]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/acoustic-guitar-clipped/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>A cool design for guitarists who not only love to play their favorite instrument but also want to show it on a t-shirt, hoodie or other product. A great idea for a birthday or Christmas gift. / The design consists of a clipped acoustic guitar showing part of the corpus and neck in brownish/golden colors. Keep on strumming! • Also buy this artwork on apparel, phone cases, home decor, and more.</p><img src="/img/preview/acoustic-guitar-clipped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/acoustic-guitar-clipped/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[T-shirt de guitare acoustique - conception fraîche de guitariste en niveaux de gris]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/acoustic-guitar-clipped-grayscale/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Un design cool pour les guitaristes qui non seulement adorent jouer leur instrument préféré mais veulent aussi le montrer sur un t-shirt, un sweat à capuche ou un autre produit. Une excellente idée pour un cadeau d&#39;anniversaire ou de Noël. La conception consiste en une guitare acoustique taillée montrant une partie du corpus et du manche dans différentes nuances de gris. Continuez à gratter! • Also buy this artwork on apparel, phone cases, home decor et more.</p><img src="/img/preview/acoustic-guitar-clipped-grayscale.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/acoustic-guitar-clipped-grayscale/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>