<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » American Academy Of Arts And Sciences</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » American Academy Of Arts And Sciences</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 20:58:33 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Judy Collins]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/judy-collins/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Judith Marjorie Collins is a Grammy Award-winning American singer and songwriter with a career spanning over 60 years. She is known for her eclectic tastes in the material she records for her social activism, and for the clarity of her voice. Collins has released 28 studio albums, 4 live albums, numerous compilation albums and 4 holiday albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/57/Judy_Collins_by_Bryan_Ledgard_2_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/judy-collins/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joan Baez]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joan-baez/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joan Chandos Baez is an American singer, songwriter, musician, and activist. Her contemporary folk music often includes songs of protest and social justice. Baez has performed publicly for over 60 years, releasing over 30 albums. Fluent in Spanish and English, she has also recorded songs in at least six other languages.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2f/Joan_baez01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joan-baez/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bono]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bono/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul David Hewson, known by his stage name Bono, is an Irish singer-songwriter, activist, philanthropist, venture capitalist, businessman, and actor. He is best known as the lead vocalist and primary lyricist of rock band U2.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/dd/Bono_U2_360_Tour_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bono/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robbie Robertson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-robertson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jaime Royal 'Robbie' Robertson, OC, is a Canadian musician, songwriter, film composer, producer, actor, and author. Robertson is best known for his work as lead guitarist and songwriter for The Band, and for his career as a solo recording artist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2e/RobbieRobertson2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-robertson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Emmylou Harris]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emmylou-harris/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Emmylou Harris is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. She has released dozens of albums and singles over the course of her career and has won 14 Grammys, the Polar Music Prize, and numerous other honors, including induction into the Country Music Hall of Fame. In 2018, she was presented the Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/55/Emmylou_Harris_with_guitar.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emmylou-harris/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[B. B. King]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/b.b.-king/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Riley B. King, known professionally as B.B. King, was an American blues singer-songwriter, guitarist, and record producer. He introduced a sophisticated style of soloing based on fluid string bending, shimmering vibrato and staccato picking that influenced many later blues electric guitar players. AllMusic recognized King as 'the single most important electric guitarist of the last half of the 20th century'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2b/B.B._King%2C_2006-06-26.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/b.b.-king/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bob Dylan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-dylan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bob Dylan is an American singer-songwriter, author and visual artist. Often regarded as one of the greatest songwriters of all time, Dylan has been a major figure in popular culture during a career spanning nearly 60 years. Much of his most celebrated work dates from the 1960s, when songs such as 'Blowin' in the Wind' (1963) and 'The Times They Are a-Changin'' (1964) became anthems for the civil rights and anti-war movements. His lyrics during this period incorporated a range of political, social, philosophical, and literary influences, defying pop music conventions and appealing to the burgeoning counterculture.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/28/Joan_Baez_Bob_Dylan_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-dylan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruce Springsteen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bruce-springsteen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bruce Frederick Joseph Springsteen is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. He has released twenty studio albums, many of which feature his backing band, the E Street Band. Originally from the Jersey Shore, he is one of the originators of the heartland rock style of music, combining mainstream rock musical style with narrative songs about working class American life. During a career that has spanned five decades, Springsteen has become known for his poetic, socially conscious lyrics and energetic stage performances, sometimes lasting up to four hours in length. He has been nicknamed 'The Boss'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d7/Bruce_Springsteen_Oslo_2019_193031.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bruce-springsteen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:38 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>