<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » American Academy Of Arts And Sciences</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » American Academy Of Arts And Sciences</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:46:53 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[B. B. King]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/b.b.-king/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Riley B. King, known professionally as B.B. King, was an American singer-songwriter, guitarist, and record producer. King introduced a sophisticated style of soloing based on fluid string bending and shimmering vibrato that influenced many later electric blues guitarists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2b/B.B._King%2C_2006-06-26.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/b.b.-king/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Judy Collins]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/judy-collins/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Judith Marjorie Collins is an American singer and songwriter known for her eclectic tastes in the material she records and for her social activism.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/57/Judy_Collins_by_Bryan_Ledgard_2_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/judy-collins/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruce Springsteen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bruce-springsteen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bruce Frederick Joseph Springsteen is an American singer, songwriter, and musician who is both a solo artist and the leader of the E Street Band. He received critical acclaim for his early 1970s albums and attained worldwide fame upon the release of Born to Run in 1975. During a career that has spanned five decades, Springsteen has become known for his poetic and socially conscious lyrics and lengthy, energetic stage performances, earning the nickname 'The Boss'. He has recorded both rock albums and folk-oriented works, and his lyrics often address the experiences and struggles of working-class Americans.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d7/Bruce_Springsteen_Oslo_2019_193031.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bruce-springsteen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Emmylou Harris]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emmylou-harris/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Emmylou Harris is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. She has released dozens of albums and singles over the course of her career and won 14 Grammys, the Polar Music Prize, and numerous other honors, including induction into the Country Music Hall of Fame. In 2018 she was presented the Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/55/Emmylou_Harris_with_guitar.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emmylou-harris/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bono]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bono/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul David Hewson, KBE OL, known by his stage name Bono, is an Irish singer-songwriter, musician, venture capitalist, businessman, and philanthropist. He is best known as the lead vocalist and primary lyricist of rock band U2.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/dd/Bono_U2_360_Tour_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bono/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bob Dylan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-dylan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bob Dylan is an American singer-songwriter, author, and visual artist who has been a major figure in popular culture for more than fifty years. Much of his most celebrated work dates from the 1960s, when songs such as 'Blowin' in the Wind' (1963) and 'The Times They Are a-Changin'' (1964) became anthems for the civil rights movement and anti-war movement. His lyrics during this period incorporated a wide range of political, social, philosophical, and literary influences, defied pop-music conventions and appealed to the burgeoning counterculture.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/28/Joan_Baez_Bob_Dylan_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-dylan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>