<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » American Academy Of Arts And Sciences</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » American Academy Of Arts And Sciences</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 15:23:51 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Judy Collins]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/judy-collins/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Judith Marjorie Collins is a Grammy Award-winning American singer and songwriter with a career spanning over 60 years. She is known for her eclectic tastes in the material she records and for her social activism. Collins has released 28 studio albums, 4 live albums, numerous compilation albums and 4 holiday albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/57/Judy_Collins_by_Bryan_Ledgard_2_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/judy-collins/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruce Springsteen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bruce-springsteen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bruce Frederick Joseph Springsteen is an American singer, songwriter, and musician who is both a solo artist and the leader of the E Street Band. Originally from the Jersey Shore, he received critical acclaim for his early 1970s albums and attained worldwide fame upon the release of Born to Run in 1975. During a career that has spanned five decades, Springsteen has become known for his poetic, socially conscious lyrics and energetic stage performances, sometimes lasting up to four hours in length. He has been given the nickname 'The Boss'. He has recorded both rock albums and folk-oriented works, and his lyrics often address the experiences and struggles of working-class Americans.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d7/Bruce_Springsteen_Oslo_2019_193031.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bruce-springsteen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Emmylou Harris]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emmylou-harris/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Emmylou Harris is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. She has released dozens of albums and singles over the course of her career and has won 14 Grammys, the Polar Music Prize, and numerous other honors, including induction into the Country Music Hall of Fame. In 2018 she was presented the Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/55/Emmylou_Harris_with_guitar.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emmylou-harris/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joan Baez]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joan-baez/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joan Chandos Baez is an American singer, songwriter, musician and activist. Her contemporary folk music often includes songs of protest or social justice. Baez has performed publicly for over 60 years, releasing over 30 albums. Fluent in Spanish and English, she has also recorded songs in at least six other languages.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a2/Joan_Baez_1966.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joan-baez/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bono]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bono/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul David Hewson, known by his stage name Bono, is an Irish singer, songwriter, philanthropist, activist, venture capitalist, businessman, and actor. He is best known as the lead vocalist and primary lyricist of rock band U2.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/dd/Bono_U2_360_Tour_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bono/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bob Dylan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-dylan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bob Dylan is an American singer-songwriter, author and visual artist. Widely regarded as one of the greatest songwriters of all time, Dylan has been a major figure in popular culture for more than 50 years. Much of his most celebrated work dates from the 1960s, when songs such as 'Blowin' in the Wind' (1963) and 'The Times They Are a-Changin'' (1964) became anthems for the civil rights and anti-war movements. His lyrics during this period incorporated a range of political, social, philosophical, and literary influences, defied pop music conventions and appealed to the burgeoning counterculture.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/28/Joan_Baez_Bob_Dylan_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-dylan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>