<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Country Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Country Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 01:03:45 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Willie Nelson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Willie Hugh Nelson is an American musician, actor, and activist. The critical success of the album Shotgun Willie (1973), combined with the critical and commercial success of Red Headed Stranger (1975) and Stardust (1978), made Nelson one of the most recognized artists in country music. He was one of the main figures of outlaw country, a subgenre of country music that developed in the late 1960s as a reaction to the conservative restrictions of the Nashville sound. Nelson has acted in over 30 films, co-authored several books, and has been involved in activism for the use of biofuels and the legalization of marijuana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/WillieNelson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Elvis Presley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elvis-presley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Elvis Aaron Presley, also known mononymously as Elvis, was an American singer and actor. Regarded as one of the most significant cultural icons of the 20th century, he is often referred to as the 'King of Rock and Roll' or simply 'the King'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2d/PresleyPromo1954PhotoOnly.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elvis-presley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Garth Brooks]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/garth-brooks/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Troyal Garth Brooks is an American singer and songwriter. His integration of rock and pop elements into the country genre has earned him immense popularity in the United States. Brooks has had great success on the country single and album charts, with multi-platinum recordings and record-breaking live performances, while also crossing over into the mainstream pop arena.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Garth_Brooks_2019_By_Glenn_Francis.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/garth-brooks/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jason Ringenberg]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-ringenberg/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jason Ringenberg is an American musician, singer-songwriter and guitarist and the lead singer of Jason & the Scorchers.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Jason_Ringenberg_2015_by_Brian_Mansfield.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-ringenberg/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Earle]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-earle/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen Fain Earle is an American rock, country and folk singer-songwriter, record producer, author and actor. Earle began his career as a songwriter in Nashville and released his first EP in 1982.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a2/Steve_Earle_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-earle/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Crosby]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-crosby/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Van Cortlandt Crosby is an American singer-songwriter and musician. In addition to his solo career, he was a founding member of both the Byrds and Crosby, Stills & Nash.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bc/David_Crosby_2019_by_Glenn_Francis.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-crosby/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Dawson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-dawson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Collins Dawson IV, nicknamed 'Marmaduke', was an American musician, singer, and songwriter. He was best known as the leader and co-founder of the country rock band the New Riders of the Purple Sage. He sang lead vocals on most of the band’s songs.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ad/197311290000_John_Dawson_NRPS_R1_05.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-dawson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Neil Young]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Neil Percival Young is a Canadian singer-songwriter. After embarking on a music career in the 1960s, he moved to Los Angeles, where he formed Buffalo Springfield with Stephen Stills, Richie Furay and others. Young had released two solo albums and three as a member of Buffalo Springfield by the time he joined Crosby, Stills & Nash in 1969. From his early solo albums and those with his backing band Crazy Horse, Young has recorded a steady stream of studio and live albums, sometimes warring with his recording company along the way.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bb/Neil_Young_-_Per_Ole_Hagen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Clarence White]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/clarence-white/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Clarence White, was an American bluegrass and country guitarist and singer. He is best known as a member of the bluegrass ensemble the Kentucky Colonels and the rock band the Byrds, as well as for being a pioneer of the musical genre of country rock during the late 1960s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/90/The_Byrds_%281970%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/clarence-white/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Damon Johnson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/damon-johnson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Damon Rogers Johnson is an American guitarist, vocalist, and songwriter, currently a solo artist and member of Thin Lizzy. In the 1990s he co-founded Brother Cane, and later joined Alice Cooper's band as lead guitarist. He was also the lead guitarist and co-songwriter for hard rock group Black Star Riders from 2012 to 2018. Johnson has also released several solo albums and his songs have been recorded by many artists including Stevie Nicks and Carlos Santana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2f/Black_Star_Riders_%288_von_28%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/damon-johnson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>