<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Traditional Heavy Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Traditional Heavy Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:52:56 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Satriani]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-satriani/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Satriani is an American musician, composer, songwriter, and guitar teacher. Early in his career, Satriani worked as a guitar instructor, with many of his former students achieving fame, such as Steve Vai, Larry LaLonde, Rick Hunolt, Kirk Hammett, Andy Timmons, Charlie Hunter, Kevin Cadogan, and Alex Skolnick; he then went on to have a successful solo music career. He is a 15-time Grammy Award nominee and has sold over 10 million albums, making him the biggest-selling instrumental rock guitarist of all time.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/24/Satriani_2010_13_12_1112.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-satriani/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bruce Kulick]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bruce-kulick/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bruce Howard Kulick is an American guitarist, musician and since 2000 a member of the band Grand Funk Railroad. Previously, Kulick was a long-time member of the band Kiss (1984–1996). He was also a member of Union with John Corabi from 1997–2002 and Blackjack from 1979–1980.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/17/BruceKulickGFR2002.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bruce-kulick/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Myles Kennedy]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/myles-kennedy/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Myles Richard Bass, known professionally as Myles Kennedy, is an American musician, singer, and songwriter, best known as the lead vocalist and rhythm guitarist of the rock band Alter Bridge, and as the lead vocalist in guitarist Slash's backing band, known as Myles Kennedy and the Conspirators. A former guitar instructor from Spokane, Washington, he has worked as a session musician and songwriter, making both studio and live appearances with several artists, and has been involved with several projects throughout his career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/88/20170615-079-Nova_Rock_2017-Alter_Bridge-Myles_Kennedy_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/myles-kennedy/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>