<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Traditional Heavy Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Traditional Heavy Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:27:46 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gary Moore]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gary-moore/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert William Gary Moore was a Northern Irish guitarist and singer-songwriter. According to Ultimate Classic Rock, Moore had a 'restless career trajectory—taking in blues, rock, heavy metal, jazz-fusion and other styles over four and a half decades'. He is often described as a virtuoso guitarist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e4/Gary-Moore-at-Pite-Havsbad.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gary-moore/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Harris]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-harris/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen Percy Harris is an English musician, songwriter, bassist, occasional keyboardist, backing vocalist, primary songwriter and founder of the British heavy metal band Iron Maiden. He has been the band's only constant member since their inception in 1975 and one of only two to have appeared on all of their albums, the other being guitarist Dave Murray.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d9/Steve_Harris_Costa_Rica.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-harris/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jason Newsted]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-newsted/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jason Curtis Newsted is an American metal musician, known for being the bassist of the band Metallica from October 1986 until his sudden departure in January 2001.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/68/13-06-09_RaR_Newsted_10.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-newsted/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Malcolm Young]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/malcolm-young/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Malcolm Mitchell Young was an Australian musician and songwriter, best known as a co-founder, rhythm guitarist, backing vocalist and songwriter for the hard rock band AC/DC. Except for a brief absence in 1988, he was with the band from its November 1973 beginning until retiring in 2014 due to health reasons. Young and the other members of AC/DC were inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 2003.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7a/Malcolm_Young_en_2010.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/malcolm-young/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Eddie Van Halen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eddie-van-halen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Edward Lodewijk Van Halen is a Dutch-American musician, songwriter, and producer. He is the main songwriter and founder—with brother and drummer Alex Van Halen, bassist Mark Stone, and singer David Lee Roth—of the American hard rock band Van Halen. In 2012, he was voted number one in a Guitar World magazine reader's poll for 'The 100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a7/Eddie_Van_Halen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eddie-van-halen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Perry]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-perry/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Anthony Joseph Pereira, better known by his stage name, Joe Perry, is an American musician, singer and songwriter who is best known as the lead guitarist and founding member of the American rock band Aerosmith. Sometimes referred to as the 'Greatest American Rock Band of All-Time' and the 'Bad Boys from Boston'. Aerosmith has sold over 150 million albums worldwide and 70 million in the U.S. alone, making them one of the biggest selling artists of all-time.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7c/HollywoodVampsSSe200618-151_%2843604265504%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-perry/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Olve Eikemo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/olve-eikemo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Olve Eikemo, better known by his stage name Abbath Doom Occulta or simply Abbath, is a Norwegian musician best known as a founding member of the black metal band Immortal. Before founding Immortal, Abbath performed with Old Funeral alongside future Immortal member Demonaz. While working with Old Funeral, he also joined Demonaz's band Amputation which later became Immortal. He also plays bass in Demonaz's eponymous project.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/AbbathWOA2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/olve-eikemo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brad Delson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brad-delson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bradford Phillip Delson is an American musician and record producer, best known as the lead guitarist and one of the founding members of the American rock band Linkin Park.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/17/Brad_Delson_playing_at_Smirnoff_Music_Centre.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brad-delson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[James Hetfield]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-hetfield/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Alan Hetfield is an American musician and songwriter best known for being the co-founder, lead vocalist/rhythm guitarist and main songwriter for the American heavy metal band Metallica. Hetfield is mainly known for his intricate rhythm playing, but occasionally performs lead guitar duties and solos, both live and in the studio. Hetfield co-founded Metallica in October 1981 after answering an advertisement by drummer Lars Ulrich in the Los Angeles newspaper The Recycler. Metallica has won nine Grammy Awards and released ten studio albums, three live albums, four extended plays and 24 singles.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fd/JamesHetfield2012.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-hetfield/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>