<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Country Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Country Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 23:54:38 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Will Oldham]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bonnie-"prince"-billy/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William 'Will' Oldham, better known by the stage name Bonnie 'Prince' Billy, is an American singer-songwriter and actor. From 1993 to 1997, he performed and recorded under variations of the Palace name, including Palace Brothers, Palace Songs, and Palace Music. After releasing material under his own name, he adopted the Bonnie 'Prince' Billy name for the majority of his output since 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/67/BonniePrinceBilly3_gobeirne.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bonnie-"prince"-billy/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Willie Nelson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Willie Hugh Nelson is an American musician, actor, and activist. The critical success of the album Shotgun Willie (1973), combined with the critical and commercial success of Red Headed Stranger (1975) and Stardust (1978), made Nelson one of the most recognized artists in country music. He was one of the main figures of outlaw country, a subgenre of country music that developed in the late 1960s as a reaction to the conservative restrictions of the Nashville sound. Nelson has acted in over 30 films, co-authored several books, and has been involved in activism for the use of biofuels and the legalization of marijuana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/WillieNelson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Linda Ronstadt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/linda-ronstadt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Linda Maria Ronstadt is a retired American popular music singer known for singing in a wide range of genres including rock, country, light opera, and Latin. She has earned 10 Grammy Awards, three American Music Awards, two Academy of Country Music awards, an Emmy Award, and an ALMA Award, and many of her albums have been certified gold, platinum or multiplatinum in the United States and internationally. She has also earned nominations for a Tony Award and a Golden Globe award. She was awarded the Latin Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award by The Latin Recording Academy in 2011 and also awarded the Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award by The Recording Academy in 2016. She was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in April 2014. On July 28, 2014, she was awarded the National Medal of Arts and Humanities. In 2019, she will receive a joint star with Dolly Parton and Emmylou Harris on the Hollywood Walk of Fame for their work as the group Trio.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/50/LindaRonstadtPerforming.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/linda-ronstadt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Merle Haggard]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/merle-haggard/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Merle Ronald Haggard was an American country singer, songwriter, guitarist, and fiddler.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/34/MerleHaggardJun09.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/merle-haggard/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Grand]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-grand/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steve Grand is an American singer, songwriter and model from Lemont, Illinois, a Chicago suburb. He became an overnight internet celebrity and the music video of his first hit 'All-American Boy' went viral on YouTube in less than a week in July 2013. This attention landed Grand on Good Morning America, CNN and other national media. In addition to being a musician, Grand has become an active figure in the LGBT equality movement. He released his debut album titled All American Boy financed by a successful Kickstarter public funding campaign. The follow-up album Not the End of Me was released in 2018.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/36/Steve_Grand_-_1032013.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-grand/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Blake Shelton]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/blake-shelton/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Blake Tollison Shelton is an American country singer and television personality. In 2001, he made his debut with the single 'Austin'. The lead-off single from his self-titled debut album, 'Austin' spent five weeks at number one on the Billboard Hot Country Songs chart. The now Platinum-certified debut album also produced two more top 20 entries.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/02/BlakeSheltonApr10.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/blake-shelton/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hank Williams III]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hank-williams-iii/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shelton Hank Williams, known as Hank Williams III and Hank 3, is an American musician, singer and multi-instrumentalist, known for his alternating musical style, between country, punk rock and heavy metal. He is the principal member of the punk metal band Assjack, the drummer for the Southern hardcore punk band Arson Anthem, and was the bassist for Pantera singer Phil Anselmo's band Superjoint Ritual. He has released eleven studio albums, including five for Curb Records. Williams is the grandson of Hank Williams, the son of Hank Williams Jr., the nephew of Jett Williams, and the half-brother of Holly Williams.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c9/Hank_Williams_III_SXSW_2006_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hank-williams-iii/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roy Clark]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-clark/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roy Linwood Clark was an American singer and musician. He is best known for having hosted Hee Haw, a nationally televised country variety show, from 1969 to 1997. Clark was an important and influential figure in country music, both as a performer and in helping to popularize the genre.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/95/WIKI_ROY_CLARK.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-clark/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Carl Perkins]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/carl-perkins/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Carl Lee Perkins was an American singer-songwriter who recorded most notably at the Sun Studio, in Memphis, beginning in 1954. Amongst his best-known songs are 'Blue Suede Shoes', 'Matchbox' and 'Everybody's Trying to Be My Baby'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/79/Cavenaugh_Park_Walnut_Ridge_AR_2013-04-27_013.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/carl-perkins/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[k.d. lang]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/k.d.-lang/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kathryn Dawn Lang, known by her stylized stage name k.d. lang, is a Canadian pop and country singer-songwriter and occasional actress.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/76/Kd_lang_-_AIS_Arena%2C_Canberra_-_7_Nov_11%283%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/k.d.-lang/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>