<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Country Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Country Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 11:07:50 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Willie Nelson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Willie Hugh Nelson is an American musician, actor, and activist. The critical success of the album Shotgun Willie (1973), combined with the critical and commercial success of Red Headed Stranger (1975) and Stardust (1978), made Nelson one of the most recognized artists in country music. He was one of the main figures of outlaw country, a subgenre of country music that developed in the late 1960s as a reaction to the conservative restrictions of the Nashville sound. Nelson has acted in over 30 films, co-authored several books, and has been involved in activism for the use of biofuels and the legalization of marijuana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/WillieNelson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Linda Ronstadt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/linda-ronstadt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Linda Maria Ronstadt is a retired American singer who performed and recorded in diverse genres including rock, country, light opera, and Latin. She has earned 10 Grammy Awards, three American Music Awards, two Academy of Country Music awards, an Emmy Award, and an ALMA Award. Many of her albums have been certified gold, platinum or multiplatinum in the United States and internationally. She has also earned nominations for a Tony Award and a Golden Globe award. She was awarded the Latin Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award by the Latin Recording Academy in 2011 and also awarded the Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award by the Recording Academy in 2016. She was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in April 2014. On July 28, 2014, she was awarded the National Medal of Arts and Humanities. In 2019, she received a star jointly with Dolly Parton and Emmylou Harris on the Hollywood Walk of Fame for their work as the group Trio. Ronstadt was among five honorees who received the 2019 Kennedy Center Honors for lifetime artistic achievements.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/50/LindaRonstadtPerforming.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/linda-ronstadt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Merle Haggard]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/merle-haggard/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Merle Ronald Haggard was an American country singer, songwriter, guitarist, and fiddler.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/34/MerleHaggardJun09.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/merle-haggard/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Blake Shelton]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/blake-shelton/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Blake Tollison Shelton is an American country music singer and television personality. In 2001, he made his debut with the single 'Austin'. The lead-off single from his self-titled debut album, 'Austin' spent five weeks at number one on the Billboard Hot Country Songs chart. The now Platinum-certified debut album also produced two more top 20 entries.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a2/Blake_Shelton_July_2017_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/blake-shelton/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hank Williams III]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hank-williams-iii/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shelton Hank Williams known as Hank Williams III and Hank 3, is an American musician, singer and multi-instrumentalist, known for his alternating musical style, between country, punk rock, and heavy metal. He is the principal member of the punk metal band Assjack, the drummer of hardcore punk band Arson Anthem, and former bassist of Phil Anselmo's band Superjoint Ritual. He has released eleven studio albums, including five for Curb Records. Williams is the grandson of Hank Williams, the son of Hank Williams Jr., the nephew of Jett Williams, and the half-brother of Holly Williams.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c9/Hank_Williams_III_SXSW_2006_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hank-williams-iii/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roy Clark]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-clark/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/72/Roy_Clark_a_conversation_with_OETA_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-clark/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[k.d. lang]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/k.d.-lang/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kathryn Dawn Lang, known by her stylized stage name k.d. lang, is a Canadian pop and country singer-songwriter and occasional actress. Lang has won Juno Awards and Grammy Awards for her musical performances. Hits include the songs 'Constant Craving' and 'Miss Chatelaine'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/88/Pop_Conference_2016_-_Keynote_-_29_-_k.d._lang.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/k.d.-lang/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sheryl Crow]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sheryl-crow/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sheryl Suzanne Crow is an American musician, singer, songwriter, and actress. Her music incorporates elements of pop, rock, country, jazz, and blues. She has released ten studio albums, four compilations, two live albums, and has contributed to a number of film soundtracks. Her most popular songs include 'All I Wanna Do' (1994), 'Strong Enough' (1994), 'If It Makes You Happy' (1996), 'Everyday Is a Winding Road' (1996), 'Tomorrow Never Dies' (1997), 'My Favorite Mistake' (1998), 'Picture' (2002) and 'Soak Up the Sun' (2002). She has sold more than 50 million albums worldwide. Crow has garnered nine Grammy Awards from the National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/dc/Sheryl_Crow.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sheryl-crow/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Suzy Bogguss]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/suzy-bogguss/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/85/SuzyBogguss_wiki.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/suzy-bogguss/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stephen Stills]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stephen-stills/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen Arthur Stills is an American singer, songwriter, and multi-instrumentalist best known for his work with Buffalo Springfield and Crosby, Stills, Nash & Young. As both a solo act and member of two successful bands, Stills has combined record sales of over 35 million albums. He was ranked number 28 in Rolling Stone's 2003 list of 'The 100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time' and number 47 in the 2011 list. Stills became the first person to be inducted twice on the same night into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame. According to Neil Young, 'Stephen is a genius.'</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/27/Stephen_Stills_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stephen-stills/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>