<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Country Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Country Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:52:56 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Willie Nelson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Willie Hugh Nelson is an American musician, actor, and activist. The critical success of the album Shotgun Willie (1973), combined with the critical and commercial success of Red Headed Stranger (1975) and Stardust (1978), made Nelson one of the most recognized artists in country music. He was one of the main figures of outlaw country, a subgenre of country music that developed in the late 1960s as a reaction to the conservative restrictions of the Nashville sound. Nelson has acted in over 30 films, co-authored several books, and has been involved in activism for the use of biofuels and the legalization of marijuana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/WillieNelson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Linda Ronstadt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/linda-ronstadt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Linda Maria Ronstadt is a retired American popular music singer known for singing in a wide range of genres including rock, country, light opera, and Latin. She has earned 10 Grammy Awards, three American Music Awards, two Academy of Country Music awards, an Emmy Award, and an ALMA Award, and many of her albums have been certified gold, platinum or multiplatinum in the United States and internationally. She has also earned nominations for a Tony Award and a Golden Globe award. She was awarded the Latin Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award by The Latin Recording Academy in 2011 and also awarded the Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award by The Recording Academy in 2016. She was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in April 2014. On July 28, 2014, she was awarded the National Medal of Arts and Humanities. In 2019, she will receive a joint star with Dolly Parton and Emmylou Harris on the Hollywood Walk of Fame for their work as the group Trio.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/50/LindaRonstadtPerforming.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/linda-ronstadt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Grand]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-grand/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steve Grand is an American singer, songwriter and model from Lemont, Illinois, a Chicago suburb. He became an overnight internet celebrity and the music video of his first hit 'All-American Boy' went viral on YouTube in less than a week in July 2013. This attention landed Grand on Good Morning America, CNN and other national media. In addition to being a musician, Grand has become an active figure in the LGBT equality movement. He released his debut album titled All American Boy financed by a successful Kickstarter public funding campaign. The follow-up album Not the End of Me was released in 2018.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/36/Steve_Grand_-_1032013.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-grand/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sheryl Crow]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sheryl-crow/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sheryl Suzanne Crow is an American musician, singer, songwriter, and actress. Her music incorporates elements of pop, rock, country, jazz, and blues. She has released ten studio albums, four compilations, two live albums, and has contributed to a number of film soundtracks. Her songs include 'All I Wanna Do', 'If It Makes You Happy', 'My Favorite Mistake' and the theme song for the 1997 James Bond film Tomorrow Never Dies. She has sold more than 50 million albums worldwide. Crow has garnered nine Grammy Awards from the National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/dc/Sheryl_Crow.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sheryl-crow/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steven Seagal]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steven-seagal/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steven Frederic Seagal is an American actor, producer, screenwriter, martial artist, and musician who holds American, Serbian, and Russian citizenship.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d9/Steven_Seagal_November_2016.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steven-seagal/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sammy Kershaw]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sammy-kershaw/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Samuel Paul Kershaw is an American country music artist. He has released 16 studio albums, with three RIAA platinum certifications and two gold certifications among them. More than 25 singles have entered Top 40 on the Billboard Hot Country Songs charts, including the number one hit 'She Don't Know She's Beautiful' and 10 more Top 10 hits: 'Cadillac Style', 'Anywhere but Here', 'Haunted Heart', 'Queen of My Double-Wide Trailer', 'I Can't Reach Her Anymore', 'National Working Woman's Holiday', 'Third Rate Romance', 'Meant to Be', 'Vidalia', and 'Love of My Life'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/02/Sammy_Kershaw_at_Renfro_Valley_Ky.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sammy-kershaw/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Glenn Frey]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glenn-frey/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Glenn Lewis Frey was an American singer, songwriter, actor and founding member of the rock band the Eagles. Frey was the co-lead singer and frontman for the Eagles, roles he came to share with fellow member Don Henley, with whom he wrote most of the Eagles' material. Frey played guitar and keyboards as well as singing lead vocals on songs such as 'Take It Easy', 'Peaceful Easy Feeling', 'Tequila Sunrise', 'Already Gone', 'James Dean', 'Lyin' Eyes', 'New Kid in Town', and 'Heartache Tonight'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8a/Glenn_Frey.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glenn-frey/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brad Paisley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brad-paisley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brad Douglas Paisley is an American country music singer and songwriter. Starting with his 1999 debut album Who Needs Pictures, he has released eleven studio albums and a Christmas compilation on the Arista Nashville label, with all of his albums certified Gold or higher by the RIAA. He has scored 32 Top 10 singles on the US Billboard Country Airplay chart, 19 of which have reached number 1. He set a new record in 2009 for the most consecutive singles (10) reaching the top spot on that chart.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/89/Paisley%2C_Brad_%282007%29_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brad-paisley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Earle]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-earle/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen Fain Earle is an American rock, country and folk singer-songwriter, record producer, author and actor. Earle began his career as a songwriter in Nashville and released his first EP in 1982.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a2/Steve_Earle_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-earle/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Wariner]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-wariner/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steven Noel Wariner is an American country music singer, songwriter, and guitarist. Initially a backing musician for Dottie West, Bob Luman, and Chet Atkins, he began recording as a solo artist in the late 1970s. He has released eighteen studio albums for multiple labels, including the Nashville divisions of RCA, MCA, Arista, and Capitol Records, along with his own SelecTone label. He has also charted more than fifty singles on the Billboard Hot Country Songs charts, of which ten reached number one: 'All Roads Lead to You', 'Some Fools Never Learn', 'You Can Dream of Me', 'Life's Highway', 'Small Town Girl', 'The Weekend', 'Lynda', 'Where Did I Go Wrong', 'I Got Dreams', and 'What If I Said', a duet with Anita Cochran. Three of his studio albums have been certified gold by the Recording Industry Association of America for shipping 500,000 copies in the United States.</p>]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-wariner/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>