<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Country Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Country Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 22:51:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gary Louris]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gary-louris/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gary Louris is an American guitarist, singer, and songwriter of alternative country and pop music. He was a founding member of the Minneapolis-based band the Jayhawks and their principal songwriter and vocalist after the departure of Mark Olson. Louris is often credited with the band's subsequent move from folk-country toward a more progressive, pop sound.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/15/The_Jayhawks_2009.05.30_003.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gary-louris/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Eric Johnson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eric-johnson-(guitarist)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Eric Johnson is an American guitarist, vocalist, composer, and multi-instrumentalist. His 1990 album Ah Via Musicom was certified platinum by the RIAA, and the single 'Cliffs of Dover' won the Grammy Award for Best Rock Instrumental Performance.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ea/Eric_Johnson_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eric-johnson-(guitarist)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Martin Murphey]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-martin-murphey/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Martin Murphey is an American singer-songwriter best known for writing and performing Western music, country music and popular music. A multiple Grammy nominee, Murphey has six gold albums, including Cowboy Songs, the first album of cowboy music to achieve gold status since Gunfighter Ballads and Trail Songs by Marty Robbins in 1959. He has recorded the hit singles 'Wildfire', 'Carolina in the Pines', 'What's Forever For', 'A Long Line of Love', 'What She Wants', 'Don't Count the Rainy Days', and 'Maybe This Time'. Murphey is also the author of New Mexico's state ballad, 'The Land of Enchantment'. Murphey has become a prominent musical voice for the Western horseman, rancher, and cowboy.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Michael_Martin_Murphey_2012.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-martin-murphey/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Elisabeth Andreassen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elisabeth-andreassen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Elisabeth Gunilla Andreassen, also known as just Bettan, is a Norwegian-Swedish singer who has finished both first and second in the Eurovision Song Contest.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/80/Elisabeth_Andreassen_2010_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elisabeth-andreassen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Fogerty]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-fogerty/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Cameron Fogerty is an American musician, singer, and songwriter. Together with Doug Clifford, Stu Cook, and his brother Tom Fogerty, he founded the band Creedence Clearwater Revival (CCR), for which he was the lead singer, lead guitarist, and principal songwriter. The group had nine top-10 singles and eight gold albums between 1968 and 1972, and was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1993.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4a/John_Forgerty_in_2000.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-fogerty/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gillian Welch]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gillian-welch/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gillian Howard Welch is an American singer-songwriter. She performs with her musical partner, guitarist David Rawlings. Their sparse and dark musical style, which combines elements of Appalachian music, bluegrass, country and Americana, is described by The New Yorker as 'at once innovative and obliquely reminiscent of past rural forms.'</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0d/Gillian_Welch_at_MerleFest-2006-04-29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gillian-welch/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Luke Bryan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/luke-bryan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Luther 'Luke' Bryan is an American country music singer and songwriter. He began his music career writing songs for Travis Tritt and Billy Currington before signing with Capitol Nashville in 2007.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ad/LukeBryanApr10.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/luke-bryan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul Franklin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-franklin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul V. Franklin is an American multi-instrumentalist, known mainly for his work as a steel guitarist. He began his career in the 1970s as a member of Barbara Mandrell's road band; in addition he toured with Vince Gill, Mel Tillis, Jerry Reed and Dire Straits. He has since become a prolific session musician in Nashville, playing on more than 500 albums. He has been named by the Academy of Country Music as Best Steel Guitarist on several occasions. He was inducted into the Steel Guitar Hall of Fame in 2000 and the Musicians Hall of Fame and Museum in 2019. In addition to the pedal steel guitar and lap steel guitar, Franklin plays Dobro, fiddle, and drums, as well as three custom-built instruments called the Pedabro, The Box, and the baritone steel guitar.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5d/Paul_Franklin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-franklin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Malcolm Holcombe]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/malcolm-holcombe/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0a/Malcolm_Holcombe_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/malcolm-holcombe/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jimmie Rodgers]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jimmie-rodgers-(country-singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Charles Rodgers was an American singer-songwriter and musician who rose to popularity in the late 1920s. Widely regarded as 'the Father of Country Music', he is best known for his distinctive rhythmic yodeling. Unusual for a music star of his era, Rodgers rose to prominence based upon his recordings, among country music's earliest, rather than concert performances – which followed to similar public acclaim.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/58/Jimmie_Rodgers.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jimmie-rodgers-(country-singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>