<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Roots Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Roots Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 01:03:46 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Alvin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Albert Alvin is an American singer-songwriter, guitarist, music producer and poet. He is a former and founding member of the roots rock band the Blasters. Alvin has recorded and performed as a solo artist since the late 1980s and has been involved in various side projects and collaborations. He has had brief stints as a member of the bands X and the Knitters.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Dave_Alvin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bryan Adams]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bryan-adams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bryan Guy Adams is a Canadian singer, songwriter, record producer, guitarist, photographer, philanthropist and activist. He rose to fame in Canada and the United States with his 1983 album Cuts Like a Knife and turned into a global star with his 1984 album Reckless, which produced some of his best known songs, including 'Run to You', 'Summer of '69' and his first number one, 'Heaven'. In 1991, he released the album Waking Up the Neighbours, which included the song '(Everything I Do) I Do It for You'. The song became a worldwide hit and reached number 1 in many countries, including a new record of 16 consecutive weeks in the United Kingdom. Adams also had the U.S. Billboard Hot 100 number-one singles 'All for Love' and 'Have You Ever Really Loved a Woman?'</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7e/Bryan_Adams_Hamburg_MG_0631_flickr.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bryan-adams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>