<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » X Japan</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » X Japan</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 01:13:48 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Toshi]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/toshi/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Toshimitsu Deyama , known exclusively by his stage name Toshi, is a Japanese singer and songwriter. He is best known as the lead vocalist and a co-founder of the rock band X Japan, who rose to prominence in the late 1980s and early 1990s and are credited as founders of the Japanese visual kei movement. Toshi began an extensive solo career in 1992 before leaving X Japan at the end of 1997. By his own admission, Toshi was 'brainwashed' by a group called Home of Heart, whose leader would control his musical output for the next 12 years. In 2007, X Japan reunited and began a world tour. Toshi severed ties with Home of Heart in January 2010 and renewed his solo career. His distinctive, impassioned tenor vocals have been compared to those of Steve Perry. In Japan, he also uses the stage name Ryūgentoshi (龍玄とし).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/05/Deadpool_2_Japan_Premiere_Red_Carpet_Toshl_%2841555176645%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/toshi/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sugizo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sugizo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Yūne Sugihara , born Yasuhiro Sugihara , better known exclusively by his stage name Sugizo, is a Japanese musician, singer, songwriter, composer, record producer, actor, writer, and activist. He is best known as the lead guitarist and violinist of the rock band Luna Sea since 1989.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/28/Sugizo_in_S%C3%A3o_Paulo%2C_Brazil_2011-11-09.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sugizo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[hide]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hide/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hideto Matsumoto , better known by his stage name hide, was a Japanese musician, singer-songwriter and record producer. He was lead guitarist of the rock band X Japan, a solo artist and a co-founder of the United States-based rock band Zilch.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/95/Xjapan_hongkong2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hide/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>