<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Neurotic Outsiders</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Neurotic Outsiders</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 22:31:47 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen Philip Jones is an English rock guitarist, singer, actor and radio DJ, best known as a guitarist with the Sex Pistols. Following the split of the Sex Pistols, he formed the Professionals with former bandmate Paul Cook. He has also released two solo albums, and worked with the likes of Johnny Thunders, Iggy Pop, Bob Dylan and Thin Lizzy. In 1995, he formed the short lived supergroup Neurotic Outsiders with members of Guns N' Roses and Duran Duran. Jones was ranked #97 in Rolling Stone's list of the '100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time,' which was published in 2015.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/dc/Camp_Freddy_-_Steve_Jones_-_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:37 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Taylor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-taylor-(bass-guitarist)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nigel John Taylor, is an English musician, singer, songwriter, producer, and actor, who is best known as the bass guitarist for new romantic band Duran Duran, of which he was a founding member. Duran Duran was one of the most popular bands in the world during the 1980s due in part to their revolutionary music videos which played in heavy rotation in the early days of MTV. Taylor played with Duran Duran from its founding in 1978 until 1997, when he left to pursue a solo recording and film career. He recorded a dozen solo releases through his private record label B5 Records over the next four years, had a lead role in the movie Sugar Town, and made appearances in a half dozen other film projects. He rejoined Duran Duran for a reunion of the original five members of the group in 2001 and has remained with the group since.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/75/Nigel_John_Taylor.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-taylor-(bass-guitarist)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:36 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>