<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Lo Fi Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Lo Fi Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 23:39:00 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Daniel Johnston]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daniel-johnston/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Daniel Dale Johnston was an American singer-songwriter and visual artist regarded as a significant figure in outsider, lo-fi, and alternative music scenes. Most of his work consisted of cassettes recorded alone in his home, and his music was frequently cited for its 'pure' and 'childlike' qualities.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/76/Daniel_Johnston_and_British_Sea_Power_%286935765808%29_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daniel-johnston/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Beatie Wolfe]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/beatie-wolfe/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Beatie Wolfe is an Anglo-American singer-songwriter, described as 'a pioneering songwriter' known for 'seeing music differently' and creating new tangible formats for music, which include the 'World's First 3D Interactive Album App' for her debut album 8ight, a musical jacket for her second album Montagu Square and the world's first live 360 AR stream for her third album Raw Space. These musical innovations have gained Wolfe critical acclaim with Highsnobiety naming Wolfe as one of '10 Ways Music Will Change in 2017' and Wired (magazine) featuring Wolfe as one of 22 changing the world.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b0/Beatie_Wolfe_portrait.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/beatie-wolfe/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Elliott Smith]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elliott-smith/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steven Paul 'Elliott' Smith was an American singer, songwriter, and multi-instrumentalist. Smith was born in Omaha, Nebraska, raised primarily in Texas, and lived much of his life in Portland, Oregon, where he first gained popularity. Smith's primary instrument was the guitar, though he also used piano, clarinet, bass guitar, drums, and harmonica. Smith had a distinctive vocal style, characterized by his 'whispery, spiderweb-thin delivery', and used multi-tracking to create vocal layers, textures, and harmonies.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8c/Elliott_Smith.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elliott-smith/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bill Callahan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-callahan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bill Callahan is an American singer-songwriter and guitarist who has also recorded and performed under the band name Smog. Callahan began working in the lo-fi genre of underground rock, with home-made tape-albums recorded on four track tape recorders. Later he began releasing albums with the label Drag City, to which he remains signed today.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1f/Bill_callahan_atp.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-callahan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Liz Phair]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/liz-phair/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Elizabeth Clark Phair is an American singer, songwriter, guitarist, composer, and actress. Born in New Haven, Connecticut, Phair was adopted at birth and raised primarily in the Chicago area. After graduating from Oberlin College in 1990, she attempted to start a musical career in San Francisco, California, but returned to her home in Chicago, where she began self-releasing audio cassettes under the name Girly Sound. The tapes led to a recording contract with the independent record label Matador Records.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e3/Liz_Phair_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/liz-phair/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jason Molina]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-molina/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jason Andrew Molina was an American musician and singer-songwriter. Raised in northern Ohio, he came to prominence performing and recording as Songs: Ohia, both in solo projects and with a rotating cast of musicians in the late 1990s. Beginning in 2003, he would garner a further indie following for his releases with the band Magnolia Electric Co.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fb/Magnolia_Electric_Co._live_20050707.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-molina/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>