<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » The Time Jumpers</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » The Time Jumpers</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 22:06:16 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul Franklin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-franklin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul V. Franklin is an American multi-instrumentalist, known mainly for his work as a steel guitarist. He began his career in the 1970s as a member of Barbara Mandrell's road band; in addition he toured with Vince Gill, Mel Tillis, Jerry Reed and Dire Straits. He has since become a prolific session musician in Nashville, playing on more than 500 albums. He has been named by the Academy of Country Music as Best Steel Guitarist on several occasions. He was inducted into the Steel Guitar Hall of Fame in 2000 and the Musicians Hall of Fame and Museum in 2019. In addition to the pedal steel guitar and lap steel guitar, Franklin plays Dobro, fiddle, and drums, as well as three custom-built instruments called the Pedabro, The Box, and the baritone steel guitar.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5d/Paul_Franklin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-franklin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vince Gill]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vince-gill/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vincent Grant Gill is an American country singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. He has achieved commercial success and fame both as frontman to the country rock band Pure Prairie League in the 1970s and as a solo artist beginning in 1983, where his talents as a vocalist and musician have placed him in high demand as a guest vocalist and a duet partner.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6b/Vince_Gill.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vince-gill/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>