<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Christian Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Christian Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 19:23:24 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Sweet]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-sweet/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Harrison Sweet is a singer and guitarist from Whittier, California; he is the co-founder, writer, lead guitarist, lead singer and front man of the Christian metal band Stryper. He was also singer and guitarist for Boston from 2007 to 2011.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2a/Michael_sweet-1474062276.jpeg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-sweet/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael W. Smith]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-w.-smith/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Whitaker Smith is an American musician, who has charted in both contemporary Christian and mainstream charts. His biggest success in mainstream music was in 1991 when 'Place in this World' hit No. 6 on the Billboard Hot 100. Over the course of his career, he has sold more than 18 million albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/56/Michael_W._Smith.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-w.-smith/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lacey Sturm]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lacey-sturm/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lacey Nicole Sturm is an American singer and songwriter born in Homestead, Florida and raised in Arlington, Texas. She is a co-founder and former lead vocalist of the hard rock band Flyleaf. In February 2016, Sturm became the first solo female to top the Billboard Hard Rock Albums chart with her debut release.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/12/Lacey_Sturm_%28Flyleaf%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lacey-sturm/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Matt Thiessen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/matt-thiessen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Matthew Arnold Thiessen is a Canadian-American musician, singer and songwriter known for being co-founder, lead singer, guitarist, pianist, and primary songwriter for the Christian rock band Relient K. With Relient K, he has released eight full-length albums, including three that were certified Gold, and three that peaked in the top twenty on the Billboard 200. Outside of his work with Relient K, Thiessen leads a side project called Matthew Thiessen and the Earthquakes, which released its debut album Wind Up Bird on August 31, 2018. In 2009, he co-produced and collaborated on Owl City's album Ocean Eyes.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/58/MatthewThiessen-RelientK.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/matt-thiessen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>