<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Saxophone</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Saxophone</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:04:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andrea Bocelli]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrea-bocelli/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Andrea Bocelli is an Italian opera singer, songwriter, and record producer. Celine Dion has said that 'if God would have a singing voice, he must sound a lot like Andrea Bocelli,' and David Foster, a record producer, often describes Bocelli's voice as the most beautiful in the world.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/15/AndreaBocelliMar10.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrea-bocelli/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Toto Cutugno]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/toto-cutugno/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Salvatore 'Toto' Cutugno is an Italian pop singer-songwriter and musician. He may be best known for his worldwide hit song, 'L'Italiano', released on his 1983 album of the same title. Cutugno also won the Eurovision Song Contest 1990 with the song 'Insieme: 1992', for which he wrote both lyrics and music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Toto_Cutugno.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/toto-cutugno/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hyde]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hyde/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hideto Takarai , known exclusively by his stage name Hyde, is a Japanese musician, singer, songwriter, producer, and actor. He is best known as lead vocalist of the rock band L'Arc-en-Ciel. He is also lead vocalist of Vamps and has a solo career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/Hyde_in_2013.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hyde/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Bowie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-bowie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Robert Jones, known professionally as David Bowie, was an English singer-songwriter and actor. He was a leading figure in the music industry and is considered one of the most influential musicians of the 20th century, acclaimed by critics and musicians, particularly for his innovative work during the 1970s. His career was marked by reinvention and visual presentation, with his music and stagecraft having a significant impact on popular music. During his lifetime, his record sales, estimated at 140 million albums worldwide, made him one of the world's best-selling music artists. In the UK, he was awarded ten platinum album certifications, eleven gold and eight silver, and released eleven number-one albums. In the US, he received five platinum and nine gold certifications. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1996.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e8/David-Bowie_Chicago_2002-08-08_photoby_Adam-Bielawski-cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-bowie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sting]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sting/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gordon Matthew Thomas Sumner, known as Sting, is an English musician and actor. He was the principal songwriter, lead singer, and bassist for the new wave rock band the Police from 1977 to 1984, and launched a solo career in 1985. He has included elements of rock, jazz, reggae, classical, new-age and worldbeat in his music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Sting_-_Deutscher_Radiopreis_Hamburg_2016_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sting/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marilyn Manson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marilyn-manson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Hugh Warner, known professionally as Marilyn Manson, is an American singer, songwriter, record producer, actor, visual artist and music video director. He is known for his controversial stage personality and image as the lead singer of the band Marilyn Manson, which he co-founded with guitarist Daisy Berkowitz and of which he remains the only constant member. Like the other founding members of the band, his stage name was formed by combining and juxtaposing the names of two American pop cultural icons of the 1960s: actress Marilyn Monroe and criminal Charles Manson.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Revolver_Golden_Gods_Awards.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marilyn-manson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vladimir Kuzmin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vladimir-kuzmin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vladimir Borisovich Kuzmin is a Russian rock singer, guitarist, and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b9/%D0%9A%D1%83%D0%B7%D1%8C%D0%BC%D0%B8%D0%BD-%D0%9A%D0%B0%D0%BC%D0%B5%D0%BD%D1%81%D0%BA_21-10-12_cr.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vladimir-kuzmin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>