<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Saxophone</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Saxophone</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 01:13:48 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andrea Bocelli]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrea-bocelli/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Andrea Bocelli is an Italian opera singer, songwriter, and record producer. Celine Dion has said that 'if God would have a singing voice, he must sound a lot like Andrea Bocelli,' and David Foster, a record producer, often describes Bocelli's voice as the most beautiful in the world.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/15/AndreaBocelliMar10.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrea-bocelli/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lowell George]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lowell-george/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lowell Thomas George was an American singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, and record producer, who was the primary guitarist, vocalist, and songwriter for the rock band Little Feat.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/19/Little_Feat_Lowell_George.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lowell-george/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Trent Reznor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Trent Reznor is an American singer, songwriter, musician, record producer, and film score composer. He is the founder, lead vocalist, and principal songwriter of the industrial rock band Nine Inch Nails, which he founded in 1988 and of which he was the sole official member until adding long-time collaborator Atticus Ross as a permanent member in 2016. His first release under the Nine Inch Nails name, the 1989 album Pretty Hate Machine, was a commercial and critical success. He has since released nine Nine Inch Nails studio albums. He left Interscope Records in 2007 and was an independent recording artist until signing with Columbia Records in 2012.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d5/Trent_Reznor-FEB2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roy Wood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-wood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roy Wood is an English singer-songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. He was particularly successful in the 1960s and 1970s as member and co-founder of The Move, Electric Light Orchestra and Wizzard. As a songwriter, he contributed a number of hits to the repertoire of these bands. Collectively, hit records by The Move, Electric Light Orchestra, Wizzard, and Wood's own solo singles demonstrated an impressive chart run for an individual, both as composer and performer. Altogether he had more than 20 singles in the UK Singles Chart under various guises, including three UK No. 1 hits.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0f/Roy_Wood_TopPop.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-wood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Todd Rundgren]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Todd Harry Rundgren is an American multi-instrumentalist, singer, songwriter, and record producer who has performed a diverse range of styles as a solo artist, and as a member of the band Utopia. He is known for his sophisticated and often-unorthodox music, flamboyant stage outfits, and his later experiments with interactive entertainment. He also produced music videos, pioneered forms of multimedia, and was an early adopter and promoter of various computer technologies, such as using the Internet as a means of music distribution in the late 1990s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4b/Todd_Rundgren_performs_%40_WorkPlay.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Toto Cutugno]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/toto-cutugno/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Salvatore 'Toto' Cutugno is an Italian pop singer-songwriter and musician. He may be best known for his worldwide hit song, 'L'Italiano', released on his 1983 album of the same title. Cutugno also won the Eurovision Song Contest 1990 with the song 'Insieme: 1992', for which he wrote both lyrics and music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Toto_Cutugno.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/toto-cutugno/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Garth Brooks]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/garth-brooks/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Troyal Garth Brooks is an American singer and songwriter. His integration of rock and pop elements into the country genre has earned him immense popularity in the United States. Brooks has had great success on the country single and album charts, with multi-platinum recordings and record-breaking live performances, while also crossing over into the mainstream pop arena.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Garth_Brooks_2019_By_Glenn_Francis.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/garth-brooks/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hyde]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hyde/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hideto Takarai , known exclusively by his stage name Hyde, is a Japanese musician, singer, songwriter, producer, and actor. He is best known as lead vocalist of the rock band L'Arc-en-Ciel. He is also lead vocalist of Vamps and has a solo career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/Hyde_in_2013.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hyde/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Bowie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-bowie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Robert Jones, known professionally as David Bowie, was an English singer-songwriter and actor. He was a leading figure in the music industry and is considered one of the most influential musicians of the 20th century, acclaimed by critics and musicians, particularly for his innovative work during the 1970s. His career was marked by reinvention and visual presentation, with his music and stagecraft having a significant impact on popular music. During his lifetime, his record sales, estimated at 140 million albums worldwide, made him one of the world's best-selling music artists. In the UK, he was awarded ten platinum album certifications, eleven gold and eight silver, and released eleven number-one albums. In the US, he received five platinum and nine gold certifications. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1996.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e8/David-Bowie_Chicago_2002-08-08_photoby_Adam-Bielawski-cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-bowie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lewis Brian Hopkins Jones was an English musician, best known as the founder and original leader of the Rolling Stones. Initially a slide guitarist, Jones would go on to play a wide variety of instruments on Rolling Stones recordings and in concerts, such as rhythm and lead guitar, sitar, dulcimer, various keyboard instruments such as piano and mellotron, marimba, wind instruments such as harmonica, recorder, saxophone, as well as drums, vocals and numerous others.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6b/Brian_Jones%2C_Statesboro%2C_Georgia%2C_May_4%2C_1965_%28377872218%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>