<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Adult Contemporary Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Adult Contemporary Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:06:55 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[k.d. lang]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/k.d.-lang/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kathryn Dawn Lang, known by her stylized stage name k.d. lang, is a Canadian pop and country singer-songwriter and occasional actress.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/76/Kd_lang_-_AIS_Arena%2C_Canberra_-_7_Nov_11%283%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/k.d.-lang/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sarah McLachlan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sarah-mclachlan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sarah Ann McLachlan, is a Canadian singer-songwriter known for her emotional ballads and mezzo-soprano vocal range. As of 2015 she had sold over 40 million albums worldwide. McLachlan's best-selling album to date is Surfacing, for which she won two Grammy Awards and four Juno Awards. In addition to her personal artistic efforts, she founded the Lilith Fair tour, which showcased female musicians on an unprecedented scale. The Lilith Fair concert tours took place from 1997 to 1999, and resumed in the summer of 2010.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/SarahMclachlanJLC2005.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sarah-mclachlan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bryan Adams]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bryan-adams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bryan Guy Adams is a Canadian singer, songwriter, record producer, guitarist, photographer, philanthropist and activist. He rose to fame in Canada and the United States with his 1983 album Cuts Like a Knife and turned into a global star with his 1984 album Reckless, which produced some of his best known songs, including 'Run to You', 'Summer of '69' and his first number one, 'Heaven'. In 1991, he released the album Waking Up the Neighbours, which included the song '(Everything I Do) I Do It for You'. The song became a worldwide hit and reached number 1 in many countries, including a new record of 16 consecutive weeks in the United Kingdom. Adams also had the U.S. Billboard Hot 100 number-one singles 'All for Love' and 'Have You Ever Really Loved a Woman?'</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7e/Bryan_Adams_Hamburg_MG_0631_flickr.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bryan-adams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>