<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Organ</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Organ</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 12:09:49 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Glenn Frey]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glenn-frey/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Glenn Lewis Frey was an American singer, songwriter, actor and founding member of the rock band the Eagles. Frey was the co-lead singer and frontman for the Eagles, roles he came to share with fellow member Don Henley, with whom he wrote most of the Eagles' material. Frey played guitar and keyboards as well as singing lead vocals on songs such as 'Take It Easy', 'Peaceful Easy Feeling', 'Tequila Sunrise', 'Already Gone', 'James Dean', 'Lyin' Eyes', 'New Kid in Town', and 'Heartache Tonight'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8a/Glenn_Frey.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glenn-frey/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gregg Allman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gregg-allman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gregory LeNoir Allman was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was known for performing in the Allman Brothers Band. Allman grew up with an interest in rhythm and blues music, and the Allman Brothers Band fused it with rock music, jazz, and country at times. He wrote several of the band's biggest songs, including 'Whipping Post', 'Melissa', and 'Midnight Rider'. Allman also had a successful solo career, releasing seven studio albums. He was born and spent much of his childhood in Nashville, Tennessee, before relocating to Daytona Beach, Florida and then Richmond Hill, Georgia.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6f/Gregg_Allman_1975.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gregg-allman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David A. Stewart]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-a.-stewart/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ac/David_A._Stewart_Rock_am_Ring_1987.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-a.-stewart/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[James McMurtry]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-mcmurtry/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/70/James_McMurtry_SXSW_2006_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-mcmurtry/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nat King Cole]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nat-king-cole/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nathaniel Adams Coles, known professionally as Nat King Cole, was an American singer, jazz pianist, and actor. He recorded over 100 songs that became hits on the pop charts. His trio was the model for small jazz ensembles that followed. Cole also acted in films and on television and performed on Broadway. He was the first African-American man to host an American television series. He was the father of singer-songwriter Natalie Cole (1950–2015).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/83/Nat_King_Cole_%28Gottlieb_01511%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nat-king-cole/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Shinoda]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Kenji Shinoda is an American musician, rapper, singer, songwriter, record producer, and graphic designer. He co-founded Linkin Park in 1996 and is the band's lead vocalist, as well as rhythm guitarist, keyboardist, primary songwriter and producer. Shinoda later created a hip-hop-driven side project, Fort Minor, in 2004. He has also served as a producer for tracks and albums by Lupe Fiasco, Styles of Beyond and the X-Ecutioners.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/Mike_Shinoda_4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[T-Bone Walker]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/t-bone-walker/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Aaron Thibeaux 'T-Bone' Walker was an American blues guitarist, singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist, who was a pioneer and innovator of the jump blues and electric blues sound. In 2018 Rolling Stone magazine ranked him number 67 on its list of 'The 100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time'. In March 1975, Walker died due to health issues in his Los Angeles home.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ee/T-Bone_Walker_1972.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/t-bone-walker/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[James Taylor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-taylor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Vernon Taylor is an American singer-songwriter and guitarist. A six-time Grammy Award winner, he was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 2000. He is one of the best-selling music artists of all time, having sold more than 100 million records worldwide.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/88/James_Taylor_at_Tanglewood.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-taylor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Neil Young]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Neil Percival Young is a Canadian-American singer-songwriter, musician, and activist. After embarking on a music career in Winnipeg in the 1960s, Young moved to Los Angeles, joining Buffalo Springfield with Stephen Stills, Richie Furay and others. Since the beginning of his solo career with his backing band Crazy Horse, Young has released many critically acclaimed and important albums, such as After the Gold Rush, Everybody Knows This Is Nowhere, and Harvest.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bb/Neil_Young_-_Per_Ole_Hagen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bryan Adams]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bryan-adams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bryan Guy Adams is a Canadian guitarist, singer, composer, record producer, photographer, and philanthropist. With several number-one singles and albums in various countries, Adams has sold over 100 million records worldwide. Adams was the most played artist on Canadian radio in the 2010s and he has had 25 top-15 singles in Canada, and a dozen or more in the US, UK and Australia.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7e/Bryan_Adams_Hamburg_MG_0631_flickr.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bryan-adams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>