<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Ska</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Ska</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:08:38 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Winehouse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Jade Winehouse was an English singer and songwriter. She was known for her deep, expressive contralto vocals and her eclectic mix of musical genres, including soul rhythm and blues, and jazz. Winehouse's debut album, Frank (2003), was a critical success in the UK and was nominated for the Mercury Prize. Her follow-up album, Back to Black (2006), led to five 2008 Grammy Awards, tying the then record for the most wins by a female artist in a single night, and made her the first British woman to win five Grammys, including three of the General Field 'Big Four' Grammy Awards: Best New Artist, Record of the Year and Song of the Year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Amy_Winehouse_f4962007_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tim Armstrong]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tim-armstrong/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Timothy Ross Armstrong is an American musician, singer, songwriter, producer, and actor. He is best known as the singer/guitarist for the punk rock band Rancid and hip hop/punk rock supergroup Transplants. Prior to forming Rancid, Armstrong was in the influential ska punk band Operation Ivy. In 1997, along with Brett Gurewitz of the band Bad Religion and owner of Epitaph Records, Armstrong founded Hellcat Records. In 2012, through his website, Armstrong started releasing music that influenced him, along with stripped-down cover songs of his own work under the name Tim Timebomb. He has released at least one song per week since late 2012. Armstrong is also a songwriter for other artists. Armstrong won a Grammy Award for his work with Jimmy Cliff and Pink, and has also worked with Joe Walsh.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/17/TimLiveSept2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tim-armstrong/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sergey Shnurov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sergey-shnurov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sergey Vladimirovich Shnurov is a Russian musician and songwriter, best known as Shnur, of the ska-punk band Leningrad which he formed in 1997 and was the frontman of till the end of 2008. In December 2008 the group disbanded, Shnur with some of its members forming Rubl.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6f/Sergei_Shnurov.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sergey-shnurov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ernest Ranglin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ernest-ranglin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ernest Ranglin OD is a Jamaican guitarist and composer who established his career while working as a session guitarist and music director for various Jamaican record labels including Studio One and Island Records. Ranglin played guitar on many early ska recordings and helped create the rhythmic guitar style that defined the form. Ranglin has worked with Theophilus Beckford, Jimmy Cliff, Monty Alexander, Prince Buster, the Skatalites, Bob Marley and the Eric Deans Orchestra. He is noted for a chordal and rhythmic approach that blends jazz, mento and reggae with percussive guitar solos incorporating rhythm 'n' blues and jazz inflections.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/47/Ernest_Ranglin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ernest-ranglin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mark Foggo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-foggo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Mark Foggo is an English-born ska musician currently based in England, United Kingdom</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f1/Mark_Foggo.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-foggo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mark Bedford]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-bedford/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Mark William Bedford, nicknamed Bedders, is an English musician, songwriter and composer. Bedford came to prominence in the late 1970s as the bass guitarist for the English ska band Madness.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7e/Bedders.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-bedford/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bob Marley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-marley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Nesta Marley, was a Jamaican singer and songwriter. Considered one of the pioneers of reggae, his musical career was marked by blending elements of reggae, ska, and rocksteady, as well as forging a smooth and distinctive vocal and songwriting style. Marley's contributions to music increased the visibility of Jamaican music worldwide, and made him a global figure in popular culture for over a decade.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5e/Bob-Marley.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-marley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>