<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Upright Piano</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Upright Piano</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 12:09:49 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jim Lea]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jim-lea/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f2/Slade_-_TopPop_1974_3_%28cropped%29.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jim-lea/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Wes Scantlin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wes-scantlin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Wesley Reid Scantlin is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. He is best known as the lead vocalist, guitarist, and only constant member of rock band Puddle of Mudd. He was named one of the 'Top 100 Heavy Metal Vocalists' by Hit Parader.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/41/Wes_Scantlin_Puddle_of_Mudd_2009_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wes-scantlin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bryan Adams]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bryan-adams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bryan Guy Adams is a Canadian guitarist, singer, composer, record producer, photographer, and philanthropist. With several number-one singles and albums in various countries, Adams has sold over 100 million records worldwide. Adams was the most played artist on Canadian radio in the 2010s and he has had 25 top-15 singles in Canada, and a dozen or more in the US, UK and Australia.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7e/Bryan_Adams_Hamburg_MG_0631_flickr.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bryan-adams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Entwistle]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-entwistle/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John ‍Alec ‍Entwistle was an English musician and songwriter who was the bassist ‍for the rock band the Who. Nicknamed 'The Ox' and 'Thunderfingers', Entwistle's music career spanned over four decades. He was the band's only member with formal musical training and also provided backing and occasional lead vocals. Entwistle was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Who in 1990.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f5/John_Entwistle_in_1967_with_The_Who.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-entwistle/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mick Jagger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mick-jagger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir Michael Philip Jagger is an English singer, songwriter, actor, and film producer who has gained worldwide fame as the lead singer and one of the founder members of the Rolling Stones. Jagger's career has spanned over six decades, and he has been described as 'one of the most popular and influential frontmen in the history of rock & roll'. His distinctive voice and energetic live performances, along with Keith Richards' guitar style, have been the trademark of the Rolling Stones throughout the band's career. Jagger gained press notoriety for his romantic involvements and was often portrayed as a countercultural figure.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/74/Rolling_Stones_04.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mick-jagger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nick Drake]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nick-drake/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nicholas Rodney Drake was an English singer-songwriter and musician known for his acoustic guitar-based songs. Though he never found a wide audience during his lifetime, his work has gradually achieved wider notice and recognition. Drake signed to Island Records when he was 20 years old and a student at the University of Cambridge. He released his debut album, Five Leaves Left, in 1969. He recorded two more albums—Bryter Layter (1970) and Pink Moon (1972). Neither sold more than 5,000 copies on initial release. His reluctance to perform live, or be interviewed, contributed to his lack of commercial success. There is no known video footage of the adult Drake; he was only ever captured in still photographs and in home footage from his childhood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/61/Nick_Drake_%281971%29.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nick-drake/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sergei Trofimov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sergei-trofimov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8e/2012-03-05_%D0%A1%D0%B5%D1%80%D0%B3%D0%B5%D0%B9_%D0%A2%D1%80%D0%BE%D1%84%D0%B8%D0%BC%D0%BE%D0%B2.jpeg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sergei-trofimov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lights]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lights/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lights Poxleitner-Bokan, known mononymously as Lights, is a Canadian musician, singer, and songwriter. She is known for singles 'Drive My Soul', 'February Air', 'Ice', 'Second Go', 'Toes', 'Lions' and 'Up We Go'. She was awarded the 2009 Juno Award for New Artist of the Year and two 2009 Astral Media Radio awards during Canadian Music Week.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ea/Lights_09_20_2017_-5_%2837009966944%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lights/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marié Digby]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marié-digby/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Marié Christina Digby is an American singer, songwriter, guitarist and pianist known for her acoustic cover version of Rihanna's 'Umbrella', which was posted on YouTube in 2007. The song was subsequently played on the radio station STAR 98.7, was featured on the highly rated third season opening episode of the MTV show The Hills, and peaked at #10 on the Bubbling Under Hot 100 Singles chart. Digby performed the song on the late night talk show Last Call with Carson Daly on August 2, 2007. Since then, Digby has released several studio albums, EPs and singles, including one Japanese cover album. Her fifth studio album Winter Fields was released on October 29, 2013. On August 16, 2014, Marié released Chimera, a 3 track EP.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/Mari%C3%A9_Digby_-_Dream_World.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marié-digby/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dotan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dotan-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dotan Harpenau, better known by his stage name Dotan, is a Dutch-Israeli singer-songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, and record producer.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f5/Dotan_%282015%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dotan-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>