<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Upright Piano</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Upright Piano</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 22:26:45 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Phil Spector]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/phil-spector/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Phillip Harvey Spector is an American record producer, musician, and songwriter. He developed the Wall of Sound, a music production formula he described as a Wagnerian approach to rock and roll. Spector was dubbed the 'First Tycoon of Teen' by writer Tom Wolfe and is acknowledged as one of the most influential figures in pop music history. After the 1970s, Spector mostly retired from public life. In 2009, he was convicted of second-degree murder and has remained incarcerated since.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/24/Phil_Spector_2000.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/phil-spector/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Entwistle]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-entwistle/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Alec Entwistle was an English bass guitarist, singer, songwriter, and film and music producer. In a music career that spanned more than 40 years, Entwistle was best known as the original bass guitarist for the English rock band the Who. He was the only member of the band to have formal musical training. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Who in 1990.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f5/John_Entwistle_in_1967_with_The_Who.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-entwistle/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lights]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lights/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lights Poxleitner-Bokan, known mononymously as Lights, is a Canadian musician, singer, songwriter, author, and illustrator. She is known for her gold-certified albums The Listening and Siberia as well as singles 'Drive My Soul', 'February Air', 'Ice', 'Second Go', 'Toes', and 'Up We Go'. She released her fourth studio album, Skin & Earth, in 2017 accompanied by a graphic novel of the same name.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/LIGHTS_IMG_6799_%2815999651243%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lights/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nick Drake]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nick-drake/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nicholas Rodney 'Nick' Drake was an English singer-songwriter. Although his music did not find a wide audience during his lifetime, he gradually achieved wider recognition and is now considered among the most influential English singer-songwriters of the last 50 years. Drake signed to Island Records when he was 20 years old and released his debut album, Five Leaves Left, in 1969. By 1972, he had recorded two more albums: Bryter Layter and Pink Moon. Neither sold more than 5,000 copies on initial release.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/61/Nick_Drake_%281971%29.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nick-drake/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marié Digby]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marié-digby/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Marié Christina Digby is an American singer, songwriter, guitarist and pianist known for her acoustic cover version of Rihanna's 'Umbrella', which was posted on YouTube in 2007. The song was subsequently played on the radio station STAR 98.7, was featured on the highly rated third season opening episode of the MTV show The Hills, and peaked at #10 on the Bubbling Under Hot 100 Singles chart. Digby performed the song on the late night talk show Last Call with Carson Daly on August 2, 2007. Since then, Digby has released several studio albums, EPs and singles, including one Japanese cover album. Her fifth and latest studio album Winter Fields was released on October 29, 2013. On August 16, 2014, Marié released Chimera, a 3 track EP.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/Mari%C3%A9_Digby_-_Dream_World.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marié-digby/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Buckethead]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Patrick Carroll, known professionally as Buckethead, is an American multi-instrumental musician who has received critical acclaim for his innovative electric guitar playing. His music spans many genres, including progressive metal, funk, blues, bluegrass, ambient, and avant-garde music. He performs primarily as a solo artist, though he has collaborated extensively with a wide variety of high-profile artists such as Bill Laswell, Bootsy Collins, Bernie Worrell, Iggy Pop, Les Claypool, Serj Tankian, Bill Moseley, Mike Patton, Viggo Mortensen, That 1 Guy, Bassnectar, and was a member of Guns N' Roses from 2000 to 2004. He has released 306 studio albums, four special releases, and one EP. He has also performed on more than 50 other albums by other artists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Neumos_seattle_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bryan Adams]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bryan-adams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bryan Guy Adams is a Canadian singer, songwriter, record producer, guitarist, photographer, philanthropist and activist. He rose to fame in Canada and the United States with his 1983 album Cuts Like a Knife and turned into a global star with his 1984 album Reckless, which produced some of his best known songs, including 'Run to You', 'Summer of '69' and his first number one, 'Heaven'. In 1991, he released the album Waking Up the Neighbours, which included the song '(Everything I Do) I Do It for You'. The song became a worldwide hit and reached number 1 in many countries, including a new record of 16 consecutive weeks in the United Kingdom. Adams also had the U.S. Billboard Hot 100 number-one singles 'All for Love' and 'Have You Ever Really Loved a Woman?'</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7e/Bryan_Adams_Hamburg_MG_0631_flickr.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bryan-adams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tilo Wolff]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tilo-wolff/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tilo Wolff is a German musician who currently lives in Switzerland.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a2/Lacrimosa_2005_-_Tilo_Wolff_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tilo-wolff/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Wes Scantlin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wes-scantlin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Wesley Reid Scantlin is an American singer, songwriter, musician, and the only remaining founding member of the American post-grunge band Puddle of Mudd.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/86/Wes_Scantlin_Puddle_of_Mudd_2009.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wes-scantlin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jim Lea]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jim-lea/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Whild Lea is an English musician, most notable for playing bass guitar, keyboards, piano, violin, and guitar, and singing backing vocals in Slade from their inception until 1992, and for co-writing most of their songs.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Slade_-_TopPop_1973_19_-_Jim_Lea_-_Crop.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jim-lea/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>