<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Marimba</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Marimba</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 22:31:47 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robbie Williams]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-williams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Peter Williams is an English singer-songwriter and entertainer. He found fame as a member of the pop group Take That from 1990 to 1995, but achieved greater commercial success with his solo career, beginning in 1996. Williams has released seven UK number one singles and eleven out of his twelve studio albums have reached number one in the UK. Six of his albums are among the top 100 biggest-selling albums in the United Kingdom–four albums in the top 60–and in 2006 he entered the Guinness Book of World Records for selling 1.6 million tickets of his Close Encounters Tour in a single day.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/Robbie_Williams.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-williams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lewis Brian Hopkin Jones was an English musician and composer, best known as the founder and original leader of the Rolling Stones. Initially a slide guitarist, Jones went on to play a wide variety of instruments on Rolling Stones recordings and in concerts, including rhythm guitar, lead guitar, sitar, dulcimer, various keyboard instruments such as piano and mellotron, marimba, wind instruments such as harmonica, recorder, saxophone, as well as drums, vocals and numerous others.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6b/Brian_Jones%2C_Statesboro%2C_Georgia%2C_May_4%2C_1965_%28377872218%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Trent Reznor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Trent Reznor is an American musician, singer, songwriter, record producer, and composer. He serves as the lead vocalist, multi-instrumentalist, and principal songwriter of the industrial rock band Nine Inch Nails, which he founded in 1988 and of which he was the sole official member until 2016. The first Nine Inch Nails album, Pretty Hate Machine (1989), was a commercial and critical success. Reznor has since released 11 more Nine Inch Nails studio albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c9/Trent_Reznor-FEB2008_%28cropped%2C_but_higher_quality%29_%282%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:37 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>