<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Electronic Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Electronic Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:12:56 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vyacheslav Butusov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vyacheslav-butusov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vyacheslav Gennadievich Butusov, is a Russian singer and songwriter. He was the lead singer of Nautilus Pompilius and U-Piter. Since 2019, he has been playing in the group 'Orden Slavy' created by him. He also has his own solo career as a singer and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e1/Vyacheslav_Butusov_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vyacheslav-butusov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ilya Lagutenko]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ilya-lagutenko/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/23/Ilya_Lagutenko_%40_Park_Live_%28cropped%29.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ilya-lagutenko/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Madonna]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/madonna/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Madonna Louise Ciccone is an American singer, songwriter, and actress. Referred to as the 'Queen of Pop', she is regarded as one of the most significant figures in popular culture. Madonna is noted for her continual reinvention and versatility in music production, songwriting, and visual presentation. She is also known for pushing the boundaries of artistic expression in mainstream music while remaining completely in charge of every aspect of her career. Her works, which incorporate social, political, sexual, and religious themes, have generated both critical acclaim and controversy. Madonna is often cited as an influence by other artists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Madonna_Rebel_Heart_Tour_2015_-_Stockholm_%2823051472299%29_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/madonna/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Graham Russell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/graham-russell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Graham Cyril Russell is an English musician, songwriter, and singer/guitarist of the soft rock duo Air Supply.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/64/Graham_Russell.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/graham-russell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gary Numan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gary-numan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gary Anthony James Webb, better known as Gary Numan, is an English musician, singer, songwriter, composer, and record producer. He entered the music industry as the frontman of the new wave band Tubeway Army. After releasing two albums with the band, he released his debut solo album The Pleasure Principle in 1979, topping the UK Albums Chart. While his commercial popularity peaked in the late 1970s and early 1980s with hits including 'Are 'Friends' Electric?' and 'Cars', he maintains a cult following. He has sold over 10 million records.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/93/Gary_Numan.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gary-numan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Magnet]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/magnet/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7d/Magnet01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/magnet/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Squarepusher]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/squarepusher/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tom Jenkinson, known professionally as Squarepusher, is an English electronic musician, record producer, bassist, and DJ. His music spans several genres, including drum and bass, IDM, jazz, and electroacoustic music. His recordings are often typified by a combination of complex drum programming, live instrumental playing, and digital signal processing. Since 1995, he has recorded for Warp Records as well as smaller labels. He released 1996 debut LP Feed Me Weird Things on Rephlex Records.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c4/Squarepusher.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/squarepusher/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sufjan Stevens]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sufjan-stevens/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sufjan Stevens is an American singer, songwriter, and multi-instrumentalist. He has released eight solo studio albums and multiple collaborative albums with other artists. Stevens has received Academy Award and Grammy Award nominations.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/84/Sufjan_Stevens_playing_banjo_edit1_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sufjan-stevens/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alex James]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alex-james/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steven Alexander James, FRSA is an English musician and songwriter, as well as a journalist and cheesemaker. Best known as the bassist of the band Blur, he has also played with temporary bands Fat Les, Me Me Me, WigWam and Bad Lieutenant.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d0/Alex_James_2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alex-james/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robbie Williams]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-williams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Peter Williams is an English singer-songwriter and entertainer. He found fame as a member of the pop group Take That from 1990 to 1995, but achieved greater commercial success with his solo career, beginning in 1996. Williams has released seven UK number one singles and eleven out of his twelve studio albums have reached number one in the UK. Six of his albums are among the top 100 biggest-selling albums in the United Kingdom–four albums in the top 60–and in 2006 he entered the Guinness Book of World Records for selling 1.6 million tickets of his Close Encounters Tour in a single day.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/Robbie_Williams.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-williams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>