<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Electronic Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Electronic Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:07:39 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vyacheslav Butusov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vyacheslav-butusov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vyacheslav Gennadievich Butusov, is a Russian singer and songwriter. He was the lead singer of Nautilus Pompilius and U-Piter. He also has his own solo career as a singer and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e1/Vyacheslav_Butusov_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vyacheslav-butusov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ilya Lagutenko]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ilya-lagutenko/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ilya Igorevich Lagutenko is the founder and lead singer of MTV Award-winning band Mumiy Troll.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e8/%D0%98%D0%BB%D1%8C%D1%8F_%D0%9B%D0%B0%D0%B3%D1%83%D1%82%D0%B5%D0%BD%D0%BA%D0%BE_2016_2_%281%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ilya-lagutenko/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alex James]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alex-james/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steven Alexander James, FRSA is an English musician and songwriter, as well as a journalist and cheesemaker. Best known as the bassist of the band Blur, he has also played with temporary bands Fat Les, Me Me Me, WigWam and Bad Lieutenant.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d0/Alex_James_2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alex-james/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jade Puget]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jade-puget/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jade Errol Puget is an American musician and producer, best known as the guitarist for the rock band AFI, the guitarist/writer for the straight edge hardcore band XTRMST, and the keyboardist/synthesizer operator for the electronic duo Blaqk Audio. Puget is vegetarian and straight edge.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e6/Jade_puget.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jade-puget/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Squarepusher]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/squarepusher/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tom Jenkinson, commonly known as Squarepusher, is an English electronic musician whose compositions draw on a number of influences, including drum and bass, IDM, jazz, and electroacoustic music. His recordings are typified by a combination of electronic sound sources, live instrumental playing, and digital signal processing. He is the brother of Ceephax Acid Crew.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c4/Squarepusher.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/squarepusher/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robbie Williams]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-williams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Peter Williams is an English singer-songwriter and entertainer. He found fame as a member of the pop group Take That from 1989 to 1995, but achieved greater commercial success with his solo career, beginning in 1997. Williams has released seven UK number one singles and ten out of his eleven studio albums have reached number one in the UK. He is the best-selling British solo artist in the United Kingdom and the best selling non-Latino artist in Latin America. Six of his albums are among the top 100 biggest-selling albums in the United Kingdom–four albums in the top 60–and in 2006 he entered the Guinness Book of World Records for selling 1.6 million tickets of his Close Encounters Tour in a single day.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/Robbie_Williams.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-williams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jonny Greenwood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jonny-greenwood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jonathan Richard Guy Greenwood is an English musician and composer. He is the lead guitarist and keyboardist of the alternative rock band Radiohead, and has written a number of film scores.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/ce/Jonny_Greenwood.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jonny-greenwood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Magnet]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/magnet/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Magnet is the pseudonym of Norwegian singer-songwriter Even Johansen. To date, he has released four full-length studio albums as well as several singles and EPs. Johansen draws upon many influences, including folk, pop, and electronica. His albums are composed and produced solely by him, and he usually performs live sets on his own, using preset loops or creating them as he plays.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7d/Magnet01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/magnet/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>