<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Foo Fighters</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Foo Fighters</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:12:57 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Shiflett]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-shiflett/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher Aubrey Shiflett is an American musician. He is most recognizable as lead guitarist for the American rock band Foo Fighters. He was previously a member of the punk rock bands No Use for a Name (1995–1999) and Me First and the Gimme Gimmes (1995–2019). He joined the Foo Fighters in 1999 following the release of their third album There Is Nothing Left to Lose, and performed with the Foo Fighters and the Gimmes, as well as several other side projects, simultaneously. He also hosts a podcast titled Walking the Floor and has released two solo albums, the most recent in 2019.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3c/Chris_Shiflett_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-shiflett/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Grohl]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-grohl/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Eric Grohl is an American musician, singer, songwriter, and documentary filmmaker. He was the drummer for rock band Nirvana and founded the band Foo Fighters, for whom he is the singer, guitarist, and primary songwriter. Grohl is also the drummer and co-founder of the rock supergroup Them Crooked Vultures, and wrote the music for his short-lived side projects Late! and Probot. He has also recorded and toured with Queens of the Stone Age.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/07/FoosDublin210819-2_%2848620472807%29_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-grohl/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>