<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » The Cars</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » The Cars</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 21:36:05 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Elliot Easton]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elliot-easton/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Elliot Easton is an American musician, guitarist, singer and songwriter. He played lead guitar and sang backing vocals for The Cars. His guitar solos are an integral part of the band's music. He studied music at the Berklee College of Music. He is a left-handed guitarist. After the collapse of the Cars in 1988, Easton played in bands such as the New Cars and the roots rock group Creedence Clearwater Revisited. In 2018, Easton was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Cars.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f6/Elliot-easton-performs-with-the-new-cars-2006.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elliot-easton/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ric Ocasek]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ric-ocasek/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Theodore Otcasek, known as Ric Ocasek, was an American singer, songwriter, musician and record producer. He was the primary lead vocalist, rhythm guitarist, songwriter, and frontman for the rock band the Cars. In addition to his work with the Cars, Ocasek recorded seven solo albums, and his song 'Emotion in Motion' was a top 20 hit in the United States in 1986. Ocasek also worked as a record producer for artists such as Motion City Soundtrack, Suicide, Bad Brains, Weezer, Nada Surf, Guided by Voices, and No Doubt. In 2018, Ocasek was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Cars.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f7/Ric-Ocasek.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ric-ocasek/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:38 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>