<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Country Pop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Country Pop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 19:00:47 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Cassadee Pope]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/cassadee-pope/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Cassadee Blake Pope is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. Pope was the lead vocalist of the rock band Hey Monday, with whom she released two studio albums and three EPs. Pope embarked on a solo career in early 2012, and released the EP Cassadee Pope in May 2012. She took part in the third season of The Voice and became the first female winner on December 18, 2012. Her debut solo country album, Frame by Frame, was released on October 8, 2013 to a top 10 Billboard 200 charting. It debuted at No. 1 on Top Country Albums, with 43,000 copies sold in its first week.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ab/Cassadeepope2010.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/cassadee-pope/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dolly Parton]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dolly-parton/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dolly Rebecca Parton is an American singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, actress, author, businesswoman, and humanitarian, known primarily for her work in country music. After achieving success as a songwriter for others, Parton made her album debut in 1967 with Hello, I'm Dolly, which led to success during the remainder of the 1960s, before her sales and chart peak came during the 1970s and continued into the 1980s. Parton's albums in the 1990s did not sell as well, but she achieved commercial success again in the new millennium and has released albums on various independent labels since 2000, including her own label, Dolly Records. She has sold more than 100 million records worldwide.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/17/Dolly_Parton_%286330904460%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dolly-parton/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vince Gill]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vince-gill/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vincent Grant Gill is an American country singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. He has achieved commercial success and fame both as frontman to the country rock band Pure Prairie League in the 1970s and as a solo artist beginning in 1983, where his talents as a vocalist and musician have placed him in high demand as a guest vocalist and a duet partner.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6b/Vince_Gill.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vince-gill/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Billy Ray Cyrus]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billy-ray-cyrus/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Billy Ray Cyrus is an American singer-songwriter and actor. He has released 16 studio albums and 53 singles since 1992, and is known for his hit single 'Achy Breaky Heart', which topped the U.S. Hot Country Songs chart and became the first single ever to achieve triple platinum status in Australia. It was also the best-selling single in the same country in 1992. Due to the song's music video, the line dance rose in popularity.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4a/Billy_Ray_Cyrus_2009_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billy-ray-cyrus/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Garth Brooks]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/garth-brooks/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Troyal Garth Brooks is an American singer and songwriter. His integration of rock and pop elements into the country genre has earned him popularity, particularly in the United States with success on the country music single and album charts, multi-platinum recordings and record-breaking live performances, while also crossing over into the mainstream pop arena.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Garth_Brooks_2019_By_Glenn_Francis.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/garth-brooks/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jordan Davis]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jordan-davis/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b2/Jordan_Davis_2019_by_Glenn_Francis.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jordan-davis/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hunter Hayes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hunter-hayes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hunter Easton Hayes is an American multi-genre singer, songwriter, record producer, and multi-instrumentalist. He is proficient at more than 30 instruments.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fd/Hunter_Hayes.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hunter-hayes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Billy Dean]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billy-dean/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Harold Dean Jr. is an American country music singer and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/42/Billy_Dean_in_1998_by_Jim_Williams.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billy-dean/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:36 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>