<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Country Pop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Country Pop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:07:39 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Garth Brooks]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/garth-brooks/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Troyal Garth Brooks is an American singer and songwriter. His integration of rock and pop elements into the country genre has earned him immense popularity in the United States. Brooks has had great success on the country single and album charts, with multi-platinum recordings and record-breaking live performances, while also crossing over into the mainstream pop arena.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Garth_Brooks_2019_By_Glenn_Francis.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/garth-brooks/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hunter Hayes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hunter-hayes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hunter Easton Hayes is an American country music singer, songwriter, and multi-instrumentalist. He is proficient at more than 30 instruments and is signed to Warner Music Nashville.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fd/Hunter_Hayes.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hunter-hayes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vince Gill]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vince-gill/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vincent Grant Gill is an American country singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. He has achieved commercial success and fame both as frontman to the country rock band Pure Prairie League in the 1970s and as a solo artist beginning in 1983, where his talents as a vocalist and musician have placed him in high demand as a guest vocalist and a duet partner.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9c/VinceGillCrossroads2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vince-gill/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Billy Ray Cyrus]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billy-ray-cyrus/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Billy Ray Cyrus is an American singer-songwriter and actor. He has released 16 studio albums and 53 singles since 1992, and is known for his number one single 'Achy Breaky Heart', which became the first single ever to achieve triple Platinum status in Australia. It was also the best-selling single in the same country in 1992. Due to the song's music video, the line dance rose in popularity.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4a/Billy_Ray_Cyrus_2009_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billy-ray-cyrus/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dolly Parton]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dolly-parton/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dolly Rebecca Parton is an American singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, actress, author, businesswoman, and humanitarian, known primarily for her work in country music. After achieving success as a songwriter for others, Parton made her album debut in 1967 with Hello, I'm Dolly. With steady success during the remainder of the 1960s, her sales and chart peak came during the 1970s and continued into the 1980s. Parton's albums in the 1990s did not sell as well, but she achieved commercial success again in the new millennium and has released albums on various independent labels since 2000, including her own label, Dolly Records.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d8/Dolly_Parton_accepting_Liseberg_Applause_Award_2010_portrait.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dolly-parton/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>