<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Whitesnake</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Whitesnake</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 22:23:47 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bernie Marsden]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bernie-marsden/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bernard John Marsden is an English rock and blues guitarist. He is primarily known for his work with Whitesnake, having written or co-written with David Coverdale many of the group's hit songs, such as 'Fool for Your Loving', 'Walking in the Shadow of the Blues', 'She's A Woman', 'Lovehunter', 'Trouble', 'Child of Babylon', 'Rough and Ready', and the multi-million selling chart-topper 'Here I Go Again'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/33/Bernie_Marsden.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bernie-marsden/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adrian Vandenberg]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adrian-vandenberg/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Adrian Vandenberg is a Dutch rock guitarist, best known for his tenure as one of the guitarists in Whitesnake during their successful late 1980s period and the band Vandenberg which he started in 1981. In 2013, Adrian formed a new band, Vandenberg's MoonKings, and recorded a new album which was released in early 2014.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/17/AdrianVandenberg.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adrian-vandenberg/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Reb Beach]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/reb-beach/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7b/Whitesnake_San_Antonio_2015_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/reb-beach/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Micky Moody]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/micky-moody/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Joseph Moody is an English guitarist, and a former member of the rock bands Juicy Lucy and Whitesnake. He was also a founder-member of Snafu. Together with his former Whitesnake colleague Bernie Marsden he founded the Moody Marsden Band, and later, The Snakes, having previously collaborated with unofficial 5th Status Quo member Bob Young in Young & Moody. Along with Marsden and ex-Whitesnake bassist, Neil Murray, he formed The Company of Snakes and M3 Classic Whitesnake with which they mainly performed early Whitesnake songs. From 2011 to 2015, Moody toured and recorded with Snakecharmer, a band he co-formed.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b2/Micky_Moody_%2814709865671%29_Cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/micky-moody/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Coverdale]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-coverdale/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Coverdale is an English rock singer-songwriter best known for his work with Whitesnake, a hard rock band he founded in 1978. Before Whitesnake, Coverdale was the lead singer of Deep Purple from 1973 to 1976, after which he established his solo career. A collaboration with Jimmy Page resulted in a 1993 album that was certified Platinum. In 2016, Coverdale was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of Deep Purple, giving one of the band's induction speeches. Coverdale is known in particular for his powerful blues-tinged voice.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/02/David_Coverdale_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-coverdale/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vivian Campbell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vivian-campbell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vivian Patrick Campbell is a Northern Irish singer-songwriter and musician. He came to prominence in the early 1980s as a member of Dio, and has been a member of Def Leppard since 1992. Campbell has also worked with Thin Lizzy, Whitesnake, Sweet Savage, Trinity, Riverdogs, and Shadow King.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/CampbellDef.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vivian-campbell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>