<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Glockenspiel</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Glockenspiel</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 12:09:49 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Mogis]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-mogis/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Riley Mogis is an American producer/engineer and multi-instrumentalist who, along with his brother A.J. Mogis, founded Presto! Recording Studios. Mogis currently runs ARC in downtown Omaha.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a9/Mikemogis.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-mogis/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jimi Hendrix]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jimi-hendrix/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Marshall 'Jimi' Hendrix was an American musician, singer, and songwriter. Although his mainstream career spanned only four years, he is widely regarded as one of the most influential electric guitarists in the history of popular music, and one of the most celebrated musicians of the 20th century. The Rock and Roll Hall of Fame describes him as 'arguably the greatest instrumentalist in the history of rock music'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/86/HendrixHoepla1967-2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jimi-hendrix/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Beck]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/beck/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Beck David Hansen is an American musician, singer, songwriter, and record producer. He rose to fame in the early 1990s with his experimental and lo-fi style, and became known for creating musical collages of wide-ranging genres. He has musically encompassed folk, funk, soul, hip hop, electronic, alternative rock, country, and psychedelia. He has released 14 studio albums, as well as several non-album singles and a book of sheet music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/31/Beck_Hansen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/beck/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>