<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Buffalo Springfield</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Buffalo Springfield</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 14:17:31 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stephen Stills]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stephen-stills/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen Arthur Stills is an American singer, songwriter, and multi-instrumentalist best known for his work with Buffalo Springfield and Crosby, Stills, Nash & Young. As both a solo act and member of two successful bands, Stills has combined record sales of over 35 million albums. He was ranked number 28 in Rolling Stone's 2003 list of 'The 100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time' and number 47 in the 2011 list. Stills became the first person to be inducted twice on the same night into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame. According to Neil Young, 'Stephen is a genius.'</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/27/Stephen_Stills_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stephen-stills/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jim Messina]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jim-messina/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Messina is an American musician, songwriter, singer, guitarist, recording engineer and record producer. He was a member of the folk rock group Buffalo Springfield, a founding member of the pioneering country rock band Poco, and half of the soft rock duo Loggins and Messina with [Kenny Loggins]].</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1b/JimMessina%28by_Scott_Dudelson%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jim-messina/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Neil Young]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Neil Percival Young is a Canadian-American singer-songwriter, musician, and activist. After embarking on a music career in Winnipeg in the 1960s, Young moved to Los Angeles, joining Buffalo Springfield with Stephen Stills, Richie Furay and others. Since the beginning of his solo career with his backing band Crazy Horse, Young has released many critically acclaimed and important albums, such as After the Gold Rush, Everybody Knows This Is Nowhere, and Harvest.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bb/Neil_Young_-_Per_Ole_Hagen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Richie Furay]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richie-furay/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul Richard Furay is an American singer, songwriter, and Rock & Roll Hall of Fame member. He is best known for forming the bands Buffalo Springfield with Stephen Stills, Neil Young, Bruce Palmer, and Dewey Martin, and Poco with Jim Messina, Timothy B. Schmit, Rusty Young, George Grantham and Randy Meisner. His best known song was 'Kind Woman,' which he wrote for his wife, Nancy.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f8/Richie_Furay_SXSW_2006_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richie-furay/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:37 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>