<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Buffalo Springfield</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Buffalo Springfield</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:06:55 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stephen Stills]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stephen-stills/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen Arthur Stills is an American singer, songwriter, and multi-instrumentalist best known for his work with Buffalo Springfield and Crosby, Stills, Nash & Young. Stills's solo career and bands have combined sales of over 35 million albums. Stills was ranked number 28 in Rolling Stone's 2003 list of 'The 100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time' and number 47 in the 2011 list. He became the first person to be inducted twice on the same night into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame. According to Neil Young, 'Stephen is a genius.'</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/27/Stephen_Stills_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stephen-stills/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Neil Young]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Neil Percival Young is a Canadian singer-songwriter. After embarking on a music career in the 1960s, he moved to Los Angeles, where he formed Buffalo Springfield with Stephen Stills, Richie Furay and others. Young had released two solo albums and three as a member of Buffalo Springfield by the time he joined Crosby, Stills & Nash in 1969. From his early solo albums and those with his backing band Crazy Horse, Young has recorded a steady stream of studio and live albums, sometimes warring with his recording company along the way.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bb/Neil_Young_-_Per_Ole_Hagen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Richie Furay]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richie-furay/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul Richard Furay is an American singer, songwriter, and Rock & Roll Hall of Fame member. He is best known for forming the bands Buffalo Springfield with Stephen Stills, Neil Young, Bruce Palmer, and Dewey Martin, and Poco with Jim Messina, Rusty Young, George Grantham and Randy Meisner. His best known song was Kind Woman, which he wrote for his wife, Nancy.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f8/Richie_Furay_SXSW_2006_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richie-furay/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>