<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Heavy Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Heavy Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 01:03:45 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Axel Rudi Pell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/axel-rudi-pell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Axel Rudi Pell is a German heavy metal guitar player who currently works as a lead guitarist for an unnamed backing band he founded as a solo work. He started off with the band Steeler (1984–88) before leaving to start his solo career in 1989. During this time, he has played with such drummers as Jörg Michael and Mike Terrana, and singers Johnny Gioeli, Jeff Scott Soto, and Rob Rock.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/ca/Axel_Rudi_Pell.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/axel-rudi-pell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Richie Faulkner]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richie-faulkner/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Ian Faulkner, is an English musician best known as one of the lead guitarists for the heavy metal band Judas Priest since 2011, replacing original member K. K. Downing. Faulkner has also performed with Lauren Harris, Christopher Lee, Voodoo Six, Dirty Deeds, and Ace Mafia.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/42/Richie_Faulkner.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richie-faulkner/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Carl Johan Grimmark]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/carl-johan-grimmark/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Carl Johan Grimmark is a Swedish guitarist. He has appeared with several influential Christian metal bands including Narnia, Saviour Machine, and Rob Rock. He recently joined the band Beautiful Sin in 2006. He also has been a special guest guitarist on fellow Narnia bandmate Christian Liljegren's side projects Divinefire and Audiovision. He recently recorded his debut solo album that is set to be titled Grimmark, where he also handles the lead vocals. Grimmark's style of playing, especially on Narnia's earlier work, is often compared to the neo-classical metal stylings of Yngwie Malmsteen, or under a more broad genre, neo-classicism.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ea/Carl_Johann_Grimmark.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/carl-johan-grimmark/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joey Vera]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joey-vera/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph 'Joey' Vera is an American heavy metal bassist who is known as a member of the heavy metal band Armored Saint and the progressive metal band Fates Warning. In 2004-2005 he replaced Frank Bello in Anthrax as the band's bassist, but did not record with them. He was also a member of Engine, recorded with Tribe After Tribe, and appears on the OSI album Free. His first solo album, A Thousand Faces, was released in 1994. His current solo project, A Chinese Firedrill, released an album titled Circles in 2007. On August 1, 2019, Joey was announced as the touring bassist for a newly reunited Mercyful Fate filling in for Timi Hansen.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2c/Joey_Vera_%28Fates_Warning%293.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joey-vera/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Rob Caggiano]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rob-caggiano/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert 'Rob' Caggiano is an American guitarist and producer. As of 2013, Caggiano is lead guitarist of the band Volbeat. Caggiano had formerly been lead guitarist of the thrash metal band Anthrax.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f5/Volbeat_-_Ilosaarirock_2016_-_07.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rob-caggiano/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Serj Tankian]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Serj Tankian is an Armenian-American musician, singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, poet and political activist. He is best known as the lead vocalist, songwriter, keyboardist, and occasional live rhythm guitarist of the band System of a Down, formed in 1994.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/69/Serj_Tankian_Spirit_of_Burgas_Bulgaria_2010_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Impellitteri]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-impellitteri/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Chris Impellitteri is the lead guitarist and founder of the heavy metal band Impellitteri. In 2008 Guitar World magazine named Chris Impellitteri as one of the fastest guitarists of all time.
In 2003, Guitar One Magazine voted Chris Impellitteri the 2nd fastest guitar shredder of all time, behind only Michael Angelo Batio; Yngwie Malmsteen was dubbed the 3rd fastest shredder.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/ff/Chris_Impellitteri.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-impellitteri/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pepper Keenan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pepper-keenan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Pepper J. Keenan, is an American guitarist and vocalist, best known for his work with heavy metal bands Corrosion of Conformity and Down. He joined Corrosion of Conformity in 1989, but did not become the lead singer until the recording of Deliverance in 1994. In 1991 he formed Down with Phil Anselmo of Pantera, Jimmy Bower of Eyehategod, and Kirk Windstein and Todd Strange of Crowbar.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a2/W0828-Hellfest2013_Down_PepperKeenan_69263.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pepper-keenan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Toshi]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/toshi/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Toshimitsu Deyama , known exclusively by his stage name Toshi, is a Japanese singer and songwriter. He is best known as the lead vocalist and a co-founder of the rock band X Japan, who rose to prominence in the late 1980s and early 1990s and are credited as founders of the Japanese visual kei movement. Toshi began an extensive solo career in 1992 before leaving X Japan at the end of 1997. By his own admission, Toshi was 'brainwashed' by a group called Home of Heart, whose leader would control his musical output for the next 12 years. In 2007, X Japan reunited and began a world tour. Toshi severed ties with Home of Heart in January 2010 and renewed his solo career. His distinctive, impassioned tenor vocals have been compared to those of Steve Perry. In Japan, he also uses the stage name Ryūgentoshi (龍玄とし).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/05/Deadpool_2_Japan_Premiere_Red_Carpet_Toshl_%2841555176645%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/toshi/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sascha Paeth]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sascha-paeth/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sascha Paeth is a German guitarist, bassist, musical producer, and mixer known for working with heavy metal bands such as Avantasia, Edguy, Angra, Shaaman, Rhapsody of Fire, Kamelot, After Forever and Epica. He owns the 'Gate Studios', Wolfsburg previously used for recordings with his former band Heavens Gate.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/73/SaschaPaeth.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sascha-paeth/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>