<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Heavy Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Heavy Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:04:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gene Simmons]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gene-simmons/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gene Klein, known professionally as Gene Simmons, is an Israeli-American musician, singer, songwriter, record producer, entrepreneur, actor, author and television personality. Also known by his stage persona The Demon, he is the bassist and co-lead singer of Kiss, the rock band he co-founded with lead singer and rhythm guitarist Paul Stanley in the early 1970s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/14/Gene_Simmons2_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gene-simmons/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Matthias Jabs]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/matthias-jabs/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Matthias Jabs is a German guitarist and songwriter. He is best known for being the lead guitarist in the hard rock band Scorpions. He has played on all Scorpions studio albums starting with Lovedrive (1979) to Return to Forever (2015). He has a music store, MJ Guitars, in Munich, Germany.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/79/20140801-150-See-Rock_Festival_2014--Matthias_Jabs.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/matthias-jabs/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Oliver Hartmann]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/oliver-hartmann/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Oliver Hartmann is a German metal vocalist, guitarist, songwriter, and producer who performed in various acts, either as guitarist, solo or choir singer. He is best known for his role as vocalist and one of the founders of the band At Vance, his own band Hartmann and his guest appearances on albums of several prominent metal bands, including Freedom Call, Edguy, Rhapsody, Genius rock opera, Iron Mask, Aina's metal opera Days of Rising Doom and the metal opera Avantasia where he participated as a vocalist in 4 albums and also as a guitarist of the live and studio line up. He is also guitarist and vocalist with the Pink-Floyd tribute band Echoes.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ac/OliverHartman.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/oliver-hartmann/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marco Hietala]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marco-hietala/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Marko Tapani 'Marco' Hietala is a Finnish heavy metal vocalist, bassist and songwriter. Internationally, he is most known as the current bassist, male vocalist and secondary composer to Tuomas Holopainen, of the symphonic metal band Nightwish. He is also the vocalist and bassist as well as composer and lyricist for the heavy metal band Tarot.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1d/Tuska_20130630_-_Nightwish_-_15.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marco-hietala/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andrew W.K.]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrew-w.k./]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Andrew Fetterly Wilkes-Krier is an American rock singer, multi-instrumentalist, and record producer. Raised in Michigan, Wilkes-Krier began his musical career in the mid-1990s performing in a number of local bands before eventually moving to New York, where he produced his first recordings under the Andrew W.K. moniker.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4e/Andrew_WK.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrew-w.k./]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Devin Townsend]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/devin-townsend/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Devin Garrett Townsend is a Canadian musician, songwriter and record producer. He founded extreme metal band Strapping Young Lad and was its primary songwriter, vocalist, and guitarist from 1994 to 2007, and has an extensive career as a solo artist.
After performing in a number of heavy metal bands in high school, Townsend was discovered by a record label in 1993 and asked to perform lead vocals on Steve Vai's album Sex & Religion. After recording and touring with Vai, Townsend was discouraged by what he found in the music industry, and vented his anger on the solo album Heavy as a Really Heavy Thing, released under the pseudonym Strapping Young Lad. He soon assembled a band under the name, and released the critically acclaimed City in 1997. Since then, he has released three more studio albums with Strapping Young Lad, along with solo material released under his own independent record label, HevyDevy Records.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e0/Devin_Townsend_Project_GRF2012-5415.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/devin-townsend/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jack Black]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-black/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Jacob Black is an American actor, comedian, singer, musician, songwriter, and YouTuber. He is known for his roles in films such as High Fidelity (2000), Shallow Hal (2001), School of Rock (2003), King Kong (2005), Tenacious D in the Pick of Destiny (2006), The Holiday (2006), the Kung Fu Panda franchise (2008–2016), Tropic Thunder (2008), Gulliver's Travels (2010), Bernie (2011), Goosebumps (2015), and Jumanji: Welcome to the Jungle (2017). For his work in School of Rock and Bernie, he gained Golden Globe nominations, and was inducted into Hollywood's Walk of Fame in 2018.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/74/Jack_Black_2_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-black/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>