<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Blue Eyed Soul</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Blue Eyed Soul</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 20:40:49 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Winehouse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Jade Winehouse was an English singer and songwriter. She was known for her deep, expressive contralto vocals and her eclectic mix of musical genres, including soul rhythm and blues, and jazz. Winehouse's debut album, Frank (2003), was a critical success in the UK and was nominated for the Mercury Prize. Her follow-up album, Back to Black (2006), led to five 2008 Grammy Awards, tying the then record for the most wins by a female artist in a single night, and made her the first British woman to win five Grammys, including three of the General Field 'Big Four' Grammy Awards: Best New Artist, Record of the Year and Song of the Year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Amy_Winehouse_f4962007_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Todd Rundgren]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Todd Harry Rundgren is an American multi-instrumentalist, singer, songwriter, and record producer who has performed a diverse range of styles as a solo artist, and as a member of the band Utopia. He is known for his sophisticated and often-unorthodox music, flamboyant stage outfits, and his later experiments with interactive entertainment. He also produced music videos, pioneered forms of multimedia, and was an early adopter and promoter of various computer technologies, such as using the Internet as a means of music distribution in the late 1990s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4b/Todd_Rundgren_performs_%40_WorkPlay.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alex Chilton]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alex-chilton/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alexander William Chilton was an American singer-songwriter, guitarist, and record producer, best known as the lead singer of the Box Tops and Big Star. Chilton's early commercial success in the 1960s as a teen vocalist for the Box Tops was never repeated in later years with Big Star and in his subsequent indie music solo career on small labels, but he drew an intense following among indie and alternative music musicians. He is frequently cited as a seminal influence by influential rock artists and bands, some of whose testimonials appeared in the 2012 documentary Big Star: Nothing Can Hurt Me.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5e/Alex_Chilton.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alex-chilton/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tom Goss]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-goss/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Patrick Goss is an American singer-songwriter and actor. Goss has self-released five studio albums, one live album, two EPs, and multiple non-album singles. He has seen commercial success with his music featured on MTV's Logo TV. He won Best Gay Musician in DC from The Washington Blade, both in 2011 and 2012. Many of Goss' songs and music videos speak to LGBT issues such as marriage equality, Don't ask, don't tell (DADT), and gay subcultures such as bears. Goss tours internationally, often playing at LGBT establishments. In 2014, Goss landed his first starring role in a feature film—the gay-themed Out to Kill.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/98/Tom_Goss_2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-goss/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vince Gill]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vince-gill/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vincent Grant Gill is an American country singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. He has achieved commercial success and fame both as frontman to the country rock band Pure Prairie League in the 1970s and as a solo artist beginning in 1983, where his talents as a vocalist and musician have placed him in high demand as a guest vocalist and a duet partner.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9c/VinceGillCrossroads2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vince-gill/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Loredana Bertè]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/loredana-bertè/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Loredana Bertè is an Italian singer. In her long career she has worked with prominent Italian songwriters such as Pino Daniele, Ivano Fossati, Mario Lavezzi, Mango and Enrico Ruggeri, among others. She has experimented with different genres, from rock to reggae, from funk to pop. Her sister Mia Martini was also a prominent singer. Bertè is known for the eccentric clothing she wears onstage for her performances. At some point in her life, she was married to the tennis great Bjorn Borg (1988-1992).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8e/Libert%C3%A8.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/loredana-bertè/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sting]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sting/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gordon Matthew Thomas Sumner, known as Sting, is an English musician and actor. He was the principal songwriter, lead singer, and bassist for the new wave rock band the Police from 1977 to 1984, and launched a solo career in 1985. He has included elements of rock, jazz, reggae, classical, new-age and worldbeat in his music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Sting_-_Deutscher_Radiopreis_Hamburg_2016_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sting/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lou Reed]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lou-reed/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lewis Allan Reed was an American musician, singer, songwriter and poet. He was the lead guitarist, singer and principal songwriter for the rock band the Velvet Underground and had a solo career that spanned five decades. The Velvet Underground was not a commercial success during its existence, but became regarded as one of the most influential bands in the history of underground and alternative rock music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c9/Lou_Reed_Malaga%2C_Spain_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lou-reed/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul Carrack]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-carrack/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul Melvyn Carrack is an English singer, songwriter, composer and multi-instrumentalist who has recorded as both a solo artist and as a member of several popular bands. The BBC dubbed Carrack 'The Man with the Golden Voice', while Record Collector remarked: 'If vocal talent equalled financial success, Paul Carrack would be a bigger name than legends such as Phil Collins or Elton John.'</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d1/Paul_Carrack_1.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-carrack/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adele]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adele/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Adele Laurie Blue Adkins is an English singer-songwriter. After graduating from the BRIT School in 2006, Adele signed a recording contract with XL Recordings. In 2007, she received the Brit Awards Critics' Choice award and won the BBC Sound of 2008 poll. Her debut album, 19, was released in 2008 to commercial and critical success. It is certified eight times platinum in the UK, and three times platinum in the US. The album contains her first song, 'Hometown Glory', written when she was 16, which is based on her home suburb of West Norwood in London. An appearance she made on Saturday Night Live in late 2008 boosted her career in the US. At the 51st Grammy Awards in 2009, Adele received the awards for Best New Artist and Best Female Pop Vocal Performance.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f3/Adele_-_Live_2016%2C_Glasgow_SSE_Hydro_03.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adele/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>