<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Blue Eyed Soul</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Blue Eyed Soul</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:52:56 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Winehouse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Jade Winehouse was an English singer and songwriter. She was known for her deep, expressive contralto vocals and her eclectic mix of musical genres, including soul rhythm and blues, and jazz. Winehouse's debut album, Frank (2003), was a critical success in the UK and was nominated for the Mercury Prize. Her follow-up album, Back to Black (2006), led to five 2008 Grammy Awards, tying the then record for the most wins by a female artist in a single night, and made her the first British woman to win five Grammys, including three of the General Field 'Big Four' Grammy Awards: Best New Artist, Record of the Year and Song of the Year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Amy_Winehouse_f4962007_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tom Goss]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-goss/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Patrick Goss is an American singer-songwriter and actor. Goss has self-released five studio albums, one live album, two EPs, and multiple non-album singles. He has seen commercial success with his music featured on MTV's Logo TV. He won Best Gay Musician in DC from The Washington Blade, both in 2011 and 2012. Many of Goss' songs and music videos speak to LGBT issues such as marriage equality, Don't ask, don't tell (DADT), and gay subcultures such as bears. Goss tours internationally, often playing at LGBT establishments. In 2014, Goss landed his first starring role in a feature film—the gay-themed Out to Kill.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/98/Tom_Goss_2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-goss/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sting]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sting/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gordon Matthew Thomas Sumner, known as Sting, is an English musician and actor. He was the principal songwriter, lead singer, and bassist for the new wave rock band the Police from 1977 to 1984, and launched a solo career in 1985. He has included elements of rock, jazz, reggae, classical, new-age and worldbeat in his music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Sting_-_Deutscher_Radiopreis_Hamburg_2016_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sting/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lou Reed]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lou-reed/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lewis Allan Reed was an American musician, singer, songwriter and poet. He was the lead guitarist, singer and principal songwriter for the rock band the Velvet Underground and had a solo career that spanned five decades. The Velvet Underground was not a commercial success during its existence, but became regarded as one of the most influential bands in the history of underground and alternative rock music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c9/Lou_Reed_Malaga%2C_Spain_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lou-reed/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adele]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adele/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Adele Laurie Blue Adkins is an English singer-songwriter. After graduating from the BRIT School in 2006, Adele signed a recording contract with XL Recordings. In 2007, she received the Brit Awards Critics' Choice award and won the BBC Sound of 2008 poll. Her debut album, 19, was released in 2008 to commercial and critical success. It is certified eight times platinum in the UK, and three times platinum in the US. The album contains her first song, 'Hometown Glory', written when she was 16, which is based on her home suburb of West Norwood in London. An appearance she made on Saturday Night Live in late 2008 boosted her career in the US. At the 51st Grammy Awards in 2009, Adele received the awards for Best New Artist and Best Female Pop Vocal Performance.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f3/Adele_-_Live_2016%2C_Glasgow_SSE_Hydro_03.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adele/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nikolai Noskov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nikolai-noskov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nikolai Ivanovich Noskov is a Russian singer and former vocalist of the hard rock band Gorky Park. Five-time winner of the Golden Gramophone. He was also a member of Москва (Moscow) ensemble in the early 1980s, in band Гран-при in 1988 just before joining Gorky Park, and much later in the 1990s in band Николай (Nikolai). Starting 1998 Noskov had a solo career releasing six solo albums. In 2015 he was jury in second season of reality TV series Glavnaya Stsena</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/32/%D0%9D%D0%B8%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%BB%D0%B0%D0%B9_%D0%9D%D0%BE%D1%81%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%B2_%D0%B2_2009_%284%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nikolai-noskov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Winwood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-winwood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen Lawrence Winwood is an English singer and musician whose genres include progressive rock, blue-eyed soul, rhythm and blues, blues rock, pop rock, and jazz. Though primarily a vocalist and keyboardist, Winwood also plays a wide variety of other instruments; on several of his solo albums he has played all instrumentation, including drums, mandolin, guitars, bass and saxophone.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/81/Steve_Winwood_scottfisher.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-winwood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jason Mraz]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-mraz/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jason Thomas Mraz is an American singer-songwriter. In 2002 he released his debut studio album, Waiting for My Rocket to Come, which contained the single 'The Remedy ' that reached #4 on the US Billboard chart. His second album, Mr. A-Z, released in 2005, peaked at number 5 on the Billboard 200 and sold over 100,000 copies in the US. In 2008 Mraz released his third studio album, We Sing. We Dance. We Steal Things. It debuted at number 3 on the Billboard 200. and was an international commercial success primarily due to the hit 'I'm Yours'. The song peaked at number 6 on the Billboard Hot 100, giving him his first top ten single, and spent a then-record 76 weeks on the Hot 100. His fourth album, Love Is a Four Letter Word, peaked at number 2 on the Billboard 200, his highest-charting album to date.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/Jason_Mraz_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-mraz/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gavin DeGraw]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gavin-degraw/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gavin Shane DeGraw is an American musician, singer, and songwriter. He rose to fame with the single 'I Don't Want to Be' from his debut album Chariot which became the theme song for the television drama series One Tree Hill. Other singles from the album included notably 'Chariot' and 'Follow Through'. His second self-titled album was released in 2008 and included the top-twenty single 'In Love with a Girl'. In 2009, DeGraw released his third album Free. His fourth album Sweeter (2011) spawned hit single 'Not Over You', as well as 'Soldier' and 'Sweeter'. In 2013, DeGraw released Make a Move, and Something Worth Saving followed in September 2016.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7c/AMAS2012.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gavin-degraw/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>