<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Fairport Convention</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Fairport Convention</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:04:33 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Swarbrick]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-swarbrick/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Cyril Eric Swarbrick was an English folk musician and singer-songwriter. He has been described by Ashley Hutchings as 'the most influential [British] fiddle player bar none' and his style has been copied or developed by almost every British and many world folk violin players who have followed him. He was one of the most highly regarded musicians produced by the second British folk revival, contributing to some of the most important groups and projects of the 1960s, and he became a much sought-after session musician, which led him throughout his career to work with many of the major figures in folk and folk rock music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/87/Dave_Swarbrick.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-swarbrick/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Pegg]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-pegg/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dave Pegg is an English multi-instrumentalist and record producer, primarily a bass guitarist. He is the longest-serving member of the British folk rock band Fairport Convention and has been bassist with a number of folk and rock groups including the Ian Campbell Folk Group and Jethro Tull.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e9/Dave_Pegg3.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-pegg/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Simon Nicol]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/simon-nicol/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Simon John Breckenridge Nicol is an English guitarist, singer, multi-instrumentalist and record producer. He was a founding member of British folk rock group Fairport Convention and is the only founding member still in the band. He has also been involved with the Albion Band and a wide range of musical projects, both as a collaborator, producer and as a solo artist. He has received several awards for his work and career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/33/Simon_Nicol.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/simon-nicol/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Maartin Allcock]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/maartin-allcock/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Maartin Allcock was an English multi-instrumentalist musician and record producer.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/42/Maartin_Allcock.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/maartin-allcock/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>