<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Guns N' Roses</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Guns N' Roses</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:08:37 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Richard Fortus]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-fortus/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Fortus is an American guitarist. He is best known as a member of the hard rock band Guns N' Roses, with whom he has been a member since 2002, and with whom he has recorded one studio album. Fortus has also collaborated extensively with The Psychedelic Furs frontman Richard Butler and fellow Guns N' Roses bandmate Frank Ferrer. Aside from lead singer Axl Rose, and keyboardist Dizzy Reed, Fortus is the longest tenured member of Guns N' Roses, having been with the band continuously since 2002.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0c/Richard_Fortus_%288056234364%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-fortus/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Duff McKagan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/duff-mckagan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Andrew 'Duff' McKagan, sometimes credited as Duff 'Rose' McKagan, is an American multi-instrumentalist, singer, songwriter and author. He is best known for his twelve-year tenure as the bassist of the hard rock band Guns N' Roses, with whom he achieved worldwide success in the late 1980s and early 1990s. McKagan rejoined the band in 2016, following their induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/77/Duff_McKagan_2012.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/duff-mckagan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gilby Clarke]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gilby-clarke/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gilbert 'Gilby' J. Clarke is an American musician, singer, songwriter and record producer best known for a 3-year tenure as the rhythm guitarist of Guns N' Roses, replacing Izzy Stradlin in 1991 during the Use Your Illusion Tour. Following his departure from the group, Clarke went on to forge a solo career as well playing guitar with Slash's Snakepit, Kat Men, Heart, Nancy Sinatra, Kathy Valentine, MC5 and forming his own group Rock Star Supernova with members of Metallica and Mötley Crüe.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Gilby_Clarke_2_2012.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gilby-clarke/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Axl Rose]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/axl-rose/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>W. Axl Rose is an American singer, songwriter, record producer and musician. He is the lead vocalist of the hard rock band Guns N' Roses, and has also been the band's sole constant member since its inception in 1985. In addition to Guns N' Roses, he also toured with Australian rock band AC/DC in 2016 during the final two legs of their Rock or Bust World Tour when Brian Johnson took a break due to hearing problems. 
Rose has been named one of the greatest singers of all time by various media outlets, including Rolling Stone and NME.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/47/GNRChorzow090718-76_%2830169034758%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/axl-rose/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Slash]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/slash/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Saul Hudson, better known by his stage name Slash, is a British–American musician and songwriter. He is the lead guitarist of the American hard rock band Guns N' Roses, with whom he achieved worldwide success in the late 1980s and early 1990s. Slash has received critical acclaim and is considered one of the greatest guitarists in rock history.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/70/Slash_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/slash/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Izzy Stradlin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/izzy-stradlin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jeffrey Dean Isbell, best known as Izzy Stradlin, is an American guitarist, singer and songwriter. He is best known as the co-founder and former rhythm guitarist of the hard rock band Guns N' Roses, which he left at the height of their fame in 1991, and with whom he recorded four studio albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ea/Izzy_010.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/izzy-stradlin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>