<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Accordion</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Accordion</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 01:13:48 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nils Lofgren]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nils-lofgren/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nils Hilmer Lofgren is an American rock musician, recording artist, songwriter, and multi-instrumentalist. Along with his work as a solo artist, he has been a member of Bruce Springsteen's E Street Band since 1984, a member of Crazy Horse, and founder/frontman of the band Grin. Lofgren was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the E Street Band in 2014.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/36/Nils_Lofgren_Olbrich.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nils-lofgren/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sheryl Crow]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sheryl-crow/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sheryl Suzanne Crow is an American musician, singer, songwriter, and actress. Her music incorporates elements of pop, rock, country, jazz, and blues. She has released ten studio albums, four compilations, two live albums, and has contributed to a number of film soundtracks. Her songs include 'All I Wanna Do', 'If It Makes You Happy', 'My Favorite Mistake' and the theme song for the 1997 James Bond film Tomorrow Never Dies. She has sold more than 50 million albums worldwide. Crow has garnered nine Grammy Awards from the National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/dc/Sheryl_Crow.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sheryl-crow/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brendon Urie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brendon-urie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brendon Boyd Urie is an American singer, songwriter, and musician, best known as the lead vocalist of Panic! at the Disco, of which he is the only member remaining.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fb/Panic_at_the_Disco_Im_Park_2016_%2811_von_11%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brendon-urie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ema Shah]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ema-shah/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ema Shah is a Kuwaiti singer, composer, pianist, guitarist, actress, writer, dancer, and director. Her father is Kuwaiti and her mother is Iranian. At the Winter Film Awards of 2014 in New Your City, she won the award for Best Music Video, and won Best Short International Film at North Hollywood Cinema Festival 2016 and received Five awards at the Best Shorts Competition of 2013 in California and won Finalist Best Short Film at the Back in the Box Competition 2013 and received six nominations at the Best Shorts Competition and one in St Albans Film Festival of 2014 in UK for her Music Video Masheenee Alcketiara. In 2012, she sang to the Kuwaiti Prime minister the prince Nasser Mohammed Al-Ahmed Al-Sabah, a Song of the Kuwaiti heritage Sung by Abdel Halim Hafez.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e2/Ema_Shah_The_Launch_Emagination_2018_Album.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ema-shah/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hunter Hayes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hunter-hayes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hunter Easton Hayes is an American country music singer, songwriter, and multi-instrumentalist. He is proficient at more than 30 instruments and is signed to Warner Music Nashville.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fd/Hunter_Hayes.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hunter-hayes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lewis Brian Hopkins Jones was an English musician, best known as the founder and original leader of the Rolling Stones. Initially a slide guitarist, Jones would go on to play a wide variety of instruments on Rolling Stones recordings and in concerts, such as rhythm and lead guitar, sitar, dulcimer, various keyboard instruments such as piano and mellotron, marimba, wind instruments such as harmonica, recorder, saxophone, as well as drums, vocals and numerous others.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6b/Brian_Jones%2C_Statesboro%2C_Georgia%2C_May_4%2C_1965_%28377872218%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Yuri Antonov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yuri-antonov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Yuri Mikhailovich Antonov is a Soviet and Russian composer, singer and musician, People's Artist of Russia (1997). He is also the Distinguished performer of arts of the Russian Federation (Russia) and the Distinguished artist of the Chechnya-Ingushetia ASSR (1983).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6d/Yuri_Antonov_%28musician%29_%282015-12-10%29_04.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yuri-antonov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Will Tura]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/will-tura/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>
Arthur Achiel Albert, Knight Blanckaert, known by his stage name Will Tura, is a Belgian artist famous in Flanders and the Netherlands. Tura is a singer, musician, composer and songwriter. He is married to Jenny Swinnen, with whom he has a son David and a daughter Sandy Tura.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5c/Tura675.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/will-tura/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Dassin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-dassin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Ira Dassin was an American-born French singer-songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c9/Joe_Dassin_1970.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-dassin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pete Droge]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-droge/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Pete Droge is an American alternative/folk rock musician from Vashon Island in Washington State's Puget Sound.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4a/Pete_Droge_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-droge/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>