<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Thrash Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Thrash Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 01:13:47 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jason Newsted]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-newsted/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jason Curtis Newsted is an American metal musician, known for being the bassist of the band Metallica from October 1986 until his sudden departure in January 2001.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/68/13-06-09_RaR_Newsted_10.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-newsted/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robb Flynn]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robb-flynn/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Conrad 'Robb' Flynn is the lead vocalist and rhythm guitarist for the heavy metal band Machine Head. Flynn formed the band along with Adam Duce, Logan Mader and Tony Costanza after leaving Bay Area thrash band Vio-Lence.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/RobbFlynn2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robb-flynn/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shagrath]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shagrath/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stian Tomt Thoresen, known professionally as Shagrath, is a Norwegian musician best known as the vocalist, founding member and multi-instrumentalist of the band Dimmu Borgir.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/10/Dimmu_Borgir_Paris_041007_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shagrath/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[James Hetfield]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-hetfield/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Alan Hetfield is an American musician and songwriter best known for being the co-founder, lead vocalist/rhythm guitarist and main songwriter for the American heavy metal band Metallica. Hetfield is mainly known for his intricate rhythm playing, but occasionally performs lead guitar duties and solos, both live and in the studio. Hetfield co-founded Metallica in October 1981 after answering an advertisement by drummer Lars Ulrich in the Los Angeles newspaper The Recycler. Metallica has won nine Grammy Awards and released ten studio albums, three live albums, four extended plays and 24 singles.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fd/JamesHetfield2012.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-hetfield/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dan Spitz]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dan-spitz/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Daniel Alan Spitz is an American musician and watchmaker best known for his work as the lead guitarist of the American heavy metal band Anthrax from 1983 to 1995 and from 2005 to 2008. With Anthrax, Spitz was nominated for three Grammy awards and earned several platinum albums. Spitz also founded the Christian music group Red Lamb, which was known for lyrics on autism awareness. Spitz has earned Swiss and American degrees in luxury mechanical watchmaking and micro-mechanical engineering, certified as watchmaker instructor for the North American operations of Swiss watch company Chopard.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Dan_Spitz.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dan-spitz/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Eric Peterson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eric-peterson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Eric Peterson is an American guitarist, best known as a member of the American thrash metal band Testament and is the only remaining original member left in the band, which first started in 1982 under the name Legacy. He and vocalist Chuck Billy are the only members to appear on all of the band's studio albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cb/Testament%2C_Skogsr%C3%B6jet_2012_3.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eric-peterson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jeff Loomis]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeff-loomis/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jeff Loomis is an American musician, best known for his role as lead guitarist in the progressive metal band Nevermore. In November 2014, it was announced he was to be the new guitarist for Swedish melodic death metal band Arch Enemy.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cb/Nevermore_Summerbreeze2007_02.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeff-loomis/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roy Mayorga]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-mayorga/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roy Maurice Mayorga is an American musician, best known as the drummer for the American heavy metal bands Hellyeah and Stone Sour. He is of Ecuadorian and Cuban descent.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/dc/Roy_Mayorga_at_the_Rockstar_Uproar_Festival.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-mayorga/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andy Sneap]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andy-sneap/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Andy Sneap is a British musician, songwriter, guitar player and record producer with over 100 albums to his name, most of which have been produced at his Backstage Recording studios in rural Derbyshire. He received a Swedish Grammi for his mix on Opeth's Deliverance album, whilst Killswitch Engage's 2014 album, Disarm The Descent was US Grammy nominated. As a performer, he was first known as the guitar player of thrash metal band Sabbat, and also recently guitarist in the second incarnation of the heavy metal band Hell. In 2018, he joined Judas Priest as a touring guitarist following Glenn Tipton's announcement that he was diagnosed with Parkinson's disease and that he would no longer be able to tour.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/84/Andy_Sneap_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andy-sneap/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jeffrey Dunn]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeffrey-dunn/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jeff 'Mantas' Dunn is a British guitarist best known as one of the founder members of seminal thrash/speed metal band Venom, with which he played as a guitarist from 1979 to 1985 and 1989 to 2002.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1b/Mantas_in_London%2C_2014.02.19.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeffrey-dunn/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>