<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Thrash Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Thrash Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:08:37 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kirk Hammett]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kirk-hammett/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kirk Lee Hammett is an American musician who has been lead guitarist and a contributing songwriter for the heavy metal band Metallica since 1983. Before joining Metallica he formed and named the band Exodus. In 2003, Hammett was ranked 11th on Rolling Stone's list of The 100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time. In 2009, Hammett was ranked number 15 in Joel McIver's book The 100 Greatest Metal Guitarists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b8/Kirk_Hammett_by_Gage_Skidmore.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kirk-hammett/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Piotr Wiwczarek]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/piotr-wiwczarek/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Piotr Paweł Wiwczarek, also known as Peter, is a Polish musician who is the vocalist and lead guitarist for the death metal band Vader, as the only constant member of the band since its inception. He has also collaborated with Kazimierz 'Para' Paraszczuk on his tribute album, Bandid Rockin', and is the producer of several of Vader's releases. He is also the founder and guitarist of a side-project, named Panzer X.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/65/Piotr_Wiwczarek.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/piotr-wiwczarek/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Eric Meyer]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eric-meyer/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Eric Meyer is an American musician who is best known as the guitarist for the Los Angeles based thrash metal band Dark Angel, which he joined in 1984, and played on all of their albums from We Have Arrived onwards.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/05/Dark_Angel_2014_2014-05-08_14-18.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eric-meyer/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jeff Hanneman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeff-hanneman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jeffrey John Hanneman was an American musician, best known as a founding member of the American thrash metal band Slayer. Hanneman contributed both lyrical and musical material to every Slayer album up until his death in 2013 and wrote the songs 'Raining Blood', 'War Ensemble,' 'South of Heaven,' 'Seasons in the Abyss,' and 'Angel of Death,' all of which have been played at almost every live Slayer performance after their respective compositions. He had his own signature guitar, the ESP Jeff Hanneman Signature model.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d4/Jeff_Hanneman_f9e_o.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeff-hanneman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jason Newsted]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-newsted/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jason Curtis Newsted is an American metal musician, known for being the bassist of the band Metallica from October 1986 until his sudden departure in January 2001.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/68/13-06-09_RaR_Newsted_10.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-newsted/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lee Altus]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lee-altus/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lee Altus is a Russian American musician and heavy metal guitarist. Altus first came to public attention in the mid-1980s with his original band, Heathen. He served as the principal songwriter and a founding member of Heathen playing on all three of their LP's, Breaking The Silence, Victims of Deception and The Evolution of Chaos. In 1990, Altus was considered for the position in Megadeth vacated by Jeff Young, but declined, and the job was given instead to Marty Friedman. He later became a permanent member of the band Exodus.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/54/W0847-Hellfest2013_Heaven_g2_66918.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lee-altus/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robb Flynn]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robb-flynn/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Conrad 'Robb' Flynn is the lead vocalist and rhythm guitarist for the heavy metal band Machine Head. Flynn formed the band along with Adam Duce, Logan Mader and Tony Costanza after leaving Bay Area thrash band Vio-Lence.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/RobbFlynn2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robb-flynn/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Olve Eikemo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/olve-eikemo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Olve Eikemo, better known by his stage name Abbath Doom Occulta or simply Abbath, is a Norwegian musician best known as a founding member of the black metal band Immortal. Before founding Immortal, Abbath performed with Old Funeral alongside future Immortal member Demonaz. While working with Old Funeral, he also joined Demonaz's band Amputation which later became Immortal. He also plays bass in Demonaz's eponymous project.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/AbbathWOA2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/olve-eikemo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shagrath]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shagrath/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stian Tomt Thoresen, known professionally as Shagrath, is a Norwegian musician best known as the vocalist, founding member and multi-instrumentalist of the band Dimmu Borgir.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/10/Dimmu_Borgir_Paris_041007_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shagrath/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[James Hetfield]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-hetfield/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Alan Hetfield is an American musician and songwriter best known for being the co-founder, lead vocalist/rhythm guitarist and main songwriter for the American heavy metal band Metallica. Hetfield is mainly known for his intricate rhythm playing, but occasionally performs lead guitar duties and solos, both live and in the studio. Hetfield co-founded Metallica in October 1981 after answering an advertisement by drummer Lars Ulrich in the Los Angeles newspaper The Recycler. Metallica has won nine Grammy Awards and released ten studio albums, three live albums, four extended plays and 24 singles.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fd/JamesHetfield2012.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-hetfield/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>