<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Teen Pop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Teen Pop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 12:09:49 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Jonas]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-jonas/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Adam Jonas is an American singer, songwriter, actor, and dancer. He rose to fame as a member of the pop rock band the Jonas Brothers, alongside his brothers Kevin and Nick. The group released their debut studio album It's About Time through the Columbia label in 2006, which failed to achieve commercial success. After signing with Hollywood Records, the group released their self-titled second studio album in 2007, which became their breakthrough record. The band became prominent figures on the Disney Channel during this time, gaining a large following through the network: they appeared in the widely successful musical television film Camp Rock (2008) and its sequel Camp Rock 2: The Final Jam (2010) as well as two of their own series, Jonas Brothers: Living the Dream (2008–2010) and Jonas (2009–2010).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a8/Joe_Jonas_2012_%28Straighten_Crop%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-jonas/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Demi Lovato]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/demi-lovato/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Demetria Devonne Lovato is an American singer, songwriter, and actor. After appearing on the children's television series Barney & Friends (2002–2004), Lovato rose to prominence for their role as Mitchie Torres in the musical television film Camp Rock (2008) and its sequel Camp Rock 2: The Final Jam (2010); the former film's soundtrack contained 'This Is Me', Lovato's debut single and duet with Joe Jonas, which peaked at number nine on the Billboard Hot 100.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/66/Demi_Lovato_2015.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/demi-lovato/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>