<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Punk Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Punk Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:25:03 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Alvin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Albert Alvin is an American singer-songwriter, guitarist, music producer and poet. He is a former and founding member of the roots rock band the Blasters. Alvin has recorded and performed as a solo artist since the late 1980s and has been involved in various side projects and collaborations. He has had brief stints as a member of the bands X and the Knitters.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Dave_Alvin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ida Maria]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ida-maria/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ida Maria Børli Sivertsen, better known simply as Ida Maria, is a Norwegian musician and songwriter. Her first album, Fortress Round My Heart, was released in 2008. In November 2010, she released her second album Katla in Norway; the album was released internationally on 7 June 2011. In August 2013, Maria digitally released her third album Love Conquers All in Norway.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b7/Ida_Maria%2C_2008_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ida-maria/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Keith Levene]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/keith-levene/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Julian Keith Levene is an English musician, who was a founding member of both The Clash and Public Image Ltd (PiL).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fb/Keith_Levene_Metal_Box_in_Dub.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/keith-levene/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Noodles]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/noodles/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kevin John Wasserman is the lead guitarist and backing vocalist for The Offspring.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/94/Noodles.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/noodles/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tim Armstrong]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tim-armstrong/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Timothy Ross Armstrong is an American musician, singer, songwriter, producer, and actor. He is best known as the singer/guitarist for the punk rock band Rancid and hip hop/punk rock supergroup Transplants. Prior to forming Rancid, Armstrong was in the influential ska punk band Operation Ivy. In 1997, along with Brett Gurewitz of the band Bad Religion and owner of Epitaph Records, Armstrong founded Hellcat Records. In 2012, through his website, Armstrong started releasing music that influenced him, along with stripped-down cover songs of his own work under the name Tim Timebomb. He has released at least one song per week since late 2012. Armstrong is also a songwriter for other artists. Armstrong won a Grammy Award for his work with Jimmy Cliff and Pink, and has also worked with Joe Walsh.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/17/TimLiveSept2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tim-armstrong/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bob Mould]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-mould/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Arthur Mould is an American musician, principally known for his work as guitarist, vocalist, and songwriter for alternative rock bands Hüsker Dü in the 1980s and Sugar in the 1990s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8e/Bob_Mould.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-mould/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Fermin Muguruza]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fermin-muguruza/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Fermin Muguruza is a Basque rock musician, singer, songwriter, producer, record label manager, and co-founder of the ska punk band Kortatu, active from 1983 to 1988, and of the crossover group Negu Gorriak, active from 1990 to 1996.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fe/FerminMuguruza.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fermin-muguruza/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Billy Idol]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billy-idol/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Michael Albert Broad, known professionally as Billy Idol, is an English musician, singer, songwriter, and actor. He first achieved fame in the 1970s emerging from the London punk rock scene as a member of Generation X. Subsequently, he embarked on a solo career which led to international recognition and made Idol a lead artist during the MTV-driven 'Second British Invasion' in the United States. The name 'Billy Idol' was inspired by a schoolteacher's description of him as 'idle'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1a/Billy_Idol.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billy-idol/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Ness]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-ness/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael James Ness is an American musician and producer who is the lead guitarist, vocalist and songwriter for the punk rock band Social Distortion, which was formed in 1978.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/08/Mike_Ness_013.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-ness/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Greg Graffin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/greg-graffin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gregory Walter Graffin, Ph.D is an American punk rock singer-songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, college lecturer, and author. He is most recognized as the lead vocalist, songwriter, and only constant member of the noted Los Angeles band Bad Religion, which he co-founded in 1980. He also embarked on a solo career in 1997, when he released the album American Lesion. His follow-up album, Cold as the Clay was released nine years later. Graffin obtained his PhD in the history of science at Cornell University and has lectured courses in natural sciences at both the University of California, Los Angeles and at Cornell University.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/18/Greg_Graffin-Starland_BallRoom-2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/greg-graffin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>