<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » The Modern Lovers</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » The Modern Lovers</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 23:44:26 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jerry Harrison]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jerry-harrison/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jeremiah Griffin Harrison is an American songwriter, musician, producer, and entrepreneur. He began his professional music career as a member of the cult band the Modern Lovers before becoming keyboardist and guitarist for the new wave band Talking Heads. In 2002, Harrison was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of Talking Heads. Since the Talking Heads went on indefinite hiatus in 1991, he has focused more on producing other bands, a role he started while still with the Talking Heads, beginning with the Violent Femmes third album The Blind Leading the Naked in 1986. During the 1990s, he produced a number of hit albums for bands such as Live, The Verve Pipe, Big Head Todd and the Monsters, and Kenny Wayne Shepherd among others. He has also released three albums of solo music and has participated in a number of partial reunions of the Talking Heads. In 1999, he helped found the online music community GarageBand.com.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f5/Jerry-Harrison.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jerry-harrison/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jonathan Richman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jonathan-richman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jonathan Michael Richman is an American singer, songwriter and guitarist. In 1970, he founded the Modern Lovers, an influential proto-punk band. Since the mid-1970s, Richman has worked either solo or with low-key acoustic and electric backing. He now plays only acoustic to protect his hearing. He is known for his wide-eyed, unaffected, and childlike outlook, and music that, while rooted in rock and roll, is influenced by music from around the world.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/32/2014JonathanRichman.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jonathan-richman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>