<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Black Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Black Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 19:48:27 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[ICS Vortex]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ics-vortex/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Simen Hestnæs, better known by his stage name I.C.S. Vortex or simply Vortex, is a Norwegian musician. He is the vocalist of the similarly named band ICS Vortex, the avant-garde metal band Arcturus, and the doom metal band Lamented Souls. He is also the vocalist and bass guitarist to the progressive black metal band Borknagar, and the former bass guitarist and backing vocalist for the Norwegian symphonic black metal band Dimmu Borgir.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/89/Dimmu_Borgir_Paris_041007_09.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ics-vortex/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Necrobutcher]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/necrobutcher/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jørn Stubberud is a Norwegian musician best known as the bassist in the black metal band Mayhem under the stage name Necrobutcher. He is one of Mayhem's founding members, along with Euronymous, Manheim and Messiah. He is the band's only remaining original member, as Messiah and Manheim left Mayhem, respectively, in 1986 and 1988, and Euronymous was murdered in 1993. He has also played in other bands, including L.E.G.O., Kvikksølvguttene, Bloodthorn, and Checker Patrol.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f9/Mayhem_-_Jalometalli_2008_-_19.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/necrobutcher/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tchort]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tchort/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Terje Vik Schei, better known by his stage name Tchort, is a Norwegian musician. He is known for his time spent playing bass for the black metal band Emperor and for leading the progressive metal band Green Carnation. He has also played with Carpathian Forest and Blood Red Throne, Satyricon and Einherjer.
Tchort is known to be married and to have a son and a daughter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3e/Carpathian_Forest_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tchort/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sakis Tolis]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sakis-tolis/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Athanasios 'Sakis' Tolis is a Greek musician best known as the vocalist and guitarist of Rotting Christ. He is also known as Necromayhem. He has recently produced some of the band's albums and contributed as session keyboardist. Sakis has also provided guest vocals and guitars for a number of bands, for example providing guest backing vocals on the track Mocking Modesty on the Nightrage album Wearing a Martyr's Crown.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8e/Sakis_Tolis%2C_Leeuwarden%2C_2010.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sakis-tolis/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Infernus]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/infernus/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roger Tiegs, better known by his stage name Infernus, is a Norwegian black metal musician and Satanist. He is the sole founding member and chief ideologist of the Norwegian black metal band Gorgoroth, which was formed in 1992, as well as the founder and head of Forces of Satan Records. He is mainly a guitarist, but has also participated as bassist, drummer and vocalist on several recordings released both by Gorgoroth and other bands.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/33/Gorgoroth_Infernus.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/infernus/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Olve Eikemo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/olve-eikemo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Olve Eikemo, better known by his stage name Abbath Doom Occulta or simply Abbath, is a Norwegian musician best known as a founding member of the black metal band Immortal. Before founding Immortal, Abbath performed with Old Funeral alongside future Immortal member Demonaz. While working with Old Funeral, he also joined Demonaz's band Amputation which later became Immortal. He also plays bass in Demonaz's eponymous project.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/AbbathWOA2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/olve-eikemo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adam Darski]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adam-darski/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Adam 'Nergal' Darski is a Polish musician and television personality, best known for being the frontman for the blackened death metal band Behemoth.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e6/Behemoth_Hellfest_20062010_02.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adam-darski/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jeffrey Dunn]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeffrey-dunn/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jeff 'Mantas' Dunn is a British guitarist best known as one of the founder members of seminal thrash/speed metal band Venom, with which he played as a guitarist from 1979 to 1985 and 1989 to 2002.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1b/Mantas_in_London%2C_2014.02.19.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeffrey-dunn/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sigurd Wongraven]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sigurd-wongraven/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Satyr is the vocalist, lead and rhythm guitarist, bassist, and keyboardist for the Norwegian black metal band Satyricon.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4e/Satyricon_%40_Elbriot_2018_15.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sigurd-wongraven/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Rune Eriksen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rune-eriksen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Rune Eriksen is a Norwegian Spellemann award-winning musician and composer. He is best known as the former guitarist in the black metal band Mayhem under the stage name Blasphemer, which he took from a Sodom song. He joined the band in October 1994, but departed in late 2008. He currently plays in Aura Noir, Earth Electric, and the multinational bands Twilight Of The Gods and Vltimas, the latter a supergroup of sorts with vocalist David Vincent, and drummer Flo Mounier of Cryptopsy. Rune has also made guest appearances with Absu, Negură Bunget, and Root. His former bands and projects are Nader Sadek, Mezzerschmitt, and the Portuguese gothic doom band Ava Inferi. He resides in Portugal.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fd/Blasphemer.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rune-eriksen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>