<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Grateful Dead</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Grateful Dead</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 14:17:32 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jerry Garcia]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jerry-garcia/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jerome John Garcia was an American singer-songwriter and guitarist, best known for being a principal songwriter, the lead guitarist and a vocalist with the rock band the Grateful Dead, of which he was a founding member and which came to prominence during the counterculture of the 1960s. Although he disavowed the role, Garcia was viewed by many as the leader of the band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e8/Grateful_Dead_-_Jerry_Garcia.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jerry-garcia/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bob Weir]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-weir/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Hall Weir is an American musician and songwriter best known as a founding member of the rock band Grateful Dead. After the Grateful Dead disbanded in 1995, Weir performed with The Other Ones, later known as The Dead, together with other former members of the Grateful Dead. Weir also founded and played in several other bands during and after his career with the Grateful Dead, including Kingfish, the Bob Weir Band, Bobby and the Midnites, Scaring the Children, RatDog, and Furthur, which he co-led with former Grateful Dead bassist Phil Lesh. In 2015, Weir, along with former Grateful Dead members Mickey Hart and Bill Kreutzmann, joined with Grammy-winning singer/guitarist John Mayer, bassist Oteil Burbridge, and keyboardist Jeff Chimenti to form the band Dead & Company. The band remains active.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/81/Bob_Weir.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-weir/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:36 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>