<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Pop Punk</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Pop Punk</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 19:48:27 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ryan Key]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ryan-key/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Ryan Key is an American rock musician. He is best known as the former lead singer, songwriter, and rhythm guitarist of the former pop punk band Yellowcard. He is currently the owner/operator of a recording studio in Franklin, Tennessee, called The Lone Tree Recordings. He is currently touring and writing music under his full name, William Ryan Key, as a solo acoustic act. He has recently toured as guitarist/vocalist/keyboardist for New Found Glory. In late 2018, he played as a supporting act on Mayday Parade's Sunnyland tour along with This Wild Life.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/35/Ryan_Key_of_Yellowcard.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ryan-key/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Boli Joe Armstrong]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billie-joe-armstrong/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Billie Joe Armstrong is an American singer, songwriter, musician, record producer, and actor. Armstrong serves as the lead vocalist, primary songwriter, and lead guitarist of the punk rock band Green Day, co-founded with Mike Dirnt. He is also a guitarist and vocalist for the punk rock band Pinhead Gunpowder, and provides lead vocals for Green Day's side projects Foxboro Hot Tubs, The Network, and The Longshot.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/19/Billie_Joe_Armstrong_at_mic_in_Cardiff.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billie-joe-armstrong/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dougie Poynter]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dougie-poynter/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dougie Lee Poynter is an English musician, songwriter, fashion model, clothing designer, author, actor and philanthropist. He is the bassist and youngest member of the pop rock band McFly, as well as bassist for A. In 2018, he formed the rock band INK. with fellow members, Todd Dorigo, vocals and guitar, and Corey Alexander, drums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e3/McFly_Belfast_033.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dougie-poynter/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pete Shelley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-shelley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Pete Shelley was an English singer, songwriter and guitarist. He formed early punk band Buzzcocks with Howard Devoto in 1976, and became the lead singer and guitarist in 1977 when Devoto left. The group released their biggest hit 'Ever Fallen in Love ' in 1978. It broke up in 1981 and reformed at the end of the decade. Shelley also had a solo career; his song 'Homosapien' charted in the US in 1981.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/05/Pete-shelley.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-shelley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Farin Urlaub]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/farin-urlaub/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jan Vetter, better known as Farin Urlaub, is a German musician and songwriter. He is best known as the guitarist/vocalist for the German punk rock band Die Ärzte. Vetter has been a solo artist since 2001, touring with his band, the Farin Urlaub Racing Team. His releases starting in 2006 are credited to the band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/86/FarinUrlaub_credit_JoergSteinmetz.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/farin-urlaub/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Deryck Whibley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/deryck-whibley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Deryck Jason Whibley, nicknamed Bizzy D, is a Canadian musician, singer, songwriter, and record producer, best known for his work as the lead vocalist, rhythm guitarist, keyboardist, main songwriter, and producer of the rock band Sum 41.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8b/Sum41_Deryck_Whibley.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/deryck-whibley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tyson Ritter]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tyson-ritter/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tyson Jay Ritter is an American singer, songwriter, musician, actor, and model. He is best known as the lead vocalist, bassist, pianist, and songwriter of the multi-platinum selling American alternative rock band the All-American Rejects. As an actor, Ritter appeared as Dane on Amazon Video's Betas, recurred as rock musician Oliver Rome on NBC's Parenthood, and has had supporting roles in films, including The House Bunny (2008) and Miss You Already (2015). In 2018 and 2019, Ritter played recurring characters on two television series on AMC, Preacher and Lodge 49.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d1/TYSON.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tyson-ritter/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Patrick Stump]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/patrick-stump/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Patrick Martin Stumph, known professionally as Patrick Vaughn Stump, is an American musician, singer, songwriter, record producer, actor and film composer. He is the lead vocalist and rhythm guitarist of the rock band Fall Out Boy, originally from Wilmette, Illinois.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/56/Patrick_Stump_Infinity.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/patrick-stump/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jaret Reddick]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jaret-reddick/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jaret Ray Reddick is an American musician, singer, songwriter, composer, podcaster, actor, and voice actor, best known as the lead vocalist, guitarist, and primary songwriter of the rock band Bowling for Soup. His primary guitar is a Music Man Axis that has a Miller Lite design on it; his former primary guitar until 2018 was similarly a Music Man Axis with a flag of Texas design on it.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4c/Jaret_Reddick_2015.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jaret-reddick/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chad Gilbert]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chad-gilbert/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Chad Everett Gilbert is an American musician and record producer. He is a founding member of the rock band New Found Glory, for whom he plays lead guitar, sings backing vocals, and composes music. He was also the lead vocalist for New Found Glory's now-defunct side-project, International Superheroes of Hardcore. Additionally, Gilbert was the vocalist for the hardcore punk band Shai Hulud between 1995 and 1998, and he rejoined the band in 2012.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/71/ChadGilbert_NFG_290510.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chad-gilbert/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>