<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Pop Punk</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Pop Punk</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 21:59:13 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pete Shelley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-shelley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Pete Shelley was an English singer, songwriter and guitarist. He formed early punk band Buzzcocks with Howard Devoto in 1976, and became the lead singer and guitarist in 1977 when Devoto left. The group released their biggest hit 'Ever Fallen in Love ' in 1978. The band broke up in 1981 and reformed at the end of the decade. Shelley also had a solo career; his song 'Homosapien' charted in the US in 1981.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/05/Pete-shelley.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-shelley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Cassadee Pope]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/cassadee-pope/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Cassadee Blake Pope is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. Pope was the lead vocalist of the rock band Hey Monday, with whom she released two studio albums and three EPs. Pope embarked on a solo career in early 2012, and released the EP Cassadee Pope in May 2012. She took part in the third season of The Voice and became the first female winner on December 18, 2012. Her debut solo country album, Frame by Frame, was released on October 8, 2013 to a top 10 Billboard 200 charting. It debuted at No. 1 on Top Country Albums, with 43,000 copies sold in its first week.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ab/Cassadeepope2010.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/cassadee-pope/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tyson Ritter]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tyson-ritter/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tyson Jay Ritter is an American singer, songwriter, musician, actor, and model. He is best known as the lead vocalist, bassist, pianist, and songwriter of the multi-platinum selling American alternative rock band the All-American Rejects. As an actor, Ritter appeared as Dane on Amazon Video's Betas, recurred as rock musician Oliver Rome on NBC's Parenthood, and has had supporting roles in films, including The House Bunny (2008) and Miss You Already (2015). In 2018, Ritter played recurring characters on two television series on AMC, Preacher and Lodge 49. Ritter joined the main cast of Preacher for its final season in 2019.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d1/TYSON.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tyson-ritter/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dougie Poynter]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dougie-poynter/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dougie Lee Poynter is an English musician, songwriter, fashion model, aspiring clothing designer, children's author and amateur actor. He is the bassist of the pop rock band McFly.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e3/McFly_Belfast_033.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dougie-poynter/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Deryck Whibley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/deryck-whibley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Deryck Jason Whibley, nicknamed Bizzy D, is a Canadian musician, singer, songwriter, and record producer, best known for his work as the lead vocalist, rhythm guitarist, keyboardist, main songwriter, producer, and only constant member of the rock band Sum 41.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8b/Sum41_Deryck_Whibley.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/deryck-whibley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Patrick Stump]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/patrick-stump/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Patrick Martin Stumph, known professionally as Patrick Vaughn Stump, is an American musician, singer, songwriter, record producer, actor and film composer. He is the lead vocalist and rhythm guitarist of the rock band Fall Out Boy, originally from Wilmette, Illinois.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/56/Patrick_Stump_Infinity.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/patrick-stump/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chad Gilbert]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chad-gilbert/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Chad Everett Gilbert is an American musician and record producer. He is a founding member of the rock band New Found Glory, for whom he plays lead guitar, sings backing vocals, and composes music. He was also the lead vocalist for the band's now-defunct side-project, International Superheroes of Hardcore. Additionally, Gilbert was the vocalist for the hardcore punk band Shai Hulud between 1995 and 1998, and from 2012 to 2013.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/71/ChadGilbert_NFG_290510.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chad-gilbert/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pierre Bouvier]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pierre-bouvier/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Pierre Charles Bouvier is a Canadian musician, singer, songwriter, and actor best known for being the lead vocalist and bassist of the rock band Simple Plan.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/75/Pierre-SP-Beijing.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pierre-bouvier/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ryan Key]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ryan-key/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Ryan Key is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. He is best known as the former lead vocalist and rhythm guitarist of the former pop punk band Yellowcard. He is currently the owner/operator of a recording studio in Franklin, Tennessee, called The Lone Tree Recordings. He is currently writing music under his full name, William Ryan Key, as a solo acoustic act and electronic act. He is also one half of JEDHA, an electronic duo consisting of himself and former lead guitarist of Yellowcard, Ryan Mendez. He has recently toured as guitarist/vocalist/keyboardist for New Found Glory. In late 2018, he played as a supporting act on Mayday Parade's Sunnyland tour along with This Wild Life. As of 2021, he is live streaming his songwriting process live on Twitch full-time.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/35/Ryan_Key_of_Yellowcard.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ryan-key/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Billie Joe Armstrong]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billie-joe-armstrong/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Billie Joe Armstrong is an American singer, songwriter, musician, actor, and record producer. He is best known as the lead vocalist, primary songwriter, and lead guitarist of the rock band Green Day, which he co-founded with Mike Dirnt in 1985. He is also a guitarist and vocalist for the punk rock band Pinhead Gunpowder, and provides lead vocals for Green Day's side projects Foxboro Hot Tubs, The Network, The Longshot, and The Coverups.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/Billie_Joe.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billie-joe-armstrong/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>