<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Viola</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Viola</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:08:39 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Swarbrick]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-swarbrick/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Cyril Eric Swarbrick was an English folk musician and singer-songwriter. He has been described by Ashley Hutchings as 'the most influential [British] fiddle player bar none' and his style has been copied or developed by almost every British and many world folk violin players who have followed him. He was one of the most highly regarded musicians produced by the second British folk revival, contributing to some of the most important groups and projects of the 1960s, and he became a much sought-after session musician, which led him throughout his career to work with many of the major figures in folk and folk rock music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/87/Dave_Swarbrick.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-swarbrick/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adele]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adele/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Adele Laurie Blue Adkins, is an English singer-songwriter. After graduating from the BRIT School in 2006, Adele signed a recording contract with XL Recordings. In 2007, she received the Brit Awards Critics' Choice Award and won the BBC Sound of 2008 poll. Her debut album, 19, was released in 2008. It is certified 8× platinum in the UK and triple platinum in the US. The album contains her first song, 'Hometown Glory', written when she was 16, which is based on her home suburb of West Norwood in London. An appearance she made on Saturday Night Live in late 2008 boosted her career in the US. At the 2009 Grammy Awards, Adele won the awards for Best New Artist and Best Female Pop Vocal Performance.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7c/Adele_2016.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adele/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>