<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Percussion Instrument</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Percussion Instrument</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 20:58:33 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tommy Lee]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tommy-lee/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Lee Bass is an American musician and founding member of the heavy metal band Mötley Crüe. As well as being the band's long-term drummer, Lee founded rap metal band Methods of Mayhem, and has pursued solo musical projects.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/24/Tommy_Lee_2012.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tommy-lee/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paulo Jr.]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paulo-jr./]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paulo Xisto Pinto Júnior is a Brazilian musician best known as the bassist for heavy metal band Sepultura. He joined Sepultura after Roberto Raffan left the band in 1984, becoming Sepultura's second bassist. Although no original members are left in Sepultura, Pinto is the longest remaining member of Sepultura despite never performing on any album until Chaos A.D. (1993).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c4/Nova_Rock_2014_-_Paulo_Xisto_Pinto_Jr..JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paulo-jr./]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jandek]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jandek/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jandek is an American lo-fi music project centered around Sterling Smith, though the pseudonym is often used to refer to Smith directly in the context of this work. Their output is distributed by Corwood Industries, a Houston, Texas record label which is also operated by Smith.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0d/Jandek_June2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jandek/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mariusz Duda]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mariusz-duda/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Mariusz Duda is a Polish musician and composer best known as the bassist and vocalist in the band Riverside.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/Mariusz_Duda_%28Riverside%292.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mariusz-duda/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Iggy Pop]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/iggy-pop/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Newell Osterberg Jr., known professionally as Iggy Pop, is an American musician, singer, lyricist, record producer and actor. Designated the 'Godfather of Punk', he was the vocalist and lyricist of influential proto-punk band The Stooges, who were formed in 1967 and have disbanded and reunited multiple times since.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4d/IggyChesterRocks.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/iggy-pop/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul McCartney]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir James Paul McCartney is an English singer, songwriter, musician, and record and film producer who gained worldwide fame as co-lead vocalist and bassist for the Beatles. His songwriting partnership with John Lennon remains the most successful in history. After the group disbanded in 1970, he pursued a solo career and formed the band Wings with his first wife, Linda, and Denny Laine.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/ACL18051018-122_%2843716152470%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Todd Rundgren]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Todd Harry Rundgren is an American multi-instrumentalist, singer, songwriter, and record producer who has performed a diverse range of styles as a solo artist and as a member of the band Utopia. He is known for his sophisticated and often unorthodox music, his occasionally lavish stage shows, and his later experiments with interactive entertainment. He also produced music videos and was an early adopter and promoter of various computer technologies, such as using the Internet as a means of music distribution in the late 1990s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4b/Todd_Rundgren_performs_%40_WorkPlay.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Conor Oberst]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/conor-oberst/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Conor Mullen Oberst is an American singer-songwriter best known for his work in Bright Eyes. He has also played in several other bands, including Desaparecidos, The Faint, Commander Venus, Park Ave., Conor Oberst and the Mystic Valley Band, Monsters of Folk, and Better Oblivion Community Center. Oberst was named the Best Songwriter of 2008 by Rolling Stone magazine.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6e/Flickr_-_moses_namkung_-_Conor_Oberst_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/conor-oberst/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sinéad O'Connor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sinéad-o'connor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sinéad Marie Bernadette O'Connor is an Irish singer-songwriter who rose to fame in the late 1980s with her debut album The Lion and the Cobra. O'Connor achieved worldwide success in 1990 with a new arrangement of Prince's song 'Nothing Compares 2 U.'</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ad/FIL_2013_-_Sin%C3%A9ad_O%27Connor_08.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sinéad-o'connor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jason Newsted]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-newsted/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jason Curtis Newsted is an American musician who was the bassist of American heavy metal band Metallica from 1986 to 2001. Beginning his career with thrash metal band Flotsam and Jetsam from 1981 to 1986, he successfully auditioned with Metallica to succeed the deceased Cliff Burton. Newsted performed on the albums ...And Justice for All (1988), Metallica (1991), Load (1996), and Reload (1997), the most album appearances among Metallica's bassists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/68/13-06-09_RaR_Newsted_10.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-newsted/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>