<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Acoustic Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Acoustic Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:49:34 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anneke van Giersbergen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anneke-van-giersbergen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Anna Maria van Giersbergen, known artistically as Anneke van Giersbergen, is a Dutch singer, songwriter, guitarist and pianist who became known worldwide as the lead singer and songwriter for the Dutch band The Gathering, between 1994 and 2007. 
She also has a solo career. The project was originally called Agua de Annique, but now goes by her own name.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/30/Gathering_anneke.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anneke-van-giersbergen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shawn Mendes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shawn-mendes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shawn Peter Raul Mendes is a Canadian singer, songwriter and model. He gained a following in 2013, posting song covers on the video-sharing application Vine. The following year, he caught the attention of artist manager Andrew Gertler and Island Records A&R Ziggy Chareton, which led to him signing a deal with the record label. He has since released three studio albums, headlined three world tours, and received several awards.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b4/Shawn_Mendes_at_The_Queen%27s_Birthday_Party_%28cropped_2%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shawn-mendes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joshua Radin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joshua-radin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joshua Radin is an American singer-songwriter. He has recorded seven studio albums, and his songs have been used in a number of films and TV series. His most successful album, Simple Times, was released in 2008.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f1/Joshua_Radin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joshua-radin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Crystal Bowersox]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/crystal-bowersox/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Crystal Lynn Bowersox is an American singer, songwriter and actress who was the runner-up on the ninth season of American Idol. She was the first female finalist in three years.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b3/Crystal_Bowersox.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/crystal-bowersox/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marit Larsen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marit-larsen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Marit Elisabeth Larsen is a Norwegian singer and songwriter. She began playing violin at age of 5 and played it until the age of 8. She gained international fame during her teenage years as a member of the pop duo M2M with childhood friend Marion Raven. She then pursued her own music career, releasing her debut solo album Under the Surface in 2006. Her second album, The Chase, was released in Norway in October 2008. Her third album, titled Spark was released in Norway, Denmark, Sweden and Finland on 18 November 2011, and in Germany, Austria and Switzerland on 16 December 2011. Her fourth studio album When the Morning Comes was released on 20 October 2014. Larsen toured in its support within Norway with her own concerts, played songs from the album in Germany and Switzerland at public festivals and was the opening act at two of Johannes Oerding's concerts in November 2015.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/44/2015_Marit_Larsen_-_by_2eight_-_DSC3575.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marit-larsen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Daniel Lanois]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daniel-lanois/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Daniel Roland Lanois is a Canadian record producer, guitarist, vocalist, and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fe/DanielLanois_7878.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daniel-lanois/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kaki King]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kaki-king/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kaki King is an American guitarist and composer. King is known for her percussive and jazz-tinged melodies, energetic live shows, use of multiple tunings on acoustic and lap steel guitar, and her diverse range in different genres.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9b/WebsterHall2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kaki-king/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jack Savoretti]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-savoretti/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Giovanni 'Jack' Savoretti is an English solo acoustic singer of Italian descent. He has released six studio albums to date: Between the Minds (2007), Harder Than Easy (2009), Before the Storm (2012), Written in Scars (2015), Sleep No More (2016) and Singing to Strangers (2019). His song 'Candlelight' charted in 2019 in the UK charts, peaking at No. 70 on the UK Singles Chart.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8c/Jack_wiki.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-savoretti/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tomáš Klus]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tomáš-klus/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tomáš Klus is a Czech musician and songwriter from the Moravian-Silesian Region of the Czech Republic.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3c/T_Klus_2014.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tomáš-klus/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Mayer]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-mayer/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Clayton Mayer is an American singer-songwriter, guitarist, and record producer. Born in Bridgeport, Connecticut, Mayer attended Berklee College of Music in Boston, but disenrolled and moved to Atlanta in 1997 with Clay Cook. Together, they formed a short-lived two-man band called Lo-Fi Masters. After their split, Mayer continued to play local clubs, refining his skills and gaining a following. After his appearance at the 2001 South by Southwest Festival, he was signed to Aware Records, and then Columbia Records, which released his first EP, Inside Wants Out. His following two full-length albums—Room for Squares (2001) and Heavier Things (2003)—did well commercially, achieving multi-platinum status. In 2003, he won the Grammy Award for Best Male Pop Vocal Performance for the single 'Your Body Is a Wonderland'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/eb/John_Mayer_in_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-mayer/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>