<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Folk Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Folk Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:04:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vasile Șeicaru]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vasile-șeicaru/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vasile Șeicaru is a Romanian folk musician. In the past he has worked with Cenaclul Flacăra.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a2/Vasile_%C8%98eicaru.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vasile-șeicaru/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ed Sheeran]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ed-sheeran/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Edward Christopher Sheeran, is an English singer, songwriter, guitarist, record producer, and actor. In early 2011, Sheeran independently released the extended play, No. 5 Collaborations Project. After signing with Asylum Records, his debut album, +, was released in September 2011. It topped the UK and Australian charts, reached number five in the US, and has since been certified eight-times platinum in the UK. The album contains the single 'The A Team', which earned him the Ivor Novello Award for Best Song Musically and Lyrically. In 2012, Sheeran won the Brit Awards for Best British Male Solo Artist and British Breakthrough Act. 'The A Team' was nominated for Song of the Year at the 2013 Grammy Awards, where he performed the song with Elton John.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/55/Ed_Sheeran_2013.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ed-sheeran/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jake Bugg]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jake-bugg/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jake Bugg is an English musician, singer, and songwriter. His self-titled debut album Jake Bugg, some of which was co-written with songwriter Iain Archer, was released in October 2012 and reached number one on the UK Albums Chart. His second album, Shangri La, was released in November 2013 and his third, largely self-produced album On My One, in June 2016. His fourth album Hearts That Strain, a largely acoustic effort, produced by Dan Auerbach, was released in September 2017.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/37/Jake_Bugg.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jake-bugg/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nelly Furtado]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nelly Kim Furtado is a Canadian singer and songwriter. Furtado first gained fame with her debut album, Whoa, Nelly! (2000), which was a critical and commercial success that spawned two top 10 singles on the Billboard Hot 100, 'I'm Like a Bird' and 'Turn Off the Light'. The first of the two singles won her a Grammy Award for Best Female Pop Vocal Performance. In 2003, she released her second album, Folklore, which was preceded by the lead single, 'Powerless '.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/aa/Nelly_Furtado_at_Radio_Regenbogen_Award_2017_%286%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Emeric Imre]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emeric-imre/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Emeric Imre is a Romanian guitarist, musician, vocalist and composer.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d5/Emeric_Imre_Official.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emeric-imre/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Beatie Wolfe]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/beatie-wolfe/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Beatie Wolfe is an Anglo-American singer-songwriter, described as 'a pioneering songwriter' known for 'seeing music differently' and creating new tangible formats for music, which include the 'World's First 3D Interactive Album App' for her debut album 8ight, a musical jacket for her second album Montagu Square and the world's first live 360 AR stream for her third album Raw Space. These musical innovations have gained Wolfe critical acclaim with Highsnobiety naming Wolfe as one of '10 Ways Music Will Change in 2017' and Wired (magazine) featuring Wolfe as one of 22 changing the world.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b0/Beatie_Wolfe_portrait.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/beatie-wolfe/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Denver]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-denver/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Henry John Deutschendorf Jr., known professionally as John Denver, was an American singer-songwriter, record producer, actor, activist, and humanitarian, whose greatest commercial success was as a solo singer. After traveling and living in numerous locations while growing up in his military family, Denver began his music career with folk music groups during the late 1960s. Starting in the 1970s, he was one of the most popular acoustic artists of the decade and one of its best-selling artists. By 1974, he was one of America's best-selling performers, and AllMusic has described Denver as 'among the most beloved entertainers of his era'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b0/John_Denver_1975.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-denver/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dawn Landes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dawn-landes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dawn Landes is an American singer-songwriter and musician. She is originally from around Louisville, Kentucky but spent many years living and performing in Brooklyn, New York. As a recording artist she has released five full-length albums: dawn's music (2005), Fireproof (2008), Sweetheart Rodeo (2010), Bluebird (2014) and Meet Me At The River (2018) as well as five EPs: Straight Lines (2006), Two Three Four (2006), Mal Habillée (2012), Covers EP (2014) and Desert Songs (2015). In support of her releases, Landes has toured extensively in the US, Europe and around the world, often sharing the stage with artists such as Ray Lamontagne, Feist, Andrew Bird, José González, The Weakerthans, Midlake, Suzanne Vega, and Sufjan Stevens.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/91/Justin_Townes_Earle_%26_Dawn_Landes_-_2010-01-27_Nashville%2C_TN.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dawn-landes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nikolai Noskov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nikolai-noskov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nikolai Ivanovich Noskov is a Russian singer and former vocalist of the hard rock band Gorky Park. Five-time winner of the Golden Gramophone. He was also a member of Москва (Moscow) ensemble in the early 1980s, in band Гран-при in 1988 just before joining Gorky Park, and much later in the 1990s in band Николай (Nikolai). Starting 1998 Noskov had a solo career releasing six solo albums. In 2015 he was jury in second season of reality TV series Glavnaya Stsena</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/32/%D0%9D%D0%B8%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%BB%D0%B0%D0%B9_%D0%9D%D0%BE%D1%81%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%B2_%D0%B2_2009_%284%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nikolai-noskov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marissa Nadler]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marissa-nadler/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Marissa Nadler is an American musician and fine artist based in Boston, Massachusetts. Active since 2000, she is currently signed to Sacred Bones Records and Bella Union, and released her eighth full-length studio album, For My Crimes, in September 2018. As a singer-songwriter, her music defies simple classification. Her work 'is rooted in old-school country and folk but brings in elements of experimental and black metal'. Sometimes the term 'dream folk' has been invoked to describe her work.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/64/Marissa_Nadler_2012.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marissa-nadler/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>