<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Folk Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Folk Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 19:48:27 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vasile Șeicaru]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vasile-șeicaru/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vasile Șeicaru is a Romanian folk musician. In the past he has worked with Cenaclul Flacăra.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a2/Vasile_%C8%98eicaru.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vasile-șeicaru/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ed Sheeran]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ed-sheeran/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Edward Christopher Sheeran, is an English singer, songwriter, guitarist, record producer, and actor. In early 2011, Sheeran independently released the extended play, No. 5 Collaborations Project. After signing with Asylum Records, his debut album, +, was released in September 2011. It topped the UK and Australian charts, reached number five in the US, and has since been certified eight-times platinum in the UK. The album contains the single 'The A Team', which earned him the Ivor Novello Award for Best Song Musically and Lyrically. In 2012, Sheeran won the Brit Awards for Best British Male Solo Artist and British Breakthrough Act. 'The A Team' was nominated for Song of the Year at the 2013 Grammy Awards, where he performed the song with Elton John.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/55/Ed_Sheeran_2013.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ed-sheeran/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jake Bugg]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jake-bugg/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jake Bugg is an English musician, singer, and songwriter. His self-titled debut album Jake Bugg, some of which was co-written with songwriter Iain Archer, was released in October 2012 and reached number one on the UK Albums Chart. His second album, Shangri La, was released in November 2013 and his third, largely self-produced album On My One, in June 2016. His fourth album Hearts That Strain, a largely acoustic effort, produced by Dan Auerbach, was released in September 2017.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/37/Jake_Bugg.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jake-bugg/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nelly Furtado]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nelly Kim Furtado is a Canadian singer and songwriter. Furtado first gained fame with her debut album, Whoa, Nelly! (2000), which was a critical and commercial success that spawned two top 10 singles on the Billboard Hot 100, 'I'm Like a Bird' and 'Turn Off the Light'. The first of the two singles won her a Grammy Award for Best Female Pop Vocal Performance. In 2003, she released her second album, Folklore, which was preceded by the lead single, 'Powerless '.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/aa/Nelly_Furtado_at_Radio_Regenbogen_Award_2017_%286%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pete Seeger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-seeger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Peter Seeger was an American folk singer and social activist. A fixture on nationwide radio in the 1940s, he also had a string of hit records during the early 1950s as a member of the Weavers, most notably their recording of Lead Belly's 'Goodnight, Irene', which topped the charts for 13 weeks in 1950. Members of the Weavers were blacklisted during the McCarthy Era. In the 1960s, Seeger re-emerged on the public scene as a prominent singer of protest music in support of international disarmament, civil rights, counterculture, and environmental causes.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/77/Pete_Seeger_sings_%28cropped%29.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-seeger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[KT Tunstall]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kt-tunstall/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kate Victoria Tunstall, known professionally as KT Tunstall, is a Scottish singer-songwriter and musician. She broke into the public eye with a 2004 live solo performance of her song 'Black Horse and the Cherry Tree' on Later... with Jools Holland.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/79/Kt_tunstall_summer_sundae05.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kt-tunstall/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Werner Lämmerhirt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/werner-lämmerhirt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Werner Lämmerhirt was a German singer-songwriter and guitarist in the contemporary folk music style. He sang and wrote in both German and English, in a recording career that spanned more than three decades.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/11/001_2008_09_20_Konzertfotografie.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/werner-lämmerhirt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Harry Sacksioni]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/harry-sacksioni/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Harry Sacksioni is a composer and guitar virtuoso of Dutch origin. The peak of his fame was during the 1970s to 1990s. Famous works of this period include Meta Sequoia, Vensters and Elixer, along with re-arrangements of existing pieces, such as Anji, Scarborough Fair and I Wish. Sacksioni's work is mainly instrumental, although some tracks during the 1980s provided guitar accompaniments to vocals provided by himself and Raymond van het Groenewoud.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ec/Harry_sacksioni-1515278584.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/harry-sacksioni/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Angel Olsen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/angel-olsen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Angel Olsen is an American singer-songwriter and musician from St. Louis, Missouri who lives in Asheville, North Carolina.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f9/Angel_Olsen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/angel-olsen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Harry Chapin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/harry-chapin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Harry Forster Chapin was an American singer-songwriter, humanitarian, and producer best known for his folk rock and pop rock songs, who achieved worldwide success in the 1970s and became one of the most popular artists and highest paid performers. Chapin is also one of the best charting musical artists in the United States. Chapin, a Grammy Award winning artist and Grammy Hall of Fame inductee, has sold over 16 million records worldwide and has been described as one of the most beloved performers in music history.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/32/Harry_chapin_1978.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/harry-chapin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>