<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Ac Dc</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Ac Dc</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:03:07 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Malcolm Young]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/malcolm-young/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Malcolm Mitchell Young was an Australian musician and songwriter, best known as a co-founder, rhythm guitarist, backing vocalist and songwriter for the hard rock band AC/DC. Except for a brief absence in 1988, he was with the band from its November 1973 beginning until retiring in 2014 due to health reasons. Young and the other members of AC/DC were inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 2003.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7a/Malcolm_Young_en_2010.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/malcolm-young/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Axl Rose]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/axl-rose/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>W. Axl Rose is an American singer, songwriter, record producer and musician. He is the lead vocalist of the hard rock band Guns N' Roses, and has also been the band's sole constant member since its inception in 1985. In addition to Guns N' Roses, he also toured with Australian rock band AC/DC in 2016 during the final two legs of their Rock or Bust World Tour when Brian Johnson took a break due to hearing problems. 
Rose has been named one of the greatest singers of all time by various media outlets, including Rolling Stone and NME.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/47/GNRChorzow090718-76_%2830169034758%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/axl-rose/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Cliff Williams]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/cliff-williams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Clifford Williams is an English musician who has been a member of the Australian hard rock band AC/DC as their bassist and backing vocalist since 1977 except for a brief retirement from 2016 to 2018. He had started his professional music career in 1967 and was previously in the British groups Home and Bandit. His first studio album with AC/DC was Powerage in 1978. The band, including Williams, was inducted into the American Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 2003. Williams' side projects, while a member of AC/DC, include benefit concerts and playing with Emir & Frozen Camels on their album San (2002) and a European tour. In 2016, Williams announced his retirement from the music industry after AC/DC's Rock or Bust World Tour.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d6/CliffWilliams.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/cliff-williams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>