<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Synth Pop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Synth Pop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 19:07:34 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Angelakos]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-angelakos/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael John Angelakos is an American musician of Greek descent, a singer, songwriter and record producer. He is best known as the frontman of the indie electronic band Passion Pit.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Flickr_-_moses_namkung_-_Passion_Pit_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-angelakos/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Peter Hook]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-hook/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Peter Hook is an English singer, songwriter, composer, multi-instrumentalist and record producer. He is best known as the bassist and co-founder of English rock bands Joy Division and New Order. Hook often used the bass as a lead instrument, playing melodies on the high strings with a signature heavy chorus effect. In New Order, he would do this, leaving the actual basslines to keyboards or sequencers. This has often been cited as a defining characteristic of the New Order sound.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1f/Peter_Hook_Nocturnal_Culture_Night_13_2018_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-hook/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Trent Reznor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Trent Reznor is an American singer, songwriter, musician, record producer, and film score composer. He is the founder, lead vocalist, and principal songwriter of the industrial rock band Nine Inch Nails, which he founded in 1988 and of which he was the sole official member until adding long-time collaborator Atticus Ross as a permanent member in 2016. His first release under the Nine Inch Nails name, the 1989 album Pretty Hate Machine, was a commercial and critical success. He has since released nine Nine Inch Nails studio albums. He left Interscope Records in 2007 and was an independent recording artist until signing with Columbia Records in 2012.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d5/Trent_Reznor-FEB2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Magne Furuholmen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/magne-furuholmen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Magne Furuholmen is a Norwegian musician and visual artist. He was named Knights First Class of the Order of St. Olav by King Harald for his services to Norwegian music and his international success. Furuholmen, better known to music fans by his stage name Mags, is the keyboardist of the synthpop/rock band A-ha, and co-wrote hits such as 'Take On Me', 'Stay on These Roads', 'Manhattan Skyline', 'Cry Wolf', 'Forever Not Yours', 'Analogue ', 'Minor Earth Major Sky', 'Touchy!', 'You Are the One', 'Move To Memphis' and 'Foot of the Mountain'. The band A-ha has sold more than 50 million albums worldwide.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/80/Magne_Furuholmen_Kongsberg_Jazzfestival_2018_%28221600%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/magne-furuholmen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ellie Goulding]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ellie-goulding/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Elena Jane Goulding is an English singer and songwriter. Her career began when she met record producers Starsmith and Frankmusik, and she was later spotted by Jamie Lillywhite, who later became her manager and A&R. After signing to Polydor Records in July 2009, Goulding released her debut extended play, An Introduction to Ellie Goulding later that year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/71/Ellie_Goulding_-_Global_Citizen_Festival_Hamburg_09.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ellie-goulding/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lights]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lights/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lights Poxleitner-Bokan, known mononymously as Lights, is a Canadian musician, singer, songwriter, author, and illustrator. She is known for her gold-certified albums The Listening and Siberia as well as singles 'Drive My Soul', 'February Air', 'Ice', 'Second Go', 'Toes', and 'Up We Go'. She released her fourth studio album, Skin & Earth, in 2017 accompanied by a graphic novel of the same name.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/LIGHTS_IMG_6799_%2815999651243%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lights/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dmitry Koldun]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dmitry-koldun/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dmitry Aleksandrovich Koldun is a pop singer from Minsk, Belarus.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/24/Dima_Koldun_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dmitry-koldun/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pete Shelley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-shelley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Pete Shelley was an English singer, songwriter and guitarist. He formed early punk band Buzzcocks with Howard Devoto in 1976, and became the lead singer and guitarist in 1977 when Devoto left. The group released their biggest hit 'Ever Fallen in Love ' in 1978. It broke up in 1981 and reformed at the end of the decade. Shelley also had a solo career; his song 'Homosapien' charted in the US in 1981.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/05/Pete-shelley.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-shelley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul Waaktaar-Savoy]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-waaktaar-savoy/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul Waaktaar-Savoy is a Norwegian musician and songwriter. He was named Knights First Class of the Order of St. Olav by King Harald for his services to Norwegian music and his international success. Pål Savoy is best known for his work as the main songwriter and guitarist in the Norwegian pop band A-ha. He has written or co-written most of the band's biggest hits, including 'The Sun Always Shines on T.V.', 'Hunting High and Low', 'Take on Me', the James Bond theme 'The Living Daylights' and the ballad 'Summer Moved On'. In addition, Waaktaar-Savoy is also a painter. The band A-ha has sold more than 50 million albums worldwide.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/36/Paul_Waaktaar-Savoy_Kongsberg_Jazzfestival_2018_%28220430%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-waaktaar-savoy/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Trace Cyrus]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trace-cyrus/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Trace Dempsey Cyrus is an American musician. The son of country singer Billy Ray Cyrus and brother of recording artists Miley Cyrus and Noah Cyrus, he was the backing vocalist and guitarist of the band Metro Station, with time out between 2010 and 2014. In 2010, he began providing vocals and guitar in the pop rock band Ashland HIGH. He also owns the clothing company From Backseats to Bedrooms.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/16/Trace_Cyrus_Metro_Station_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trace-cyrus/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>