<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Night Ranger</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Night Ranger</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:37:01 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brad Gillis]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brad-gillis/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bradley Frank 'Brad' Gillis is a guitarist most famous for playing with the band Night Ranger. He was in the band Rubicon during the 1970s before Night Ranger. Since forming in 1979, Gillis and drummer Kelly Keagy are the only members to have appeared in every incarnation of the band and all studio releases. However, since Keagy missed several shows for the first time in 2017, Gillis is the only Night Ranger member to have appeared at every live performance in the band's history. He has also played for Ozzy Osbourne and Fiona, and has released solo albums. Gillis’s musical side projects include placing over 300 songs for ESPN’s Sports Center, The X Games, Fox Sports, Tiger Woods Sony PlayStation Games, EA Sports, The Fuse Channel and many others. He has appeared in over a dozen music videos, with TV performances on American Bandstand, Solid Gold, Rock & Roll Tonight and thousands of live concerts. He also participated in the one-time collaboration, Hear 'n Aid, for the promotional single, 'Stars,' which helped raise $1 million for famine relief in Africa. He was one of several lead guitarists to contribute guitar solos for the cause, including Vivian Campbell, Buck Dharma, and Neal Schon. His first solo album Gilrock Ranch produced a top twenty single, “Honest to God,” which was co-written and sung by Gregg Allman.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/35/Brad_Gillis_from_Night_Ranger.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brad-gillis/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>