<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Piano</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Piano</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:04:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Grand]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-grand/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steve Grand is an American singer, songwriter and model from Lemont, Illinois, a Chicago suburb. He became an overnight internet celebrity and the music video of his first hit 'All-American Boy' went viral on YouTube in less than a week in July 2013. This attention landed Grand on Good Morning America, CNN and other national media. In addition to being a musician, Grand has become an active figure in the LGBT equality movement. He released his debut album titled All American Boy financed by a successful Kickstarter public funding campaign. The follow-up album Not the End of Me was released in 2018.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/36/Steve_Grand_-_1032013.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-grand/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andrea Bocelli]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrea-bocelli/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Andrea Bocelli is an Italian opera singer, songwriter, and record producer. Celine Dion has said that 'if God would have a singing voice, he must sound a lot like Andrea Bocelli,' and David Foster, a record producer, often describes Bocelli's voice as the most beautiful in the world.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/15/AndreaBocelliMar10.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrea-bocelli/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alanis Morissette]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alanis Nadine Morissette is a Canadian-American singer, songwriter, record producer, and actress. Known for her emotive mezzo-soprano voice, Morissette began her career in Canada in the early 1990s with two mildly successful dance-pop albums. Afterwards, as part of a recording deal, she moved to Holmby Hills, Los Angeles and in 1995 released Jagged Little Pill, a more rock-oriented album which sold more than 33 million copies globally and is her most critically acclaimed work. Her follow-up album, Supposed Former Infatuation Junkie, was released in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Alanis_Morissette_5-19-2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ryan Star]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ryan-star/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ryan Stahr Kulchinsky is an American rock singer-songwriter from Long Island, New York, currently signed on Island Records. His first major label record 11:59, released via Atlantic in 2010, reached No. 31 on Billboard 200 and No. 10 on Billboard Rock albums chart. Star became known to a wider audience as contestant on the CBS reality TV show Rock Star: Supernova in 2006. His songs have featured on several TV shows and promotion. His song Brand New Day, featured as the main theme to Fox TV series Lie to Me, earned him a BMI TV Music Award in May 2009.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b7/Rstar.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ryan-star/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sheryl Crow]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sheryl-crow/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sheryl Suzanne Crow is an American musician, singer, songwriter, and actress. Her music incorporates elements of pop, rock, country, jazz, and blues. She has released ten studio albums, four compilations, two live albums, and has contributed to a number of film soundtracks. Her songs include 'All I Wanna Do', 'If It Makes You Happy', 'My Favorite Mistake' and the theme song for the 1997 James Bond film Tomorrow Never Dies. She has sold more than 50 million albums worldwide. Crow has garnered nine Grammy Awards from the National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/dc/Sheryl_Crow.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sheryl-crow/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jake Bugg]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jake-bugg/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jake Bugg is an English musician, singer, and songwriter. His self-titled debut album Jake Bugg, some of which was co-written with songwriter Iain Archer, was released in October 2012 and reached number one on the UK Albums Chart. His second album, Shangri La, was released in November 2013 and his third, largely self-produced album On My One, in June 2016. His fourth album Hearts That Strain, a largely acoustic effort, produced by Dan Auerbach, was released in September 2017.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/37/Jake_Bugg.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jake-bugg/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andrey Makarevich]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrey-makarevich/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Andrey Vadimovich Makarevich PAR is a Soviet and Russian rock musician and the founder of Russia's oldest still active rock band Mashina Vremeni.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/55/Andrey_Makarevich_2019_%282%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrey-makarevich/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Daniel Balavoine]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daniel-balavoine/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Daniel Balavoine was a French singer and songwriter. He was hugely popular in the French-speaking world, and inspired many singers in the 1980s, such as Jean-Jacques Goldman, Michel Berger, his closest friend, or the Japanese pop-rock group Crystal King; he was also a part of the original cast of the rock opera Starmania in 1978, which was written by Berger. He took part in French political life and is known for a 1980 televised verbal confrontation with then presidential candidate François Mitterrand.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/59/Daniel_Balavoine.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daniel-balavoine/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[George Winston]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-winston/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>George Winston is an American pianist who was born in Michigan and grew up mainly in Montana, as well as Mississippi and Florida. He is best known for his solo piano recordings; several of his albums from the early 1980s have sold millions of copies each. He plays in three styles: the melodic approach he developed that he calls 'rural folk piano'; stride piano, primarily inspired by Thomas 'Fats' Waller and Teddy Wilson; and his primary interest, New Orleans R&B piano, influenced by James Booker, Professor Longhair, and Henry Butler.</p>]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-winston/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>