<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Piano</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Piano</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:01:35 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[T-Bone Walker]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/t-bone-walker/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Aaron Thibeaux 'T-Bone' Walker was an American blues guitarist, singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist, who was a pioneer and innovator of the jump blues and electric blues sound. In 2018 Rolling Stone magazine ranked him number 37 on its list of 'The 100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ee/T-Bone_Walker_1972.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/t-bone-walker/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ben Moody]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ben-moody/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Benjamin Robert 'Ben' Moody is an American musician, singer, songwriter, record producer, and actor. He is best known as co-founder, lead guitarist, and co-songwriter of rock band Evanescence from its inception in 1995 to his departure in October 2003. Since leaving Evanescence, Moody has collaborated with an array of performers vocally, instrumentally, and as a writer. He is currently a member of The Halo Method and We Are the Fallen.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Evanescence_2003_barcelona_ben_moody.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ben-moody/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Herman Brood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/herman-brood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hermanus 'Herman' Brood  was a Dutch musician, painter, actor and poet. As a musician he achieved artistic and commercial success in the 1970s and 1980s, and was called 'the greatest and only Dutch rock 'n' roll star'. Later in life he started a successful career as a painter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b7/Herman_Brood_1979.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/herman-brood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Grand]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-grand/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steve Grand is an American singer, songwriter and model from Lemont, Illinois, a Chicago suburb. He became an overnight internet celebrity and the music video of his first hit 'All-American Boy' went viral on YouTube in less than a week in July 2013. This attention landed Grand on Good Morning America, CNN and other national media. In addition to being a musician, Grand has become an active figure in the LGBT equality movement. He released his debut album titled All American Boy financed by a successful Kickstarter public funding campaign. The follow-up album Not the End of Me was released in 2018.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/36/Steve_Grand_-_1032013.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-grand/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andrea Bocelli]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrea-bocelli/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Andrea Bocelli is an Italian opera singer, songwriter, and record producer. Celine Dion has said that 'if God would have a singing voice, he must sound a lot like Andrea Bocelli,' and David Foster, a record producer, often describes Bocelli's voice as the most beautiful in the world.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/15/AndreaBocelliMar10.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrea-bocelli/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alanis Morissette]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alanis Nadine Morissette is a Canadian-American singer, songwriter, record producer, and actress. Known for her emotive mezzo-soprano voice, Morissette began her career in Canada in the early 1990s with two mildly successful dance-pop albums. Afterwards, as part of a recording deal, she moved to Holmby Hills, Los Angeles and in 1995 released Jagged Little Pill, a more rock-oriented album which sold more than 33 million copies globally and is her most critically acclaimed work. Her follow-up album, Supposed Former Infatuation Junkie, was released in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Alanis_Morissette_5-19-2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Angelakos]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-angelakos/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael John Angelakos is an American musician of Greek descent, a singer, songwriter and record producer. He is best known as the frontman of the indie electronic band Passion Pit.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Flickr_-_moses_namkung_-_Passion_Pit_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-angelakos/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Phil Spector]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/phil-spector/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Phillip Harvey Spector is an American record producer, musician, and songwriter. He developed the Wall of Sound, a music production formula he described as a Wagnerian approach to rock and roll. Spector was dubbed the 'First Tycoon of Teen' by writer Tom Wolfe and is acknowledged as one of the most influential figures in pop music history. After the 1970s, Spector mostly retired from public life. In 2009, he was convicted of second-degree murder and has remained incarcerated since.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/24/Phil_Spector_2000.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/phil-spector/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Serj Tankian]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Serj Tankian is an Armenian-American musician, singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, poet and political activist. He is best known as the lead vocalist, songwriter, keyboardist, and occasional live rhythm guitarist of the band System of a Down, formed in 1994.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/69/Serj_Tankian_Spirit_of_Burgas_Bulgaria_2010_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Elvis Presley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elvis-presley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Elvis Aaron Presley, also known mononymously as Elvis, was an American singer and actor. Regarded as one of the most significant cultural icons of the 20th century, he is often referred to as the 'King of Rock and Roll' or simply 'the King'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2d/PresleyPromo1954PhotoOnly.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elvis-presley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>