<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Power Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Power Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:38:12 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Henjo Richter]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/henjo-richter/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Henjo Oliver Richter, is a guitarist and keyboardist in Gamma Ray, the German power metal band formed by Kai Hansen.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bf/Henjo_Richter_2008.01.08.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/henjo-richter/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Timo Tolkki]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/timo-tolkki/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Timo Tapio Tolkki is a Finnish musician best known as the former guitarist, songwriter and producer of the power metal band Stratovarius. With his tenure lasting for more than twenty years, he was the longest standing member of the band before his departure in 2008. After leaving Stratovarius he formed two supergroups named Revolution Renaissance and Symfonia, both of which have since disbanded. In a 2011 article by Guitar World magazine, Tolkki was included in the all-time top 50 list of the world's fastest guitarists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/30/Timo_Tolkki_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/timo-tolkki/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Oscar Dronjak]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/oscar-dronjak/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Oscar Fredrick Dronjak is a Swedish guitarist and founder of the heavy metal band HammerFall. Prior to the success of HammerFall, he also played and released albums with the death metal acts Ceremonial Oath and Crystal Age.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/84/Masters_of_Rock_2007_-_Hammerfall_-_Oscar_Dronjak_-_03.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/oscar-dronjak/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Thomas Youngblood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/thomas-youngblood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Youngblood is an American metal guitarist, songwriter, and founding member of the symphonic metal band Kamelot, currently living in Tampa, Florida, USA.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cb/Thomas_Youngblood.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/thomas-youngblood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kiko Loureiro]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kiko-loureiro/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Pedro Henrique 'Kiko' Loureiro is a Brazilian heavy metal guitarist, best known as a member of the bands Angra and Megadeth.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a1/Kiko_Loureiro%2C_em_Fort_Rock%2C_DystopiaTour_2016.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kiko-loureiro/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roland Grapow]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roland-grapow/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roland Grapow is a professional guitarist and music producer. Grapow is best known for his time in the leading power metal band Helloween, who he played with for 12 years after replacing founding member Kai Hansen. He subsequently created the power metal band Masterplan in 2001, which is still active today.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/80/Masterplan_%E2%80%93_Headbangers_Open_Air_2015_09.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roland-grapow/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Luca Turilli]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/luca-turilli/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Luca Turilli is an Italian musician and songwriter. He is one of the founders of the symphonic power metal band Rhapsody of Fire. He also worked on a trilogy of solo albums as Luca Turilli, and released one album under the name of Luca Turilli's Dreamquest, a project he worked on alongside Dominique Leurquin. In 2008, Luca began an online guitar course titled Luca Turilli's Neoclassical Revelation. The course takes its name from his neoclassical playing style.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f5/Luca_Turilli_Live.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/luca-turilli/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lauri Porra]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lauri-porra/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lauri Porra is a Finnish bassist and composer, also known for his work in Stratovarius. Lauri Porra is a fourth generation musician, and the great-grandson of famous Finnish composer Jean Sibelius. He started to study music at age 6 when he started to play cello in a local music school. In 1993 he switched to bass guitar and continued his studies in the Helsinki Pop Jazz Conservatory (1994–2004). Additionally he has taken lessons on piano, double bass, trumpet and male vocals. During 1997-1999 he sang with the renowned YL male choir performing for instance with the London Symphony Orchestra. He has released four instrumental solo albums with the latest, ‘Entropia’, released in January 2018 on BIS-records. He has also composed music to movies, tv and media. In 2016 Lauri received Nordisk Popularauktors NPU-award and was nominated for HARPA Nordic film composer music award. Lauri´s own band Lauri Porra Flyover Ensemble has performed Lauri´s music on tours and various festivals. Lauri´s orchestral music has been performed by Finnish Radio Orchestra, Trondheim Symphony Orchestra, Lahti Symphony Orchestra and many others. Lauri is artistic partner of Vantaa Pops orchestra and artistic advisor of the Helsinki Festival.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/44/Lauri_Porra.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lauri-porra/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:11 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Frédéric Leclercq]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/frédéric-leclercq/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Frédéric Alexandre 'Fred' Leclercq is a French musician and producer. He is the guitarist and main songwriter in the death metal supergroup Sinsaenum, the guitarist and vocalist in Maladaptive, and has recently joined the German thrash metal group, Kreator, as their new bassist.. He is a session musician for various other bands, including George Lynch's Souls of We. He is also a former member of power metal bands DragonForce and Heavenly and played several shows with Carnival in Coal and Sabaton.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f2/Fr%C3%A9d%C3%A9ric_Leclercq.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/frédéric-leclercq/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:11 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Yngwie Malmsteen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yngwie-malmsteen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Yngwie Johan Malmsteen is a Swedish guitarist, songwriter and bandleader. Malmsteen first became known in the 1980s for his neoclassical metal playing style in heavy metal, and has released 20 studio albums in a career spanning almost 40 years. In 2009, Time magazine rated Malmsteen as number 7 among the 10 greatest electric guitar players of all time.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/67/Yngwie_Malmsteen_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yngwie-malmsteen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:11 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>