<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Wings</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Wings</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:08:38 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Laurence Juber]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/laurence-juber/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Laurence Juber, is an English musician who played guitar in the rock band Paul McCartney and Wings from 1978 to 1981. He has also worked as a fingerstyle guitarist and studio musician.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/ce/Laurence_Juber_2019_by_Glenn_Francis.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/laurence-juber/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul McCartney]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir James Paul McCartney is an English singer, songwriter, musician, composer, and record and film producer who gained worldwide fame as co-lead vocalist and bassist for the Beatles. His songwriting partnership with John Lennon remains the most successful in history. After the group disbanded in 1970, he pursued a successful solo career and formed the band Wings with his first wife, Linda, and Denny Laine.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d6/Paul_McCartney_in_October_2018.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Denny Laine]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/denny-laine/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Denny Laine is an English musician, singer, and songwriter known as a founder of two major British rock bands: The Moody Blues, with whom he played from 1964 to 1966, and Paul McCartney and Wings, with whom he played from 1971 to 1981. Laine has worked with a variety of artists and groups over a six decade career, and continues to record and perform as a solo artist. In 2018, Laine was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Moody Blues.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c4/Denny_Laine_-_Wings_-_1976.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/denny-laine/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>