<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Contemporary Folk Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Contemporary Folk Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 19:48:27 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shakira]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shakira Isabel Mebarak Ripoll is a Colombian singer, songwriter, dancer, businesswoman, and philanthropist. Born and raised in Barranquilla, she made her recording debut under Sony Music Colombia at the age of 13. Following the commercial failure of her first two Colombian albums, Magia (1991) and Peligro (1993), she rose to prominence in Spanish-speaking countries with her next albums, Pies Descalzos (1995) and Dónde Están los Ladrones? (1998). Shakira entered the English-language market with her fifth album, Laundry Service (2001). It sold over 13 million copies and spawned the international number-one singles 'Whenever, Wherever' and 'Underneath Your Clothes'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/Shakira_in_Toronto_2018.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Will Oldham]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bonnie-"prince"-billy/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William 'Will' Oldham, better known by the stage name Bonnie 'Prince' Billy, is an American singer-songwriter and actor. From 1993 to 1997, he performed and recorded under variations of the Palace name, including Palace Brothers, Palace Songs, and Palace Music. After releasing material under his own name, he adopted the Bonnie 'Prince' Billy name for the majority of his output since 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/67/BonniePrinceBilly3_gobeirne.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bonnie-"prince"-billy/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Alvin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Albert Alvin is an American singer-songwriter, guitarist, music producer and poet. He is a former and founding member of the roots rock band the Blasters. Alvin has recorded and performed as a solo artist since the late 1980s and has been involved in various side projects and collaborations. He has had brief stints as a member of the bands X and the Knitters.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Dave_Alvin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lynn Miles]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lynn-miles/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lynn Miles is a Canadian singer-songwriter. She has won the Juno Award and three Canadian Folk Music Awards.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a7/Lynn_Miles_-_Lottes_Musiknacht_Industriemuseum_Elmshorn_2018_04.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lynn-miles/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Arjen Anthony Lucassen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/arjen-anthony-lucassen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Arjen Anthony Lucassen is a Dutch singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist musician and record producer best known for his long-running progressive metal/rock opera project Ayreon.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4b/Arjen_Anthony_Lucassen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/arjen-anthony-lucassen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[k.d. lang]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/k.d.-lang/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kathryn Dawn Lang, known by her stylized stage name k.d. lang, is a Canadian pop and country singer-songwriter and occasional actress.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/76/Kd_lang_-_AIS_Arena%2C_Canberra_-_7_Nov_11%283%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/k.d.-lang/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lisa Hannigan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lisa-hannigan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lisa Margaret Hannigan is an Irish singer, songwriter, musician, and voice actress. She began her musical career as a member of Damien Rice's band. Since beginning her solo career in 2007 she has released three albums: Sea Sew (2008), Passenger (2011), and At Swim (2016). Hannigan's music has received award nominations both in Ireland and the USA. Hannigan is also the voice actress for the character Blue Diamond in Steven Universe, an American animated television series created by Rebecca Sugar.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/13/Lisa_Hannigan_deco16-10.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lisa-hannigan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ed Sheeran]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ed-sheeran/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Edward Christopher Sheeran, is an English singer, songwriter, guitarist, record producer, and actor. In early 2011, Sheeran independently released the extended play, No. 5 Collaborations Project. After signing with Asylum Records, his debut album, +, was released in September 2011. It topped the UK and Australian charts, reached number five in the US, and has since been certified eight-times platinum in the UK. The album contains the single 'The A Team', which earned him the Ivor Novello Award for Best Song Musically and Lyrically. In 2012, Sheeran won the Brit Awards for Best British Male Solo Artist and British Breakthrough Act. 'The A Team' was nominated for Song of the Year at the 2013 Grammy Awards, where he performed the song with Elton John.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/55/Ed_Sheeran_2013.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ed-sheeran/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Iron & Wine]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/iron-&-wine/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Samuel 'Sam' Ervin Beam, better known by his stage and recording name Iron & Wine, is an American singer-songwriter. He has released six studio albums, several EPs and singles, as well as a few download-only releases, which include a live album. He occasionally tours with a full band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/84/Sambeam-brooklyn-2006.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/iron-&-wine/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nelly Furtado]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nelly Kim Furtado is a Canadian singer and songwriter. Furtado first gained fame with her debut album, Whoa, Nelly! (2000), which was a critical and commercial success that spawned two top 10 singles on the Billboard Hot 100, 'I'm Like a Bird' and 'Turn Off the Light'. The first of the two singles won her a Grammy Award for Best Female Pop Vocal Performance. In 2003, she released her second album, Folklore, which was preceded by the lead single, 'Powerless '.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/aa/Nelly_Furtado_at_Radio_Regenbogen_Award_2017_%286%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>