<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » The B 52'S</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » The B 52'S</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 21:22:37 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Keith Strickland]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/keith-strickland/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fa/Keith_Strickland_Lovebox.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/keith-strickland/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Cindy Wilson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/cindy-wilson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Cynthia Leigh Wilson is an American singer, and is one of the vocalists, songwriters and founding members of new wave rock band the B-52s. She is noted for her distinctive contralto voice and also plays percussion during live shows. She is the younger sister of the late guitarist Ricky Wilson (1953–1985), who was also a founding member of the band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/61/Cindy_Wilson_Lovebox.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/cindy-wilson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kate Pierson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kate-pierson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Catherine Elizabeth Pierson is an American singer, lyricist, and one of the singers and founding members of the B-52's. A multi-instrumentalist, she plays guitar, bass and various keyboard instruments. In the B-52s, she has performed alongside Cindy Wilson, Fred Schneider, Ricky Wilson, and Keith Strickland. In the early years, as well as being a vocalist, Pierson was the main keyboard player and was notable for performing on a keyboard bass during many live shows and on many of the band's recordings, taking on a role usually filled by a bass guitar player, which differentiated the band from their contemporaries. This, along with Pierson's distinctive wide-ranging singing voice, remains a trademark of the B-52s’ unique sound. Pierson has also collaborated with many other artists including The Ramones, Iggy Pop and R.E.M.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/81/Kate_Pierson_NYC.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kate-pierson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>