<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Yes</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Yes</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 19:54:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Trevor Rabin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trevor-rabin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Trevor Charles Rabin is a South African musician, singer-songwriter, producer, and film composer. Born into a musical family and raised in Johannesburg, Rabin took up the piano and guitar at an early age and became a session musician, playing and producing with a variety of artists. In 1972, he joined the rock band Rabbitt who enjoyed considerable success in South Africa, and released his first solo album, Beginnings. In 1978, Rabin moved to London to further his career, working as a solo artist and a producer for various artists including Manfred Mann's Earth Band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1e/Trevor_Rabin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trevor-rabin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jon Davison]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jon-davison/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jon Davison is an American singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist musician, who has been the lead vocalist of progressive rock band Yes since 2012. He is also known as the former lead singer of progressive rock band Glass Hammer from 2009 to 2014, and the former bass guitarist of Sky Cries Mary from 1993 to 2016, in which he was credited under his nickname of 'Juano' Davison.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/37/Jon_Davison_performing_at_the_Art_Park_in_Lowiston%2C_New_York_on_July_17%2C_2012.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jon-davison/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Squire]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-squire/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher Russell Edward Squire was an English musician, singer and songwriter best known as the bassist and a founding member of the progressive rock band Yes. He was the longest-serving original member, having remained in the band until his death and appearing on every studio album released from 1969 to 2014.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3d/Chris_squire_1978.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-squire/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>