<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Avant Garde Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Avant Garde Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 23:54:38 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Maureen Tucker]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/moe-tucker/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Maureen Ann 'Moe' Tucker is an American musician and singer best known for having been the drummer for the New York City-based rock band the Velvet Underground.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fa/The_Moe_Tucker_Band_%282%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/moe-tucker/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Glenn Branca]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glenn-branca/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Glenn Branca was an American avant-garde composer and guitarist known for his use of volume, alternative guitar tunings, repetition, droning, and the harmonic series. Branca received a 2009 Foundation for Contemporary Arts Grants to Artists Award.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8c/Glenn_Branca.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glenn-branca/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Buckethead]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Patrick Carroll, known professionally as Buckethead, is an American multi-instrumental musician who has received critical acclaim for his innovative electric guitar playing. His music spans many genres, including progressive metal, funk, blues, bluegrass, ambient, and avant-garde music. He performs primarily as a solo artist, though he has collaborated extensively with a wide variety of high-profile artists such as Bill Laswell, Bootsy Collins, Bernie Worrell, Iggy Pop, Les Claypool, Serj Tankian, Bill Moseley, Mike Patton, Viggo Mortensen, That 1 Guy, Bassnectar, and was a member of Guns N' Roses from 2000 to 2004. He has released 306 studio albums, four special releases, and one EP. He has also performed on more than 50 other albums by other artists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Neumos_seattle_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Frank Zappa]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/frank-zappa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Frank Vincent Zappa was an American multi-instrumentalist musician, composer, and bandleader. His work is characterized by nonconformity, free-form improvisation, sound experiments, musical virtuosity, and satire of American culture. In a career spanning more than 30 years, Zappa composed rock, pop, jazz, jazz fusion, orchestral and musique concrète works, and produced almost all of the 60-plus albums that he released with his band the Mothers of Invention and as a solo artist. Zappa also directed feature-length films and music videos, and designed album covers. He is considered one of the most innovative and stylistically diverse rock musicians of his era.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c4/Zappa_16011977_01_300.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/frank-zappa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Thurston Moore]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/thurston-moore/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thurston Joseph Moore is an American musician best known as a member of Sonic Youth. He has also participated in many solo and group collaborations outside Sonic Youth, as well as running the Ecstatic Peace! record label. Moore was ranked 34th in Rolling Stone's 2004 edition of the '100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time.' In May 2012, Spin published a staff-selected list of the top 100 rock guitarists, and ranked Moore and his Sonic Youth bandmate Lee Ranaldo together at number 1.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f9/Thurston_Moore_at_the_Brooklyn_Book_Festival.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/thurston-moore/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>