<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Rock And Roll</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Rock And Roll</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 23:53:43 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Brown]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-brown-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Roger 'Joe' Brown, MBE is an English entertainer. He has worked as a rock and roll singer and guitarist for more than six decades. He was a stage and television performer in the late 1950s and has been a UK recording star since the early 1960s. He has made six films, presented specialist radio series for BBC Radio 2, appeared on the West End stage alongside Dame Anna Neagle and has written an autobiography. In recent years he has again concentrated on recording and performing music, playing two tours of around 100 shows every year and releasing an album almost every year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2d/Joe_Brown_On_Stage.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-brown-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Herman Brood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/herman-brood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hermanus 'Herman' Brood  was a Dutch musician, painter, actor and poet. As a musician he achieved artistic and commercial success in the 1970s and 1980s, and was called 'the greatest and only Dutch rock 'n' roll star'. Later in life he started a successful career as a painter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b7/Herman_Brood_1979.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/herman-brood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hank Marvin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hank-marvin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hank Brian Marvin is an English multi-instrumentalist, vocalist and songwriter. He is best known as the lead guitarist for the Shadows, a group which primarily performed instrumentals and was the backing band for Cliff Richard, and subsequently for Marvin, Welch & Farrar.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/83/Hank_Marvin_%286289841143%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hank-marvin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Maureen Tucker]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/moe-tucker/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Maureen Ann 'Moe' Tucker is an American musician and singer best known for having been the drummer for the New York City-based rock band the Velvet Underground.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fa/The_Moe_Tucker_Band_%282%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/moe-tucker/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nic Cester]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nic-cester/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nicholas John 'Nic' Cester is an Australian musician, singer, songwriter and guitarist, known for being the frontman in rock band Jet alongside his younger brother Chris. Cester is also a founder of the Australian supergroup The Wrights. Jet's track 'Are You Gonna Be My Girl', has won APRA Awards for 'Most Performed Australian Work Overseas' in 2006 and 2007.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/31/NicCester_Chicago04.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nic-cester/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tony Sheridan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tony-sheridan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tony Sheridan was an English rock and roll singer-songwriter and guitarist who spent much of his adult life in Germany. He was best known as an early collaborator of the Beatles, one of two non-Beatles to receive label performance credit on a record with the group, and the only non-Beatle to appear as lead singer on a Beatles recording which charted as a single.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/08/TonySheridan.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tony-sheridan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Link Wray]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/link-wray/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Fred Lincoln 'Link' Wray, Jr. was a Shawnee rock and roll guitarist, songwriter, and vocalist who became popular in the late 1950s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5d/Link_Wray_-_3-8-03_Photo_by_Anthony_Pepitone.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/link-wray/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Todd Rundgren]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Todd Harry Rundgren is an American multi-instrumentalist, singer, songwriter, and record producer who has performed a diverse range of styles as a solo artist, and as a member of the band Utopia. He is known for his sophisticated and often-unorthodox music, flamboyant stage outfits, and his later experiments with interactive entertainment. He also produced music videos, pioneered forms of multimedia, and was an early adopter and promoter of various computer technologies, such as using the Internet as a means of music distribution in the late 1990s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4b/Todd_Rundgren_performs_%40_WorkPlay.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Johnny Cash]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/johnny-cash/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John R. 'Johnny' Cash was an American singer-songwriter, guitarist, actor, and author. He is one of the best-selling music artists of all time, having sold more than 90 million records worldwide. His genre-spanning songs and sound embraced country music, rock and roll, rockabilly, blues, folk, and gospel. This crossover appeal won Cash the rare honor of being inducted into the Country Music, Rock and Roll, and Gospel Music Halls of Fame.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/be/Johnny_Cash_%281964%29.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/johnny-cash/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bill Wyman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-wyman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bill Wyman is an English musician, record producer, songwriter and singer. He was the bass guitarist for the English rock and roll band the Rolling Stones from 1962 until 1993. Since 1997 he has recorded and toured with his own band, Bill Wyman's Rhythm Kings. He has worked producing records and films, and has scored music for film in films and television.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a3/Bill_Wyman_2009.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-wyman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>