<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Siouxsie And The Banshees</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Siouxsie And The Banshees</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 01:11:11 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robert Smith]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robert-smith-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert James Smith is an English singer, songwriter, musician, and record producer. He is the lead singer, guitarist, multi-instrumentalist, primary songwriter, and only continuous member of the rock band the Cure, which he co-founded in 1976. He was also the lead guitarist for the band Siouxsie and the Banshees from 1982 to 1984, and was part of the short-lived group the Glove in 1983. He is known for his distinctive voice, guitar-playing style and stage look, the latter two of which were influential on the goth subculture that rose to prominence in the 1980s. Smith was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Cure in 2019.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7a/Robert_Smith_-_The_Cure_-_Roskilde_Festival_2012_-_Orange_Stage_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robert-smith-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steven Severin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steven-severin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steven Severin, is an English musician, composer, bassist, producer and co-founding member of Siouxsie and the Banshees. He took the name 'Severin' from the Leopold von Sacher-Masoch character who is mentioned in the Velvet Underground song 'Venus in Furs'. Severin had earlier considered 'Steve Spunker' for his stage name. After the split of Siouxsie and the Banshees in 1996, Severin created his own label RE, and released several instrumental albums via his official website. In the late 2000s and the early 2010s, he regularly performed live in solo, playing music over footage of silent films.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/Siouxsie-steve-severin-oakland.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steven-severin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John McGeoch]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-mcgeoch/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Alexander McGeoch was a Scottish pop music guitarist who played with several bands of the post-punk era, including Magazine, Siouxsie and the Banshees, Visage, and Public Image Ltd.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d6/Jhon_Mcgeoch.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-mcgeoch/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>