<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Alice In Chains</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Alice In Chains</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 23:54:38 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[William DuVall]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/william-duvall/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Bradley DuVall is an American musician, best known as the current co-lead vocalist and rhythm guitarist for the rock band Alice in Chains. DuVall joined Alice in Chains in 2006, replacing the band's original lead singer Layne Staley, who died in 2002, and sharing vocal duties with guitarist/vocalist Jerry Cantrell. To date, DuVall has recorded three albums with the band, 2009's Black Gives Way to Blue, 2013's The Devil Put Dinosaurs Here, and 2018's Rainier Fog. DuVall won an ASCAP Pop Music Award for co-writing the song 'I Know' for Dionne Farris in 1996.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c5/William_Duvall.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/william-duvall/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jerry Cantrell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jerry-cantrell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jerry Fulton Cantrell Jr. is an American musician, singer-songwriter and guitarist best known as the founder, lead guitarist, co-lead vocalist and main songwriter of the rock band Alice in Chains. The band rose to international fame in the early 1990s during Seattle's grunge movement, and is known for its distinctive vocal style and the harmonized vocals between Cantrell and Layne Staley. Cantrell started to sing lead vocals on Alice in Chains' 1992 EP Sap. After Staley's death in 2002, Cantrell took the role of Alice in Chains' lead singer on most of the songs from the band's post-Staley albums, Black Gives Way to Blue (2009), The Devil Put Dinosaurs Here (2013) and Rainier Fog (2018), with DuVall harmonizing with him in the new songs and singing Staley's vocals in the old songs in live concerts.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/45/Jerry_Cantrell_at_Roskilde_Festival_%28Roskilde%2C_Denmark%29_--_2_July_2010.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jerry-cantrell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>