<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Gothic Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Gothic Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 23:20:45 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robert Smith]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robert-smith-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert James Smith is an English singer, songwriter, musician, and record producer. He is the lead singer, guitarist, multi-instrumentalist, primary songwriter, and only continuous member of the rock band the Cure, which he co-founded in 1976. He was also the lead guitarist for the band Siouxsie and the Banshees from 1982 to 1984, and was part of the short-lived group the Glove in 1983. He is known for his distinctive voice, guitar-playing style and stage look, the latter two of which were influential on the goth subculture that rose to prominence in the 1980s. Smith was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Cure in 2019.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7a/Robert_Smith_-_The_Cure_-_Roskilde_Festival_2012_-_Orange_Stage_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robert-smith-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Lee]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-lee/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Lynn Hartzler, known professionally as Amy Lee, is an American singer, songwriter, and pianist. She is the co-founder and lead vocalist of the rock band Evanescence. Along with her contributions with the band, Lee has also participated on other musical projects including Walt Disney Records' Nightmare Revisited and Muppets: The Green Album. She has performed collaborations with artists such as Korn, Seether, and David Hodges. Lee composed the soundtrack to the films War Story (2014) and Indigo Grey: The Passage (2015) with cellist Dave Eggar, and the song 'Speak to Me' for the film Voice from the Stone (2017). She possesses a mezzo-soprano vocal range.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/22/AmyLee2003BillboardAwards.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-lee/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vyacheslav Butusov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vyacheslav-butusov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vyacheslav Gennadievich Butusov, is a Russian singer and songwriter. He was the lead singer of Nautilus Pompilius and U-Piter. He also has his own solo career as a singer and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e1/Vyacheslav_Butusov_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vyacheslav-butusov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ian Curtis]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ian-curtis/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ian Kevin Curtis was an English singer-songwriter and musician. He was the lead singer and lyricist of the post-punk band Joy Division and recorded two albums with the group: Unknown Pleasures (1979) and Closer (1980). Curtis was known for his bass-baritone voice, dance style, and songwriting typically filled with imagery of desolation, emptiness, and alienation.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bc/Ian_Curtis-Cardboard-Portrait.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ian-curtis/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tilo Wolff]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tilo-wolff/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tilo Wolff is a German musician who currently lives in Switzerland.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a2/Lacrimosa_2005_-_Tilo_Wolff_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tilo-wolff/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Scott Putesky]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-putesky/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Scott Mitchell Putesky, formerly known by the stage name Daisy Berkowitz, was an American musician, who was the lead guitarist and co-founder of the industrial metal band Marilyn Manson. His stage name was created by combining Daisy Duke from The Dukes of Hazzard, with the serial killer David Berkowitz. He left the band on May 8, 1996, halfway through the recording of Antichrist Superstar.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/78/Daisy_%22SMP%22_Berkowitz_and_THEE_PAUSE_of_The_Daisy_Kids.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-putesky/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>