<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Mötley Crüe</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Mötley Crüe</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:07:39 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mick Mars]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mick-mars/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Alan Deal, known professionally as Mick Mars, is an American musician, lead guitarist and co-founder of the rock band Mötley Crüe. He is known for his aggressive, melodic solos and bluesy riffs.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Mick_Mars_2012.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mick-mars/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tommy Lee]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tommy-lee/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Lee Bass is an American musician and founding member of Mötley Crüe. As well as being the band's long-term drummer, Lee founded rap-metal band Methods of Mayhem, and has pursued solo musical projects.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/24/Tommy_Lee_2012.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tommy-lee/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vince Neil]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vince-neil/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vincent Neil Wharton is an American musician. He is best known as the lead vocalist of heavy metal band Mötley Crüe which he co-founded in 1981, but he has also released three albums as a solo artist. He is known for his turbulent personal life which has led to multiple arrests and convictions, including one for vehicular manslaughter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e5/Vince_Neil.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vince-neil/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nikki Sixx]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nikki-sixx/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nikki Sixx is an American musician, songwriter, radio host, and photographer, best known as the co-founder, bassist, and primary songwriter of the band Mötley Crüe. Prior to forming Mötley Crüe, Sixx was a member of Sister before going on to form London with his Sister bandmate Lizzie Grey. In 2000, he formed side project group 58 with Dave Darling, Steve Gibb and Bucket Baker issuing one album, titled Diet for a New America, the same year while, in 2002, he formed the hard rock supergroup Brides of Destruction with L.A. Guns guitarist Tracii Guns. Formed in 2006, initially to record an audio accompaniment to Sixx's autobiography The Heroin Diaries: A Year in the Life of a Shattered Rock Star, his side band Sixx:A.M. features songwriter, producer, and vocalist James Michael and guitarist DJ Ashba.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bc/Nikki_Sixx.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nikki-sixx/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>