<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Heartland Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Heartland Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:38:12 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Mellencamp]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-mellencamp/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John J. Mellencamp, previously known as Johnny Cougar, John Cougar, and John Cougar Mellencamp, is an American musician, singer-songwriter, painter, and actor. He is known for his catchy, populist brand of heartland rock, which emphasizes traditional instrumentation. Mellencamp rose to fame in the 1980s while 'honing an almost startlingly plainspoken writing style' that, starting in 1982, yielded a string of Top 10 singles, including 'Hurts So Good,' 'Jack & Diane,' 'Crumblin' Down,' 'Pink Houses,' 'Lonely Ol' Night,' 'Small Town,' 'R.O.C.K. in the U.S.A.,' 'Paper in Fire,' and 'Cherry Bomb.' He has amassed 22 Top 40 hits in the United States. In addition, he holds the record for the most tracks by a solo artist to hit number one on the Hot Mainstream Rock Tracks chart, with seven. Mellencamp has been nominated for 13 Grammy Awards, winning one. His latest album of original songs, Sad Clowns & Hillbillies, was released on April 28, 2017 to widespread critical acclaim.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cb/JohnMellencamp01a.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-mellencamp/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:11 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bryan Adams]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bryan-adams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bryan Guy Adams is a Canadian singer, songwriter, record producer, guitarist, photographer, philanthropist and activist. He rose to fame in Canada and the United States with his 1983 album Cuts Like a Knife and turned into a global star with his 1984 album Reckless, which produced some of his best known songs, including 'Run to You', 'Summer of '69' and his first number one, 'Heaven'. In 1991, he released the album Waking Up the Neighbours, which included the song '(Everything I Do) I Do It for You'. The song became a worldwide hit and reached number 1 in many countries, including a new record of 16 consecutive weeks in the United Kingdom. Adams also had the U.S. Billboard Hot 100 number-one singles 'All for Love' and 'Have You Ever Really Loved a Woman?'</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7e/Bryan_Adams_Hamburg_MG_0631_flickr.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bryan-adams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:10 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>