<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Bass Guitar</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Bass Guitar</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:02:55 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Power]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-power/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Timothy Power is an English singer, songwriter and rhythm guitarist, best known as the frontman of Cast. He was previously the bassist and backing vocalist for the La's from 1986 to 1991. Following the dissolution of Cast in 2001, Power embarked on a solo career. In 2005, he briefly reunited with the La's, who split up again without releasing new material. Cast reformed in 2010, releasing the album Troubled Times in March 2012, followed by Kicking Up the Dust in April 2017. Power was born in Allerton, Liverpool.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/07/John_Timothy_Power.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-power/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gail Ann Dorsey]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gail-ann-dorsey/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gail Ann Dorsey is an American musician. With a long career as a session musician mainly on bass guitar, she is perhaps best known for her lengthy residency in David Bowie's band, from 1995 to Bowie's death in 2016. Aside from playing bass, she sang lead vocals on live versions of 'Under Pressure' and dueted with Bowie on other songs, including 'The London Boys', 'Aladdin Sane (1913-1938-197?)', 'I Dig Everything', accompanying Bowie on clarinet, and a cover of Laurie Anderson's 'O Superman'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7e/Gail_Ann_Dorsey.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gail-ann-dorsey/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ben Moody]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ben-moody/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Benjamin Robert 'Ben' Moody is an American musician, singer, songwriter, record producer, and actor. He is best known as co-founder, lead guitarist, and co-songwriter of rock band Evanescence from its inception in 1995 to his departure in October 2003. Since leaving Evanescence, Moody has collaborated with an array of performers vocally, instrumentally, and as a writer. He is currently a member of The Halo Method and We Are the Fallen.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Evanescence_2003_barcelona_ben_moody.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ben-moody/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jeff Ament]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeff-ament/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jeffrey Allen Ament is an American musician and songwriter who serves as the bassist for the American rock band Pearl Jam. He is considered to be one of the greatest rock bassists of all time.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b5/Jeff_Ament.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jeff-ament/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Rob Grill]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rob-grill/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Frank Grill was an American lead singer, songwriter and bass guitarist, best known as a member of the rock and roll group The Grass Roots.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/eb/The_Grass_Roots.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rob-grill/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Geezer Butler]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/geezer-butler/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Terence Michael Joseph 'Geezer' Butler is an English musician and songwriter. Butler is best known as the bassist and primary lyricist of the heavy metal band Black Sabbath. He has also recorded and performed with Heaven & Hell, GZR, and Ozzy Osbourne. He currently serves as bassist of Deadland Ritual.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7a/Heaven_And_Hell_4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/geezer-butler/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kyle Eastwood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kyle-eastwood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kyle Eastwood is an American jazz bass musician. He studied film at the University of Southern California for two years before embarking on a music career. After becoming a session player in the early 1990s and leading his own quartet, he released his first solo album, From There to Here, in 1998. His album, The View From Here, was released 2013 by Jazz Village. Eastwood plays fretted and fretless electric bass guitar and double bass.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e6/Kyle_Eastwood.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kyle-eastwood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joey Vera]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joey-vera/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph 'Joey' Vera is an American heavy metal bassist who is known as a member of the heavy metal band Armored Saint and the progressive metal band Fates Warning. In 2004-2005 he replaced Frank Bello in Anthrax as the band's bassist, but did not record with them. He was also a member of Engine, recorded with Tribe After Tribe, and appears on the OSI album Free. His first solo album, A Thousand Faces, was released in 1994. His current solo project, A Chinese Firedrill, released an album titled Circles in 2007. On August 1, 2019, Joey was announced as the touring bassist for a newly reunited Mercyful Fate filling in for Timi Hansen.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2c/Joey_Vera_%28Fates_Warning%293.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joey-vera/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Angelakos]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-angelakos/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael John Angelakos is an American musician of Greek descent, a singer, songwriter and record producer. He is best known as the frontman of the indie electronic band Passion Pit.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Flickr_-_moses_namkung_-_Passion_Pit_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-angelakos/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Serj Tankian]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Serj Tankian is an Armenian-American musician, singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, poet and political activist. He is best known as the lead vocalist, songwriter, keyboardist, and occasional live rhythm guitarist of the band System of a Down, formed in 1994.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/69/Serj_Tankian_Spirit_of_Burgas_Bulgaria_2010_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>