<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Industrial Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Industrial Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 23:20:45 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Al Jourgensen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/al-jourgensen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Allen David Jourgensen is a Cuban-American singer-songwriter, musician and music producer. Closely related with the independent record label Wax Trax! Records, Jourgensen has an active musical career that spans four decades, and is best known as the frontman of the industrial rock band Ministry, which he founded in 1981 and of which he remains the only constant member. He was also primary musician of several Ministry-related projects, such as Revolting Cocks, Lard, Buck Satan and the 666 Shooters. He has also produced and/or recorded with numerous other artists, including The Reverend Horton Heat, Prong, Skinny Puppy, Front Line Assembly, The Blackouts, Alan Vega, Iggy Pop, Adrian Sherwood, Jello Biafra and others. Jourgensen is regarded as being one of the most prominent figures of industrial music,</ref> influencing numerous other groups and musicians, both in alternative and industrial-associated acts.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/64/Al_Jourgensen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/al-jourgensen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul Landers]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-landers/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul H. Landers is a German musician, notable as guitarist for the Neue Deutsche Härte band Rammstein, and the punk rock band Feeling B.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/be/Paul_Landers_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-landers/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Justin Broadrick]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/justin-broadrick/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Justin Karl Michael Broadrick is a British singer, songwriter, guitarist and drummer. He is best known as a founding member of the band Godflesh, one of the first bands to combine elements of extreme metal and industrial music. He was briefly in the English grindcore band Napalm Death when he was a teenager in the mid-1980s, writing and recording guitar for Side One of Napalm Death's debut album, Scum. Broadrick has also maintained a parallel career as a producer, producing records and remixes for groups such as Pantera, Isis, Mogwai and Hydra Head labelmates Pelican. Since 2012, he has been releasing hard techno music under the solo moniker JK Flesh. Broadrick has set up record labels such as HeadDirt, Avalanche Recordings, Post Mortem Productions, Lo Fibre and Heartache.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bb/Jesu_Primavera_Sound_2009.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/justin-broadrick/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marilyn Manson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marilyn-manson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Hugh Warner, known professionally as Marilyn Manson, is an American singer, songwriter, record producer, actor, visual artist and music video director. He is known for his controversial stage personality and image as the lead singer of the band Marilyn Manson, which he co-founded with guitarist Daisy Berkowitz and of which he remains the only constant member. Like the other founding members of the band, his stage name was formed by combining and juxtaposing the names of two American pop cultural icons of the 1960s: actress Marilyn Monroe and criminal Charles Manson.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Revolver_Golden_Gods_Awards.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marilyn-manson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Rob Holliday]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rob-holliday/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Rob Holliday is a professional musician. He was the live guitarist of industrial metal band Marilyn Manson as well as for Gary Numan, The Prodigy, and Sulpher. He joined in 2007 as Marilyn Manson's live bassist, but switched to guitars in January 2008 due to the return of former bass player Twiggy Ramirez.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a7/Rob_Holliday_with_Marilyn_Manson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rob-holliday/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Devin Townsend]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/devin-townsend/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Devin Garrett Townsend is a Canadian musician, songwriter and record producer. He founded extreme metal band Strapping Young Lad and was its primary songwriter, vocalist, and guitarist from 1994 to 2007, and has an extensive career as a solo artist.
After performing in a number of heavy metal bands in high school, Townsend was discovered by a record label in 1993 and asked to perform lead vocals on Steve Vai's album Sex & Religion. After recording and touring with Vai, Townsend was discouraged by what he found in the music industry, and vented his anger on the solo album Heavy as a Really Heavy Thing, released under the pseudonym Strapping Young Lad. He soon assembled a band under the name, and released the critically acclaimed City in 1997. Since then, he has released three more studio albums with Strapping Young Lad, along with solo material released under his own independent record label, HevyDevy Records.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e0/Devin_Townsend_Project_GRF2012-5415.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/devin-townsend/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tim Sköld]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tim-sköld/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tim Sköld is a Swedish musician and record producer, who in addition to producing solo work, has also collaborated with multiple musical groups including Shotgun Messiah, KMFDM, Marilyn Manson and Motionless in White.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/36/Tim_Skold_of_Marilyn_Manson%2C_live_in_Florence_29052007_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tim-sköld/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Wayne Static]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wayne-static/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Wayne Richard Wells, known professionally as Wayne Static, was an American musician, best known as the lead vocalist, guitarist, keyboardist and music sequencer for metal band Static-X. He released his only solo studio album, Pighammer, on October 4, 2011.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c5/WayneStatic07.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/wayne-static/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Scott Putesky]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-putesky/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Scott Mitchell Putesky, formerly known by the stage name Daisy Berkowitz, was an American musician, who was the lead guitarist and co-founder of the industrial metal band Marilyn Manson. His stage name was created by combining Daisy Duke from The Dukes of Hazzard, with the serial killer David Berkowitz. He left the band on May 8, 1996, halfway through the recording of Antichrist Superstar.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/78/Daisy_%22SMP%22_Berkowitz_and_THEE_PAUSE_of_The_Daisy_Kids.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-putesky/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>