<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Rock En Español</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Rock En Español</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 14:32:18 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shakira]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shakira Isabel Mebarak Ripoll is a Colombian singer, songwriter, dancer, businesswoman, and philanthropist. Born and raised in Barranquilla, she made her recording debut under Sony Music Colombia at the age of 13. Following the commercial failure of her first two Colombian albums, Magia (1991) and Peligro (1993), she rose to prominence in Spanish-speaking countries with her next albums, Pies Descalzos (1995) and Dónde Están los Ladrones? (1998). Shakira entered the English-language market with her fifth album, Laundry Service (2001). It sold over 13 million copies and spawned the international number-one singles 'Whenever, Wherever' and 'Underneath Your Clothes'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/Shakira_in_Toronto_2018.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mikel Erentxun]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mikel-erentxun/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Mikel Erentxun is a Venezuelan-born Spanish rock musician of Basque heritage. Formerly with the group Duncan Dhu, he started his solo career in 1992. He has released 16 albums as a solo artist and has covered The Smiths' song, 'There Is a Light That Never Goes Out', as 'Esta luz nunca se apagará', as well as Morrissey's 'Everyday Is Like Sunday' as 'Todo es Igual Siempre'. He has collaborated with Mark Gardener, Robert Quine, drummer Pete Thomas, Lloyd Cole, Matthew Sweet and Fred Maher. In 2005 the band the Lightning Seeds sued Erentxun for alleged plagiarism of their song 'Pure', but it was finally dismissed.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ee/Mikel_Erentxun_2007.10.13_002.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mikel-erentxun/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>