<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Indie Folk</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Indie Folk</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:46:53 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jade Bird]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jade-bird/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jade Elizabeth Bird is an English singer, songwriter, musician and former Stage School pupil. Her debut EP, Something American, was released in July 2017. Rolling Stone described her vocals as 'raw and robust' with Tony Visconti stating 'she sings so adroitly, she's very intelligent as a singer and there's nothing she can't do'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/88/Jade_Bird_09_07_2018_-17_%2843969330274%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jade-bird/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Crystal Bowersox]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/crystal-bowersox/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Crystal Lynn Bowersox is an American singer, songwriter and actress who was the runner-up on the ninth season of American Idol. She was the first female finalist in three years.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b3/Crystal_Bowersox.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/crystal-bowersox/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sufjan Stevens]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sufjan-stevens/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sufjan Stevens is an American singer-songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. His debut album A Sun Came was released in 1999 on the Asthmatic Kitty label, which he cofounded with his stepfather. He received wide recognition for his 2005 album Illinois, which hit number one on the Billboard Top Heatseekers chart, and for the single 'Chicago' from that album. He received an Academy Award nomination for Best Original Song and a Grammy Award nomination for Best Song Written for Visual Media for 'Mystery of Love' from the movie Call Me by Your Name.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/84/Sufjan_Stevens_playing_banjo_edit1_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sufjan-stevens/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Elliott Smith]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elliott-smith/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steven Paul 'Elliott' Smith was an American singer, songwriter, and multi-instrumentalist. Smith was born in Omaha, Nebraska, raised primarily in Texas, and lived much of his life in Portland, Oregon, where he first gained popularity. Smith's primary instrument was the guitar, though he also used piano, clarinet, bass guitar, drums, and harmonica. Smith had a distinctive vocal style, characterized by his 'whispery, spiderweb-thin delivery', and used multi-tracking to create vocal layers, textures, and harmonies.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8c/Elliott_Smith.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elliott-smith/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Julien Baker]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/julien-baker/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Julien Rose Baker is an American singer and guitarist from Bartlett, Tennessee. She is a member of the alternative rock band Forrister, formerly known as The Star Killers. She released her first solo studio album, Sprained Ankle, on 6131 Records, in 2015, and her second solo album, Turn Out the Lights, on Matador Records, in 2017. In 2018 she co-founded the supergroup boygenius with Lucy Dacus and Phoebe Bridgers.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/Julien_Baker_%2841096346594%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/julien-baker/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marcus Mumford]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marcus-mumford/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Marcus Oliver Johnstone Mumford is a British singer, songwriter, musician and record producer best known as the lead singer of the band Mumford & Sons. He also plays a number of instruments with the group, including guitar, drums and mandolin.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/40/Mumford_drums.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marcus-mumford/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Conor Oberst]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/conor-oberst/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Conor Mullen Oberst is an American singer-songwriter best known for his work in Bright Eyes. He has also played in several other bands, including Desaparecidos, The Faint, Commander Venus, Park Ave., Conor Oberst and the Mystic Valley Band, Monsters of Folk, and Better Oblivion Community Center. Oberst was named the Best Songwriter of 2008 by Rolling Stone magazine.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6e/Flickr_-_moses_namkung_-_Conor_Oberst_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/conor-oberst/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anais Mitchell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anaïs-mitchell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Anaïs Mitchell is an American singer-songwriter, musician, and playwright. Mitchell has released seven albums, including Hadestown (2010), Young Man in America (2012), and Child Ballads (2013).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/28/Anaismitchellclearwater.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anaïs-mitchell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>