<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Thin Lizzy</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Thin Lizzy</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 01:03:45 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Sykes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-sykes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John James Sykes is an English rock guitarist, vocalist, and songwriter who has played with Streetfighter, Tygers of Pan Tang, John Sloman's Badlands, Thin Lizzy, Whitesnake, and Blue Murder. Sykes shared composing duties for all songs on Whitesnake's 1987 self-titled album with David Coverdale. Sykes is also a successful solo artist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7f/John_Sykes_1984.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-sykes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Robertson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-robertson-(guitarist)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian David Robertson is a Scottish rock guitarist, best known as a member of Thin Lizzy and Motörhead.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7d/Brian_Robertson_in_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-robertson-(guitarist)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Scott Gorham]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-gorham/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Scott Gorham is an American guitarist and songwriter who was one of the 'twin lead guitarists' for the Irish rock band, Thin Lizzy. Although not a founding member of Thin Lizzy, he served a continuous membership after passing an audition in 1974, joining the band at a time when the band's future was in doubt after the departures of original guitarist Eric Bell and his brief replacement Gary Moore. Gorham remained with Thin Lizzy until the band's breakup in 1984. He and guitarist Brian Robertson, both hired at the same time, marked the beginning of the band's most critically successful period, and together developed Thin Lizzy's twin lead guitar style while contributing dual backing vocals as well. Gorham is the band member with the longest membership after founders Brian Downey (drummer) and frontman and bass guitarist, Phil Lynott.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9b/Black_Star_Riders_%E2%80%93_Wacken_Open_Air_2014_06.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-gorham/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vivian Campbell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vivian-campbell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vivian Patrick Campbell is a Northern Irish rock guitarist. He came to prominence in the early 1980s as a member of Dio, and has been a member of Def Leppard since 1992 Campbell has also worked with Thin Lizzy, Whitesnake, Sweet Savage, Trinity, Riverdogs, and Shadow King.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/CampbellDef.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vivian-campbell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Midge Ure]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/midge-ure/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James 'Midge' Ure is a Scottish musician, singer-songwriter and producer. His stage name, Midge, is a phonetic reversal of Jim, the diminutive form of his actual name.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bc/MIDGEURE28102005.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/midge-ure/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>