<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Velvet Revolver</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Velvet Revolver</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 19:23:24 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Duff McKagan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/duff-mckagan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Andrew 'Duff' McKagan, sometimes credited as Duff 'Rose' McKagan, is an American multi-instrumentalist, singer, songwriter and author. He is best known for his twelve-year tenure as the bassist of the hard rock band Guns N' Roses, with whom he achieved worldwide success in the late 1980s and early 1990s. McKagan rejoined the band in 2016, following their induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/77/Duff_McKagan_2012.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/duff-mckagan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Scott Weiland]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-weiland/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Scott Richard Weiland was an American musician, singer and songwriter. During a career spanning three decades, Weiland was best known as the lead singer of the band Stone Temple Pilots from 1989 to 2002 and 2008 to 2013, making six records with them. He was also lead vocalist of supergroup Velvet Revolver from 2003 to 2008, recording two albums, and he recorded one album with another supergroup, Art of Anarchy. He also established himself as a solo artist, releasing three studio albums, two cover albums, and collaborations with several other musicians throughout his career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/Scott_Weiland_3.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-weiland/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Slash]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/slash/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Saul Hudson, better known by his stage name Slash, is a British–American musician and songwriter. He is the lead guitarist of the American hard rock band Guns N' Roses, with whom he achieved worldwide success in the late 1980s and early 1990s. Slash has received critical acclaim and is considered one of the greatest guitarists in rock history.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/70/Slash_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/slash/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>