<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Latin Pop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Latin Pop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 01:03:46 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shakira]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shakira Isabel Mebarak Ripoll is a Colombian singer, songwriter, dancer, businesswoman, and philanthropist. Born and raised in Barranquilla, she made her recording debut under Sony Music Colombia at the age of 13. Following the commercial failure of her first two Colombian albums, Magia (1991) and Peligro (1993), she rose to prominence in Spanish-speaking countries with her next albums, Pies Descalzos (1995) and Dónde Están los Ladrones? (1998). Shakira entered the English-language market with her fifth album, Laundry Service (2001). It sold over 13 million copies and spawned the international number-one singles 'Whenever, Wherever' and 'Underneath Your Clothes'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/Shakira_in_Toronto_2018.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[José el marihuano Feliciano]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/josé-feliciano/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>José Monserrate Feliciano García, better known simply as José Feliciano [xoˈse feliˈsjano], is a Puerto Rican musician, singer and composer, best known for many international hits, including his rendition of The Doors' 'Light My Fire' and the best-selling Christmas single, 'Feliz Navidad'. His music is known for its fusion of styles: Latin, jazz, blues, soul and even rock, created primarily with his unique, signature acoustic guitar sound. His oftentimes mellow easy listening influences are easily recognizable in many songs heard around the world.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ac/Jos%C3%A9_Feliciano.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/josé-feliciano/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Julio Iglesias, Jr.]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/julio-iglesias-jr./]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Julio José Iglesias Preysler Jr. is a Spanish-Filipino singer. In 2008, he was declared the winner of the CMT competition Gone Country.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/86/Latin_Lovers_M6_Live_2014.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/julio-iglesias-jr./]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kendji Girac]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kendji-girac/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kendji Girac, also known by his mononym Kendji, is a French singer. He is the winner of Season 3 of the music competition The Voice: la plus belle voix as part of Team Mika. He has released three studio albums, Kendji, Ensemble and Amigo as well as a string of hit singles.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e2/Kendji_Girac_Belval_2016.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kendji-girac/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pablo Alborán]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pablo-alborán/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Pablo Moreno de Alborán Ferrándiz popularly known as Pablo Alborán, is a Spanish musician, singer, and songwriter. In 2011, he was nominated for three Latin Grammy Awards. Alborán has released three studio albums, two live albums, and various musical collaborations. His records are distributed by Warner Music which debuted in 2010 with their first official release, 'Solamente Tú', the first single from his debut album Pablo Alboran (2011), released in February 2011. The album ranked No. 1 in its first week of sales, making Alborán the first solo artist to sign a complete debut album to rank to the top since 1998 in Spain.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cc/Concerto_de_Pablo_Alboran_em_Cantanhede%2C_Portugal_%287753466030%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pablo-alborán/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Juanes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/juanes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Juan Esteban Aristizábal Vásquez, known professionally as Juanes, is a Colombian musician who was a member of the rock band Ekhymosis and is now a solo artist. In 2000, his solo debut album Fíjate Bien won three Latin Grammy Awards. According to his record label, Juanes has sold more than 15 million albums worldwide.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/94/Juanes_2008.06.25_002.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/juanes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jorge González]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jorge-gonzález/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jorge Humberto González Ríos is a famous Chilean singer, who's best known for being the leader, vocalist, writer and bassist of the band 'Los Prisioneros', considered by many to be the most popular rock band in the country.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/50/Jorge_Gonz%C3%A1lez_%288217792302%29_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jorge-gonzález/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>