<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Soft Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Soft Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:07:39 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Neil Diamond]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-diamond/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Neil Leslie Diamond is an American singer-songwriter, musician and actor. With 38 songs in the Top 10 on the Billboard Adult Contemporary charts, Diamond has sold more than 100 million records worldwide, making him one of the best-selling musicians of all time. On the Hot 100 and Adult Contemporary charts, he has had ten No. 1 singles: 'Cracklin' Rosie', 'Song Sung Blue', 'Longfellow Serenade', 'I've Been This Way Before', 'If You Know What I Mean', 'Desirée', 'You Don't Bring Me Flowers', 'America', 'Yesterday's Songs', and 'Heartlight'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/17/Neil_Diamond_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-diamond/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Macdonald]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-macdonald/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Elizabeth Macdonald is a Scottish singer-songwriter, guitarist, and musician. She has sold over 12 million records worldwide. Macdonald released her debut album This Is the Life in 2007. The singles 'Mr. Rock & Roll' and 'This Is the Life' from it were chart hits. The latter charted at number one in six countries, while reaching the top 10 in another 11 countries. The album reached number one in four European countries – the United Kingdom, Denmark, the Netherlands and Switzerland – and sold three million copies worldwide. Moderate success in the American music market followed in 2008. She was a guest on shows such as The Ellen DeGeneres Show and The Late Late Show with Craig Ferguson, where she performed two singles from the album, and This Is the Life reached number 92 on the Billboard 200.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6c/Amy_MacDonald-9546.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-macdonald/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Harry Nilsson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/harry-nilsson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Harry Edward Nilsson III, known mononymously as Nilsson, was an American singer-songwriter who achieved the peak of his commercial success in the early 1970s. His work is characterized by pioneering vocal overdub experiments, returns to the Great American Songbook, and fusions of Caribbean sounds. A tenor with a 3½ octave range, Nilsson was one of the few major pop-rock recording artists of his era to achieve significant commercial success without ever performing major public concerts or undertaking regular tours. The craft of his songs and the defiant attitude he projected remains a touchstone for later generations of indie rock musicians.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/71/Harry_Nilsson_%281972%29.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/harry-nilsson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jim Messina]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jim-messina/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Messina is an American musician, songwriter, singer, guitarist, recording engineer and record producer. He was a member of the folk rock group Buffalo Springfield, a founding member of the country rock pioneering band Poco, and half of the soft rock duo Loggins and Messina with Kenny Loggins.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1b/JimMessina%28by_Scott_Dudelson%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jim-messina/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[José el marihuano Feliciano]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/josé-feliciano/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>José Monserrate Feliciano García, better known simply as José Feliciano [xoˈse feliˈsjano], is a Puerto Rican musician, singer and composer, best known for many international hits, including his rendition of The Doors' 'Light My Fire' and the best-selling Christmas single, 'Feliz Navidad'. His music is known for its fusion of styles: Latin, jazz, blues, soul and even rock, created primarily with his unique, signature acoustic guitar sound. His oftentimes mellow easy listening influences are easily recognizable in many songs heard around the world.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ac/Jos%C3%A9_Feliciano.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/josé-feliciano/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jack Johnson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-johnson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack Hody Johnson is an American singer-songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, actor, record producer, documentary filmmaker and former professional surfer. Johnson is known primarily for his work in the soft rock and acoustic genres. In 2001, he achieved commercial success after the release of his debut album, Brushfire Fairytales. Johnson has reached number one on the Billboard 200 chart with his albums Sing-A-Longs and Lullabies for the Film Curious George in 2006, Sleep Through the Static in 2008, To the Sea in 2010 and From Here to Now to You in 2013. His album In Between Dreams peaked at number two on the chart in 2005 and again in 2013.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4f/Bonnaroo08_jackjohnson2_lg.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-johnson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Yuri Antonov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yuri-antonov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Yuri Mikhailovich Antonov is a Soviet and Russian composer, singer and musician, People's Artist of Russia (1997). He is also the Distinguished performer of arts of the Russian Federation (Russia) and the Distinguished artist of the Chechnya-Ingushetia ASSR (1983).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6d/Yuri_Antonov_%28musician%29_%282015-12-10%29_04.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yuri-antonov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marty Balin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marty-balin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Marty Balin was an American singer, songwriter, and musician best known as the founder and one of the lead singers and songwriters of Jefferson Airplane and Jefferson Starship.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ea/Marty_Balin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marty-balin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[James Blunt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-blunt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Hillier Blount, better known by his stage name James Blunt, is an English singer-songwriter, record producer and former British Army officer.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e5/James-Blunt3_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-blunt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Elton John]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elton-john/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir Elton Hercules John is an English singer, songwriter, pianist, and composer. He has worked with lyricist Bernie Taupin since 1967; they have collaborated on more than 30 albums. John has sold more than 300 million records, making him one of the world's best-selling music artists. He has more than fifty Top 40 hits, as well as seven consecutive number-one albums in the United States, 58 Billboard Top 40 singles, 27 Top 10 singles, four of which peaked at number two and nine of which reached number one. His tribute single 'Candle in the Wind 1997', rewritten in dedication to Diana, Princess of Wales, sold over 33 million copies worldwide and is the best-selling single in the history of the UK and US singles charts. He has also produced records and occasionally acted in films. John owned Watford F.C. from 1976 to 1987 and from 1997 to 2002, and is an honorary Life President of the club.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/80/Elton_John_2011_Shankbone_2_%28cropped%29.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elton-john/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>