<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Jazz Fusion</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Jazz Fusion</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:03:07 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Larry Carlton]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/larry-carlton/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Larry Eugene Carlton is an American guitarist who built his career as a studio musician in the 1970s and '80s for acts such as Steely Dan and Joni Mitchell. He has participated in thousands of recording sessions, recorded on hundreds of albums in many genres, for television and movies, and on more than 100 gold records. He has been a member of the jazz fusion group The Crusaders and smooth jazz band Fourplay and has maintained a long solo career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b7/Larry_Carlton_Gibson_ES-335.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/larry-carlton/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roy Wood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-wood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roy Wood is an English singer-songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. He was particularly successful in the 1960s and 1970s as member and co-founder of The Move, Electric Light Orchestra and Wizzard. As a songwriter, he contributed a number of hits to the repertoire of these bands. Collectively, hit records by The Move, Electric Light Orchestra, Wizzard, and Wood's own solo singles demonstrated an impressive chart run for an individual, both as composer and performer. Altogether he had more than 20 singles in the UK Singles Chart under various guises, including three UK No. 1 hits.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0f/Roy_Wood_TopPop.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-wood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul Jackson, Jr.]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-jackson-jr./]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul Milton Jackson Jr. is an American fusion/urban jazz composer, arranger, producer and guitarist. He was born and raised in Los Angeles. Jackson knew by the age of fifteen that he wanted to become a professional musician. He attended the University of Southern California, majoring in music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5a/Paul_Jackson_Jr._02.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-jackson-jr./]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gary Moore]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gary-moore/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert William Gary Moore was a Northern Irish guitarist and singer-songwriter. According to Ultimate Classic Rock, Moore had a 'restless career trajectory—taking in blues, rock, heavy metal, jazz-fusion and other styles over four and a half decades'. He is often described as a virtuoso guitarist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e4/Gary-Moore-at-Pite-Havsbad.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gary-moore/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Russ Freeman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/russ-freeman-(guitarist)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Russ Freeman is a smooth jazz guitarist who is the founder and leader of the Rippingtons.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/41/Russ_Freeman.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/russ-freeman-(guitarist)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marcus Miller]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marcus-miller/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Marcus Miller is an American jazz composer, producer and multi-instrumentalist, best known as a bass guitarist. He has worked with trumpeter Miles Davis, pianist Herbie Hancock, singer Luther Vandross, and saxophonist David Sanborn, among others.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8f/Marcus_Miller_-_Leverkusener_Jazztage_2017-7051.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marcus-miller/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Javier Ruibal]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/javier-ruibal/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Javier Ruibal is a Spanish musician and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/52/JavierRuibal.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/javier-ruibal/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marc Jordan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marc-jordan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Marc Wallace Jordan, is an American-born Canadian singer-songwriter, record producer, session musician, and actor. Covering a wide variety of genres, he has written songs for a number of well-known artists, including Diana Ross, Rod Stewart, Cher, Bette Midler, Chicago, and Josh Groban. He was named best producer with Steven MacKinnon at the Juno Awards in 1994 for 'Waiting for a Miracle' from Reckless Valentine. In early 2014, Jordan was named Chair of Slaight Family Music Lab at Norman Jewison's Canadian Film Centre.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d6/Marc_Jordan_CFC_2014_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marc-jordan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Richard Henshall]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-henshall/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard 'Hen' Henshall is a British progressive metal multi-instrumentalist. He is best known for being the guitarist and keyboardist for the bands To-Mera, Haken and Opinaut. He has released one album, Earthbound, with To-Mera; five with Haken and one solo album [The Cocoon]. EP releases are Oxygen (Opinaut) and Restoration. Henshall was classically trained on the piano from the age 7. By 11-12, he started playing the guitar on a self-taught basis. He also had drums and clarinet classes.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Richard-henshall-1361087590.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-henshall/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ryō Kawasaki]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ryo-kawasaki/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ryo Kawasaki  is a jazz fusion guitarist, composer and band leader from Tokyo, Japan. He is best known as one of the first musicians to develop and popularise the fusion genre and for helping to develop the guitar synthesizer in collaboration with Roland Corporation and Korg. His album Ryo Kawasaki and the Golden Dragon Live was one of the first all digital recordings and he created the Kawasaki Synthesizer for the Commodore 64. During the 1960s, he played with various Japanese jazz groups and also formed his own bands. In the early 1970s, he moved to New York City, where he settled and worked with Gil Evans, Elvin Jones, Chico Hamilton, Ted Curson, Joanne Brackeen amongst others. In the mid-1980s, Kawasaki drifted out of performing music in favour of writing music software for computers. He also produced several techno dance singles, formed his own record company called Satellites Records, and later returned to jazz-fusion in 1991.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c0/Ryo_Kawasaki_-2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ryo-kawasaki/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>