<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Ukulele</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Ukulele</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 23:20:45 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nelly Furtado]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nelly Kim Furtado is a Canadian singer and songwriter. Furtado first gained fame with her debut album, Whoa, Nelly! (2000), which was a critical and commercial success that spawned two top 10 singles on the Billboard Hot 100, 'I'm Like a Bird' and 'Turn Off the Light'. The first of the two singles won her a Grammy Award for Best Female Pop Vocal Performance. In 2003, she released her second album, Folklore, which was preceded by the lead single, 'Powerless '.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/aa/Nelly_Furtado_at_Radio_Regenbogen_Award_2017_%286%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[L.P.]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lp-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Laura Pergolizzi, known professionally as LP, is an American singer and songwriter. She has released five albums and three EPs. She has written songs for other artists including Cher, Rihanna, the Backstreet Boys, Leona Lewis, Mylène Farmer, and Christina Aguilera.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/db/LP_WTMD_LHCollins_sms_06062014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lp-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jack Johnson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-johnson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack Hody Johnson is an American singer-songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, actor, record producer, documentary filmmaker and former professional surfer. Johnson is known primarily for his work in the soft rock and acoustic genres. In 2001, he achieved commercial success after the release of his debut album, Brushfire Fairytales. Johnson has reached number one on the Billboard 200 chart with his albums Sing-A-Longs and Lullabies for the Film Curious George in 2006, Sleep Through the Static in 2008, To the Sea in 2010 and From Here to Now to You in 2013. His album In Between Dreams peaked at number two on the chart in 2005 and again in 2013.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4f/Bonnaroo08_jackjohnson2_lg.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-johnson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul McCartney]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir James Paul McCartney is an English singer, songwriter, musician, composer, and record and film producer who gained worldwide fame as co-lead vocalist and bassist for the Beatles. His songwriting partnership with John Lennon remains the most successful in history. After the group disbanded in 1970, he pursued a successful solo career and formed the band Wings with his first wife, Linda, and Denny Laine.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d6/Paul_McCartney_in_October_2018.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kaki King]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kaki-king/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kaki King is an American guitarist and composer. King is known for her percussive and jazz-tinged melodies, energetic live shows, use of multiple tunings on acoustic and lap steel guitar, and her diverse range in different genres.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9b/WebsterHall2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kaki-king/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Syd Barrett]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/syd-barrett/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roger Keith 'Syd' Barrett was an English singer, songwriter, and musician who co-founded the rock band Pink Floyd in 1965. Characterised for his English-accented singing and free-form writing style, Barrett named the group and was their original lead singer, guitarist and principal songwriter. His innovative use of guitar techniques, such as dissonance, distortion and feedback, proved influential to many musicians.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Syd_barrett.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/syd-barrett/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Buckethead]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Patrick Carroll, known professionally as Buckethead, is an American multi-instrumental musician who has received critical acclaim for his innovative electric guitar playing. His music spans many genres, including progressive metal, funk, blues, bluegrass, ambient, and avant-garde music. He performs primarily as a solo artist, though he has collaborated extensively with a wide variety of high-profile artists such as Bill Laswell, Bootsy Collins, Bernie Worrell, Iggy Pop, Les Claypool, Serj Tankian, Bill Moseley, Mike Patton, Viggo Mortensen, That 1 Guy, Bassnectar, and was a member of Guns N' Roses from 2000 to 2004. He has released 306 studio albums, four special releases, and one EP. He has also performed on more than 50 other albums by other artists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Neumos_seattle_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Eddie Vedder]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eddie-vedder/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Eddie Jerome Vedder is an American musician, multi-instrumentalist and singer-songwriter best known as the lead vocalist, one of three guitarists, and the lyricist of the American rock band Pearl Jam. He is known for his powerful baritone vocals. He also appeared as a guest vocalist in Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to the late singer Andrew Wood. Vedder has been ranked at number 7 on a list of 'Best Lead Singers of All Time', compiled by Rolling Stone.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5b/EddieVedder.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eddie-vedder/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[George Harrison]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-harrison/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>George Harrison was an English musician, singer-songwriter, and music and film producer who achieved international fame as the lead guitarist of the Beatles. Sometimes called 'the quiet Beatle', Harrison embraced Indian culture and helped broaden the scope of popular music through his incorporation of Indian instrumentation and Hindu-aligned spirituality in the Beatles' work. Although the majority of the band's songs were written by John Lennon and Paul McCartney, most Beatles albums from 1965 onwards contained at least two Harrison compositions. His songs for the group included 'Taxman', 'Within You Without You', 'While My Guitar Gently Weeps', 'Here Comes the Sun' and 'Something'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/42/George_Harrison_1974.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-harrison/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>