<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Ukulele</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Ukulele</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 14:45:06 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mariusz Duda]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mariusz-duda/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Mariusz Duda is a Polish musician and composer best known as the bassist and vocalist in the band Riverside.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/Mariusz_Duda_%28Riverside%292.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mariusz-duda/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul McCartney]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir James Paul McCartney is an English singer, songwriter, musician, and record and film producer who gained worldwide fame as co-lead vocalist and bassist for the Beatles. His songwriting partnership with John Lennon remains the most successful in history. After the group disbanded in 1970, he pursued a solo career and formed the band Wings with his first wife, Linda, and Denny Laine.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/ACL18051018-122_%2843716152470%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Brown]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-brown/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2d/Joe_Brown_On_Stage.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-brown/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paulinho da Viola]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paulinho-da-viola/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4e/Paulinho_da_Viola.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paulinho-da-viola/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jack Johnson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-johnson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack Hody Johnson is an American singer-songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, actor, record producer, documentary filmmaker and former professional surfer. Johnson is known primarily for his work in the soft rock and acoustic pop genres. In 2001, he achieved commercial success after the release of his debut album, Brushfire Fairytales. Johnson has reached number one on the Billboard 200 chart with his albums Sing-A-Longs and Lullabies for the Film Curious George in 2006, Sleep Through the Static in 2008, To the Sea in 2010 and From Here to Now to You in 2013. His album In Between Dreams peaked at number two on the chart in 2005 and again in 2013.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4f/Bonnaroo08_jackjohnson2_lg.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-johnson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Glen Hansard]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glen-hansard/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Glen Hansard is an Irish songwriter, actor, vocalist and guitarist for the Irish group The Frames, and one half of folk rock duo The Swell Season. He is known for his acting, having appeared in the BAFTA-winning film The Commitments, as well as starring in the film Once, which earned him a number of major awards, including the Academy Award for Best Original Song for 'Falling Slowly', with co-writer and co-star Markéta Irglová.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fd/GlenHansard.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glen-hansard/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jason Mraz]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-mraz/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jason Thomas Mraz is an American guitarist, singer and songwriter. In 2002 he released his debut studio album, Waiting for My Rocket to Come, which contained the single 'The Remedy ' that reached number 15 on the Billboard Hot 100, his first top-40 hit in the US. His second album, Mr. A-Z, released in 2005, peaked at number 5 on the Billboard 200 and sold over 100,000 copies in the US. In 2008 Mraz released his third studio album, We Sing. We Dance. We Steal Things. It debuted at number 3 on the Billboard 200 and was an international commercial success primarily due to the hit 'I'm Yours'. The song peaked at number 6 on the Billboard Hot 100, giving him his first top ten single, spent a then-record 76 weeks on the Hot 100, and was certified Diamond by the RIAA in 2019. His fourth album, Love Is a Four Letter Word, peaked at number 2 on the Billboard 200, his highest-charting album to date.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/Jason_Mraz_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-mraz/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Madonna]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/madonna/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Madonna Louise Ciccone is an American singer, songwriter, and actress. Referred to as the 'Queen of Pop', she is regarded as one of the most significant figures in popular culture. Madonna is noted for her continual reinvention and versatility in music production, songwriting, and visual presentation. She is also known for pushing the boundaries of artistic expression in mainstream music while remaining completely in charge of every aspect of her career. Her works, which incorporate social, political, sexual, and religious themes, have generated both critical acclaim and controversy. Madonna is often cited as an influence by other artists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Madonna_Rebel_Heart_Tour_2015_-_Stockholm_%2823051472299%29_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/madonna/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[L.P.]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lp-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Laura Pergolizzi, known professionally as LP, is an American singer and songwriter. LP has released five albums and three EPs. LP wrote songs for other artists including Cher, Rihanna, the Backstreet Boys, Leona Lewis, Mylène Farmer, Céline Dion and Christina Aguilera.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/db/LP_WTMD_LHCollins_sms_06062014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lp-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nelly Furtado]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nelly Kim Furtado is a Canadian singer and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5b/Nelly_Furtado_at_Radio_Regenbogen_Award_2017_%285%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>