<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Merchandise » Fretboard</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Merchandise » Fretboard</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 04:55:20 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ukulele Fretboard - All Chromatic Notes up to Fret 12]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/fretboard-all-notes-12-frets/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This design shows the 12 frets of an ukulele fretboard and the positions of all notes of the chromatic scale C, D, Db, E, Eb, F, G, Gb, A, Ab, B, Bb. Knowing the notes on the fretboard is extremely helpful if you want to get creative with the uke. Get this</p><img src="/img/preview/fretboard-all-notes-12-frets.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/fretboard-all-notes-12-frets/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[None]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/fretboard-all-notes-4-frets/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This design shows the first 4 frets of an ukulele fretboard and the positions of all notes of the chromatic scale C, D, Db, E, Eb, F, G, Gb, A, Ab, B, Bb. Knowing the notes on the fretboard is extremely helpful if you want to get creative with the uke. Get this design on one of the available produc… • Millions of unique designs by independent artists. Find your thing.</p><img src="/img/preview/fretboard-all-notes-4-frets.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/fretboard-all-notes-4-frets/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ukulele Fretboard A Major Scale 12 Frets - Music Theory Design]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/a-major-scale/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This design shows 12 frets of an ukulele fretboard and the positions of the notes of the A major scale A, B, C♯, D, E, F♯, G♯. Each note has a distinct color. Knowing the notes on the fretboard is extremely helpful if you want to get creative with the uke.</p><img src="/img/preview/a-major-scale.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/a-major-scale/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ukulele Fretboard Ab Major Scale 12 Frets - Music Theory Design]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/ab-major-scale/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This design shows 12 frets of an ukulele fretboard and the positions of the notes of the Ab major scale A♭, B♭, C, D♭, E♭, F, G. Each note has a distinct color. Knowing the notes on the fretboard is extremely helpful if you want to get creative with the uk</p><img src="/img/preview/ab-major-scale.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/ab-major-scale/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ukulele Fretboard Bb Major Scale 12 Frets - Music Theory Design]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/bb-major-scale/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This design shows 12 frets of an ukulele fretboard and the positions of the notes of the Bb major scale B♭, C, D, E♭, F, G, A. Each note has a distinct color. Knowing the notes on the fretboard is extremely helpful if you want to get creative with the uke.</p><img src="/img/preview/bb-major-scale.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/bb-major-scale/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ukulele Fretboard F Major Scale 12 Frets - Music Theory Design]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/f-major-scale/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This design shows 12 frets of an ukulele fretboard and the positions of the notes of the F major scale F, G, A, B♭, C, D, E. Each note has a distinct color. Knowing the notes on the fretboard is extremely helpful if you want to get creative with the uke. G</p><img src="/img/preview/f-major-scale.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/f-major-scale/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ukulele Fretboard G Major Scale 12 Frets - Music Theory Design]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/g-major-scale/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This design shows 12 frets of an ukulele fretboard and the positions of the notes of the G major scale G, A, B, C, D, E, F♯. Each note has a distinct color. Knowing the notes on the fretboard is extremely helpful if you want to get creative with the uke. G</p><img src="/img/preview/g-major-scale.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/g-major-scale/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ukulele Fretboard D Major Scale 12 Frets - Music Theory Design]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/d-major-scale/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This design shows 12 frets of an ukulele fretboard and the positions of the notes of the D major scale D, E, F♯, G, A, B, C♯. Each note has a distinct color. Knowing the notes on the fretboard is extremely helpful if you want to get creative with the uke.</p><img src="/img/preview/d-major-scale.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/d-major-scale/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ukulele Fretboard B Major Scale 12 Frets - Music Theory Design]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/b-major-scale/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This design shows 12 frets of an ukulele fretboard and the positions of the notes of the B major scale B, C♯, D♯, E, F♯, G♯, A♯. Each note has a distinct color. Knowing the notes on the fretboard is extremely helpful if you want to get creative with the uk</p><img src="/img/preview/b-major-scale.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/b-major-scale/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ukulele Fretboard Db Major Scale 12 Frets - Music Theory Design]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/db-major-scale/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This design shows 12 frets of an ukulele fretboard and the positions of the notes of the Db major scale D♭, E♭, F, G♭, A♭, B♭, C. Each note has a distinct color. Knowing the notes on the fretboard is extremely helpful if you want to get creative with the u</p><img src="/img/preview/db-major-scale.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/merchandise/db-major-scale/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 00:00:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>