<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Banjo</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Banjo</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:49:34 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roy Clark]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-clark/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roy Linwood Clark was an American singer and musician. He is best known for having hosted Hee Haw, a nationally televised country variety show, from 1969 to 1997. Clark was an important and influential figure in country music, both as a performer and in helping to popularize the genre.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/95/WIKI_ROY_CLARK.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-clark/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ronnie Lane]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ronnie-lane/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ronald Frederick 'Ronnie' Lane was an English musician, songwriter, and producer who is best known as the bass guitarist and founding member of two prominent English rock and roll bands: Small Faces (1965–69) and subsequently Faces (1969–73). With Small Faces he was nicknamed 'Plonk'. After their breakup, reorganisation and Lane's losing the band's frontman slot to Rod Stewart, he earned the nickname 'Three-Piece'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f7/Ronnie_Lane.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ronnie-lane/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Davey Johnstone]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/davey-johnstone/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David William Logan 'Davey' Johnstone is a Scottish rock guitarist and vocalist, best known for his work with Elton John.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b3/Davey_Johnstone_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/davey-johnstone/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stan Ridgway]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stan-ridgway/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stanard 'Stan' Ridgway is an American multi-instrumentalist singer-songwriter and film and television composer known for his distinctive voice, dramatic lyrical narratives, and eclectic solo albums. He was the original lead singer and a founding member of the band Wall of Voodoo.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/07/Stan_Ridgway_and_a_Harmony_guitar.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stan-ridgway/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Martin O'Malley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/martin-o'malley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Martin Joseph O'Malley is an American politician and attorney who served as the 61st Governor of Maryland from 2007 to 2015. He previously served as Mayor of Baltimore from 1999 to 2007, and was a councilman from the Third Council District in the northeast section of the city on the Baltimore City Council from 1991 to 1999.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5a/Martin_O%27Malley_2010.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/martin-o'malley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pete Seeger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-seeger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Peter Seeger was an American folk singer and social activist. A fixture on nationwide radio in the 1940s, he also had a string of hit records during the early 1950s as a member of the Weavers, most notably their recording of Lead Belly's 'Goodnight, Irene', which topped the charts for 13 weeks in 1950. Members of the Weavers were blacklisted during the McCarthy Era. In the 1960s, Seeger re-emerged on the public scene as a prominent singer of protest music in support of international disarmament, civil rights, counterculture, and environmental causes.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/77/Pete_Seeger_sings_%28cropped%29.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-seeger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jerry Garcia]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jerry-garcia/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jerome John 'Jerry' Garcia was an American singer-songwriter and guitarist, best known for his work as the lead guitarist and as a vocalist with the band the Grateful Dead, which came to prominence during the counterculture era in the 1960s. Although he disavowed the role, Garcia was viewed by many as the leader or 'spokesman' of the group.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e8/Grateful_Dead_-_Jerry_Garcia.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jerry-garcia/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Thile]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-thile/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher Scott Thile is an American mandolinist, singer, songwriter, composer, and radio personality, best known for his work in the progressive acoustic trio Nickel Creek and the acoustic folk and progressive bluegrass quintet Punch Brothers. He is a 2012 MacArthur Fellow. In October 2016, he became the host of the radio variety show A Prairie Home Companion, which in December 2017 was renamed Live from Here.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bc/Christhile.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-thile/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Harry Chapin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/harry-chapin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Harry Forster Chapin was an American singer-songwriter, humanitarian, and producer best known for his folk rock and pop rock songs, who achieved worldwide success in the 1970s and became one of the most popular artists and highest paid performers. Chapin is also one of the best charting musical artists in the United States. Chapin, a Grammy Award winning artist and Grammy Hall of Fame inductee, has sold over 16 million records worldwide and has been described as one of the most beloved performers in music history.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/32/Harry_chapin_1978.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/harry-chapin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lewis Brian Hopkins Jones was an English musician, best known as the founder and original leader of the Rolling Stones. Initially a slide guitarist, Jones would go on to play a wide variety of instruments on Rolling Stones recordings and in concerts, such as rhythm and lead guitar, sitar, dulcimer, various keyboard instruments such as piano and mellotron, marimba, wind instruments such as harmonica, recorder, saxophone, as well as drums, vocals and numerous others.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6b/Brian_Jones%2C_Statesboro%2C_Georgia%2C_May_4%2C_1965_%28377872218%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>