<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Progressive Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Progressive Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:04:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alanis Morissette]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alanis Nadine Morissette is a Canadian-American singer, songwriter, record producer, and actress. Known for her emotive mezzo-soprano voice, Morissette began her career in Canada in the early 1990s with two mildly successful dance-pop albums. Afterwards, as part of a recording deal, she moved to Holmby Hills, Los Angeles and in 1995 released Jagged Little Pill, a more rock-oriented album which sold more than 33 million copies globally and is her most critically acclaimed work. Her follow-up album, Supposed Former Infatuation Junkie, was released in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Alanis_Morissette_5-19-2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andrey Makarevich]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrey-makarevich/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Andrey Vadimovich Makarevich PAR is a Soviet and Russian rock musician and the founder of Russia's oldest still active rock band Mashina Vremeni.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/55/Andrey_Makarevich_2019_%282%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrey-makarevich/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andy Summers]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andy-summers/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Andrew James Somers, known professionally as Andy Summers, is an English guitarist who was a member of the rock band the Police. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the band in 2003. Summers has recorded solo albums, collaborated with other musicians, composed film scores, and exhibited his photography in galleries.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/15/Andy_Summers_Marseille_2008.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andy-summers/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Richard Henshall]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-henshall/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard 'Hen' Henshall is a British progressive metal multi-instrumentalist. He is best known for being the guitarist and keyboardist for the bands To-Mera, Haken and Opinaut. He has released one album, Earthbound, with To-Mera; five with Haken and one solo album [The Cocoon]. EP releases are Oxygen (Opinaut) and Restoration. Henshall was classically trained on the piano from the age 7. By 11-12, he started playing the guitar on a self-taught basis. He also had drums and clarinet classes.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Richard-henshall-1361087590.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-henshall/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ian Anderson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ian-anderson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ian Scott Anderson is a Scottish-born musician, singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist best known for his work as the lead vocalist, flautist and acoustic guitarist of British rock band Jethro Tull. Anderson plays several other musical instruments, including keyboards, bass guitar, bouzouki, balalaika, saxophone, harmonica, and a variety of whistles. His solo work began with the 1983 album Walk into Light, and since then he has released another five works, including the sequel to the Jethro Tull album Thick as a Brick (1972) in 2012, entitled Thick as a Brick 2.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/24/Ian_Anderson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ian-anderson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Evgeny Margulis]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/evgeny-margulis/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Evgeny Shulimovich Margulis is a Russian rock and blues musician. He was a member of the bands, Mashina Vremeni and Voskreseniye and currently performs with his solo project. He is considered a 'guru' of the Moscow rock ‘n’ roll and one of the best Blues guitarists, bass guitarists and bluesmen in Russia. In 1999 he was awarded with the title of Meritorious Artist</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e3/%D0%95%D0%B2%D0%B3%D0%B5%D0%BD%D0%B8%D0%B9_%D0%9C%D0%B0%D1%80%D0%B3%D1%83%D0%BB%D0%B8%D1%81_cropped_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/evgeny-margulis/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Phil Collins]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/phil-collins/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Philip David Charles Collins is an English drummer, singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, and actor. He was the drummer and later became singer of the rock band Genesis, and is also a solo artist. Between 1982 and 1989, Collins scored three UK and seven US number-one singles in his solo career. When his work with Genesis, his work with other artists, as well as his solo career is totalled, he had more US Top 40 singles than any other artist during the 1980s. His most successful singles from the period include 'In the Air Tonight', 'Against All Odds ', 'One More Night', 'Sussudio', 'Two Hearts' and 'Another Day in Paradise'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1a/Phil_Collins_Duesseldorf.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/phil-collins/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steven Wilson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steven-wilson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steven John Wilson is an English musician, singer, songwriter and record producer, most closely associated with the progressive rock genre. Currently a solo artist, he became known as the founder, lead guitarist, lead vocalist and songwriter of the band Porcupine Tree, as well as being a member of several other bands.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/Steven_Wilson_%28ZMF_2016%29_jm13763_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steven-wilson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Oldfield]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-oldfield/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Gordon Oldfield is an English multi-instrumentalist and composer. His work blends progressive rock with world, folk, classical, electronic, ambient, and new-age music. His biggest commercial success is the 1973 album Tubular Bells – which launched Virgin Records and became a hit in America after its opening was used as the theme for the film The Exorcist. He recorded the 1983 hit single 'Moonlight Shadow' and a rendition of the Christmas piece 'In Dulci Jubilo'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/87/Mike_Oldfield_NOTP_2006.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-oldfield/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nikolai Noskov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nikolai-noskov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nikolai Ivanovich Noskov is a Russian singer and former vocalist of the hard rock band Gorky Park. Five-time winner of the Golden Gramophone. He was also a member of Москва (Moscow) ensemble in the early 1980s, in band Гран-при in 1988 just before joining Gorky Park, and much later in the 1990s in band Николай (Nikolai). Starting 1998 Noskov had a solo career releasing six solo albums. In 2015 he was jury in second season of reality TV series Glavnaya Stsena</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/32/%D0%9D%D0%B8%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%BB%D0%B0%D0%B9_%D0%9D%D0%BE%D1%81%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%B2_%D0%B2_2009_%284%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nikolai-noskov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>