<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » The Beach Boys</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » The Beach Boys</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:25:04 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Glen Campbell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glen-campbell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Glen Travis Campbell was an American singer, guitarist, songwriter, television host, and actor. He was best known for a series of hit songs in the 1960s and 1970s, and for hosting a music and comedy variety show called The Glen Campbell Goodtime Hour on CBS television, from January 1969 until June 1972. He released over 70 albums in a career that spanned five decades, selling over 45 million records worldwide, including twelve gold albums, four platinum albums, and one double-platinum album.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/65/Campbell1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glen-campbell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Wilson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-wilson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Douglas Wilson is an American musician, singer, songwriter, and record producer who co-founded the Beach Boys. After signing with Capitol Records in 1962, Wilson wrote or co-wrote more than two dozen Top 40 hits for the group. In addition to his unorthodox approaches to pop composition and mastery of recording techniques, Wilson is known for his lifelong struggles with mental illness. He is often referred to as a genius and is widely acknowledged as one of the most innovative and significant songwriters of the late 20th century.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ad/Brian_Wilson_Jan_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-wilson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Marks]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-marks/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Lee Marks is an American guitarist who was an early member of the Beach Boys. Marks was a neighborhood friend of the original band members while growing up in Hawthorne, California, and was a frequent participant at the Wilson family Sunday night singalongs. Following his initial departure from the group, Marks fronted the Marksmen and performed and recorded as a session musician.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1f/David_Marks_2019_by_Glenn_Francis.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-marks/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>