<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » New Wave</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » New Wave</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 19:54:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Peter Hook]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-hook/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Peter Hook is an English singer, songwriter, composer, multi-instrumentalist and record producer. He is best known as the bassist and co-founder of English rock bands Joy Division and New Order. Hook often used the bass as a lead instrument, playing melodies on the high strings with a signature heavy chorus effect. In New Order, he would do this, leaving the actual basslines to keyboards or sequencers. This has often been cited as a defining characteristic of the New Order sound.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1f/Peter_Hook_Nocturnal_Culture_Night_13_2018_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-hook/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robert Smith]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robert-smith-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert James Smith is an English singer, songwriter, musician, and record producer. He is the lead singer, guitarist, multi-instrumentalist, primary songwriter, and only continuous member of the rock band the Cure, which he co-founded in 1976. He was also the lead guitarist for the band Siouxsie and the Banshees from 1982 to 1984, and was part of the short-lived group the Glove in 1983. He is known for his distinctive voice, guitar-playing style and stage look, the latter two of which were influential on the goth subculture that rose to prominence in the 1980s. Smith was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Cure in 2019.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7a/Robert_Smith_-_The_Cure_-_Roskilde_Festival_2012_-_Orange_Stage_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robert-smith-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Neil Finn]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-finn/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Neil Mullane Finn is a New Zealand singer-songwriter and musician who is currently a member of Fleetwood Mac. With his brother Tim Finn, he was the co-frontman for Split Enz, a project that he joined after it was initially founded by Tim and others, and then became the frontman for Crowded House. He has also recorded several successful solo albums and assembled diverse musicians for the 7 Worlds Collide project; contributor Ed O'Brien, also guitarist for Radiohead, has hailed Finn as popular music's 'most prolific writer of great songs'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/64/Neil_Finn_with_Split_Enz.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-finn/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jean-Jacques Burnel]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jean-jacques-burnel/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jean-Jacques 'JJ' Burnel is a Franco-English musician, producer and songwriter, best known as the bass guitarist with the English rock band the Stranglers.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6e/J-J.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jean-jacques-burnel/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steven Severin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steven-severin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steven Severin, is an English musician, composer, bassist, producer and co-founding member of Siouxsie and the Banshees. He took the name 'Severin' from the Leopold von Sacher-Masoch character who is mentioned in the Velvet Underground song 'Venus in Furs'. Severin had earlier considered 'Steve Spunker' for his stage name. After the split of Siouxsie and the Banshees in 1996, Severin created his own label RE, and released several instrumental albums via his official website. In the late 2000s and the early 2010s, he regularly performed live in solo, playing music over footage of silent films.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/Siouxsie-steve-severin-oakland.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steven-severin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stan Ridgway]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stan-ridgway/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stanard 'Stan' Ridgway is an American multi-instrumentalist singer-songwriter and film and television composer known for his distinctive voice, dramatic lyrical narratives, and eclectic solo albums. He was the original lead singer and a founding member of the band Wall of Voodoo.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/07/Stan_Ridgway_and_a_Harmony_guitar.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stan-ridgway/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul Weller]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-weller/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John William 'Paul' Weller Jr is an English singer-songwriter and musician. Weller achieved fame with the punk rock/new wave/mod revival band The Jam. He had further success with the blue-eyed soul music of The Style Council (1983–1989), before establishing himself as a solo artist in 1991.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2e/Paul_Weller1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-weller/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Porl Thompson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pearl-thompson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Pearl Thompson, previously known as Porl Thompson, is an English musician best known for being a member of the Cure. Though close friends had long used the name 'Pearl', Thompson legally changed her first name to 'Pearl' in 2011.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ac/Porl_Thompson%2C_The_Cure%2C_in_Sweden_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pearl-thompson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Boli Joe Armstrong]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billie-joe-armstrong/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Billie Joe Armstrong is an American singer, songwriter, musician, record producer, and actor. Armstrong serves as the lead vocalist, primary songwriter, and lead guitarist of the punk rock band Green Day, co-founded with Mike Dirnt. He is also a guitarist and vocalist for the punk rock band Pinhead Gunpowder, and provides lead vocals for Green Day's side projects Foxboro Hot Tubs, The Network, and The Longshot.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/19/Billie_Joe_Armstrong_at_mic_in_Cardiff.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billie-joe-armstrong/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bill Nelson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-nelson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Nelson is an English singer, guitarist, songwriter, producer, painter, video artist, writer and experimental musician. He rose to prominence as the chief songwriter, vocalist and guitarist of the rock group Be-Bop Deluxe, which he formed in 1972. Nelson has been described as 'one of the most underrated guitarists of the seventies art rock movement'. In 2015, he was recognised with the Visionary award at the Progressive Music Awards.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c9/Be_Bop_Deluxe2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-nelson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>