<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Vocalist</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Vocalist</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 20:40:50 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Angelakos]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-angelakos/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael John Angelakos is an American musician of Greek descent, a singer, songwriter and record producer. He is best known as the frontman of the indie electronic band Passion Pit.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Flickr_-_moses_namkung_-_Passion_Pit_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-angelakos/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Entwistle]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-entwistle/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Alec Entwistle was an English bass guitarist, singer, songwriter, and film and music producer. In a music career that spanned more than 40 years, Entwistle was best known as the original bass guitarist for the English rock band the Who. He was the only member of the band to have formal musical training. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Who in 1990.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f5/John_Entwistle_in_1967_with_The_Who.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-entwistle/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Scott Weiland]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-weiland/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Scott Richard Weiland was an American musician, singer and songwriter. During a career spanning three decades, Weiland was best known as the lead singer of the band Stone Temple Pilots from 1989 to 2002 and 2008 to 2013, making six records with them. He was also lead vocalist of supergroup Velvet Revolver from 2003 to 2008, recording two albums, and he recorded one album with another supergroup, Art of Anarchy. He also established himself as a solo artist, releasing three studio albums, two cover albums, and collaborations with several other musicians throughout his career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/Scott_Weiland_3.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-weiland/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nick Drake]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nick-drake/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nicholas Rodney 'Nick' Drake was an English singer-songwriter. Although his music did not find a wide audience during his lifetime, he gradually achieved wider recognition and is now considered among the most influential English singer-songwriters of the last 50 years. Drake signed to Island Records when he was 20 years old and released his debut album, Five Leaves Left, in 1969. By 1972, he had recorded two more albums: Bryter Layter and Pink Moon. Neither sold more than 5,000 copies on initial release.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/61/Nick_Drake_%281971%29.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nick-drake/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Molko]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-molko/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Molko is a Scottish-American musician and songwriter who is lead vocalist and guitarist of the band Placebo. He is known in particular for his distinctive nasal, high-pitched vocals, feminine/androgynous appearance, aggressive guitar style and unique tunings.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f9/Brian_Molko_in_the_European_Parliament_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-molko/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jimi Hendrix]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jimi-hendrix/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Marshall 'Jimi' Hendrix was an American rock guitarist, singer, and songwriter. His mainstream career lasted only four years, but he is widely regarded as one of the most influential guitarists in history and one of the most celebrated musicians of the 20th century. The Rock and Roll Hall of Fame describes him as 'the greatest instrumentalist in the history of rock music'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ae/Jimi_Hendrix_1967.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jimi-hendrix/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Rudolf Schenker]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rudolf-schenker/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Rudolf Schenker is a German guitarist and founder of the hard rock band Scorpions, being the rhythm guitarist, primary songwriter and longest-serving original member.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c0/Scorpions_-_03.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rudolf-schenker/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>