<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Keyboard Instrument</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Keyboard Instrument</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:57:43 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Snowy Shaw]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/snowy-shaw/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/38/Snowy_Shaw%2C_London%2C_December_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/snowy-shaw/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Iggy Pop]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/iggy-pop/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Newell Osterberg Jr., known professionally as Iggy Pop, is an American musician, singer, lyricist, record producer and actor. Designated the 'Godfather of Punk', he was the vocalist and lyricist of influential proto-punk band The Stooges, who were formed in 1967 and have disbanded and reunited multiple times since.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4d/IggyChesterRocks.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/iggy-pop/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Glenn Frey]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glenn-frey/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Glenn Lewis Frey was an American singer, songwriter, actor and founding member of the rock band the Eagles. Frey was the co-lead singer and frontman for the Eagles, roles he came to share with fellow member Don Henley, with whom he wrote most of the Eagles' material. Frey played guitar and keyboards as well as singing lead vocals on songs such as 'Take It Easy', 'Peaceful Easy Feeling', 'Tequila Sunrise', 'Already Gone', 'James Dean', 'Lyin' Eyes', 'New Kid in Town', and 'Heartache Tonight'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8a/Glenn_Frey.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glenn-frey/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul McCartney]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir James Paul McCartney is an English singer, songwriter, musician, and record and film producer who gained worldwide fame as co-lead vocalist and bassist for the Beatles. His songwriting partnership with John Lennon remains the most successful in history. After the group disbanded in 1970, he pursued a solo career and formed the band Wings with his first wife, Linda, and Denny Laine.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/ACL18051018-122_%2843716152470%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Matt Bellamy]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/matt-bellamy/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Matthew James Bellamy is an English singer, musician, and songwriter. He is the lead vocalist, guitarist, pianist, and primary songwriter of the rock band Muse. He is recognised for his eccentric stage persona, wide tenor vocal range and musicianship. Bellamy has released solo compositions, and plays bass in the supergroup the Jaded Hearts Club; he produced their debut album, You've Always Been Here (2020).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/36/MuseO2140919-25_%2848736144762%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/matt-bellamy/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alex Chilton]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alex-chilton/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Alexander Chilton was an American singer-songwriter, guitarist, and record producer best known as the lead singer of the Box Tops and Big Star. Chilton's early commercial success in the 1960s as a teen vocalist for the Box Tops was never repeated in later years with Big Star and in his subsequent indie music solo career on small labels, but he drew an intense following among indie and alternative music musicians. He is frequently cited as a seminal influence by influential rock artists and bands, some of whose testimonials appeared in the 2012 documentary Big Star: Nothing Can Hurt Me.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5e/Alex_Chilton.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alex-chilton/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Todd Rundgren]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Todd Harry Rundgren is an American multi-instrumentalist, singer, songwriter, and record producer who has performed a diverse range of styles as a solo artist and as a member of the band Utopia. He is known for his sophisticated and often unorthodox music, his occasionally lavish stage shows, and his later experiments with interactive entertainment. He also produced music videos and was an early adopter and promoter of various computer technologies, such as using the Internet as a means of music distribution in the late 1990s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4b/Todd_Rundgren_performs_%40_WorkPlay.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sarah McLachlan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sarah-mclachlan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sarah Ann McLachlan is a Canadian singer-songwriter known for her emotional ballads and mezzo-soprano vocal range. As of 2015 she had sold over 40 million albums worldwide. McLachlan's best-selling album to date is Surfacing, for which she won two Grammy Awards and four Juno Awards. In addition to her personal artistic efforts, she founded the Lilith Fair tour, which showcased female musicians on an unprecedented scale. The Lilith Fair concert tours took place from 1997 to 1999, and resumed in the summer of 2010.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/SarahMclachlanJLC2005.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sarah-mclachlan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brendan Benson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brendan-benson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f6/Brendan_Benson_October_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brendan-benson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Conor Oberst]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/conor-oberst/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Conor Mullen Oberst is an American singer-songwriter best known for his work in Bright Eyes. He has also played in several other bands, including Desaparecidos, The Faint, Commander Venus, Park Ave., Conor Oberst and the Mystic Valley Band, Monsters of Folk, and Better Oblivion Community Center. Oberst was named the Best Songwriter of 2008 by Rolling Stone magazine.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6e/Flickr_-_moses_namkung_-_Conor_Oberst_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/conor-oberst/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>