<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Keyboard Instrument</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Keyboard Instrument</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:52:56 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mark Ronson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-ronson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Mark Daniel Ronson is a British–American musician, DJ, songwriter and record producer. Ronson is best known for his collaborations with artists such as Amy Winehouse, Lady Gaga, Adele, Lily Allen, Miley Cyrus, Queens of the Stone Age, and Bruno Mars. He has received seven Grammy Awards, including Producer of the Year for Winehouse's album Back to Black and two for Record of the Year singles 'Rehab' and 'Uptown Funk'. He received an Academy Award, a Golden Globe Award and a Grammy Award for co-writing the song 'Shallow' for the film A Star is Born (2018).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/ce/Mark_Ronson_and_Jennifer_Su%2C_2011_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-ronson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nelly Furtado]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nelly Kim Furtado is a Canadian singer and songwriter. Furtado first gained fame with her debut album, Whoa, Nelly! (2000), which was a critical and commercial success that spawned two top 10 singles on the Billboard Hot 100, 'I'm Like a Bird' and 'Turn Off the Light'. The first of the two singles won her a Grammy Award for Best Female Pop Vocal Performance. In 2003, she released her second album, Folklore, which was preceded by the lead single, 'Powerless '.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/aa/Nelly_Furtado_at_Radio_Regenbogen_Award_2017_%286%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Toto Cutugno]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/toto-cutugno/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Salvatore 'Toto' Cutugno is an Italian pop singer-songwriter and musician. He may be best known for his worldwide hit song, 'L'Italiano', released on his 1983 album of the same title. Cutugno also won the Eurovision Song Contest 1990 with the song 'Insieme: 1992', for which he wrote both lyrics and music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Toto_Cutugno.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/toto-cutugno/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sergey Shnurov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sergey-shnurov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sergey Vladimirovich Shnurov is a Russian musician and songwriter, best known as Shnur, of the ska-punk band Leningrad which he formed in 1997 and was the frontman of till the end of 2008. In December 2008 the group disbanded, Shnur with some of its members forming Rubl.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6f/Sergei_Shnurov.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sergey-shnurov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hyde]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hyde/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hideto Takarai , known exclusively by his stage name Hyde, is a Japanese musician, singer, songwriter, producer, and actor. He is best known as lead vocalist of the rock band L'Arc-en-Ciel. He is also lead vocalist of Vamps and has a solo career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/Hyde_in_2013.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hyde/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Bowie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-bowie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Robert Jones, known professionally as David Bowie, was an English singer-songwriter and actor. He was a leading figure in the music industry and is considered one of the most influential musicians of the 20th century, acclaimed by critics and musicians, particularly for his innovative work during the 1970s. His career was marked by reinvention and visual presentation, with his music and stagecraft having a significant impact on popular music. During his lifetime, his record sales, estimated at 140 million albums worldwide, made him one of the world's best-selling music artists. In the UK, he was awarded ten platinum album certifications, eleven gold and eight silver, and released eleven number-one albums. In the US, he received five platinum and nine gold certifications. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1996.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e8/David-Bowie_Chicago_2002-08-08_photoby_Adam-Bielawski-cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-bowie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Scott Weiland]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-weiland/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Scott Richard Weiland was an American musician, singer and songwriter. During a career spanning three decades, Weiland was best known as the lead singer of the band Stone Temple Pilots from 1989 to 2002 and 2008 to 2013, making six records with them. He was also lead vocalist of supergroup Velvet Revolver from 2003 to 2008, recording two albums, and he recorded one album with another supergroup, Art of Anarchy. He also established himself as a solo artist, releasing three studio albums, two cover albums, and collaborations with several other musicians throughout his career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/Scott_Weiland_3.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-weiland/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[George Ezra]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-ezra/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>George Ezra Barnett is an English singer, songwriter and guitarist. After releasing two EPs, Did You Hear the Rain? in November 2013 and Cassy O' in March 2014, Ezra rose to prominence with the release of his hit single, 'Budapest', which reached number one in several countries. His debut studio album, Wanted on Voyage, was released in June 2014, reaching number one in the UK and the top ten in seven other countries. It was also the third best-selling album of 2014 in the UK.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/63/George_Ezra_-_Wanted_on_Voyage_%28tour%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-ezra/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shawn Mendes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shawn-mendes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shawn Peter Raul Mendes is a Canadian singer, songwriter and model. He gained a following in 2013, posting song covers on the video-sharing application Vine. The following year, he caught the attention of artist manager Andrew Gertler and Island Records A&R Ziggy Chareton, which led to him signing a deal with the record label. He has since released three studio albums, headlined three world tours, and received several awards.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b4/Shawn_Mendes_at_The_Queen%27s_Birthday_Party_%28cropped_2%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shawn-mendes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anssi Kela]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anssi-kela/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Anssi Kela is a Finnish singer-songwriter multi-instrumentalist who has published six albums. During his career, Kela has sold over 230,000 records in Finland. He received four Emma awards in 2002.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/63/Anssi_Kela.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anssi-kela/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>