<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Keyboard Instrument</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Keyboard Instrument</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 23:53:43 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Serj Tankian]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Serj Tankian is an Armenian-American musician, singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, poet and political activist. He is best known as the lead vocalist, songwriter, keyboardist, and occasional live rhythm guitarist of the band System of a Down, formed in 1994.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/69/Serj_Tankian_Spirit_of_Burgas_Bulgaria_2010_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kevin Parker]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kevin-parker/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kevin Richard Parker is an Australian singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist and record producer, best known for his musical project Tame Impala, for which he writes, records, and produces the music. At the ARIA Music Awards of 2015 he won two awards, Engineer of the Year and Producer of the Year, for his work on Tame Impala's album Currents (2015).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/08/Tame_Impala_Performing_in_NYC_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kevin-parker/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Peter Hook]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-hook/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Peter Hook is an English singer, songwriter, composer, multi-instrumentalist and record producer. He is best known as the bassist and co-founder of English rock bands Joy Division and New Order. Hook often used the bass as a lead instrument, playing melodies on the high strings with a signature heavy chorus effect. In New Order, he would do this, leaving the actual basslines to keyboards or sequencers. This has often been cited as a defining characteristic of the New Order sound.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1f/Peter_Hook_Nocturnal_Culture_Night_13_2018_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-hook/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mark Ronson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-ronson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Mark Daniel Ronson is a British–American musician, DJ, songwriter and record producer. Ronson is best known for his collaborations with artists such as Amy Winehouse, Lady Gaga, Adele, Lily Allen, Miley Cyrus, Queens of the Stone Age, and Bruno Mars. He has received seven Grammy Awards, including Producer of the Year for Winehouse's album Back to Black and two for Record of the Year singles 'Rehab' and 'Uptown Funk'. He received an Academy Award, a Golden Globe Award and a Grammy Award for co-writing the song 'Shallow' for the film A Star is Born (2018).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/ce/Mark_Ronson_and_Jennifer_Su%2C_2011_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-ronson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Snowy Shaw]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/snowy-shaw/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Snowy Shaw is a Swedish heavy metal musician, based in the port city of Gothenburg in the west coast of Sweden. He has played with many heavy metal bands, like King Diamond, Dream Evil, Mercyful Fate, IllWill, Notre Dame and Memento Mori.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/38/Snowy_Shaw%2C_London%2C_December_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/snowy-shaw/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Holmes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-holmes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Holmes is an American heavy metal guitarist and songwriter. Holmes started his musical career in the Pasadena, California area in the late 1970s and early 1980s. He is best known as the lead guitarist of heavy metal band W.A.S.P. Together with Blackie Lawless and Randy Piper he was one of the founding members of the band. Holmes was a member of W.A.S.P. first from 1982 to 1990, and again from 1996 to 2001.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1b/Chris_Holmes_Tampere_2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-holmes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Todd Rundgren]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Todd Harry Rundgren is an American multi-instrumentalist, singer, songwriter, and record producer who has performed a diverse range of styles as a solo artist, and as a member of the band Utopia. He is known for his sophisticated and often-unorthodox music, flamboyant stage outfits, and his later experiments with interactive entertainment. He also produced music videos, pioneered forms of multimedia, and was an early adopter and promoter of various computer technologies, such as using the Internet as a means of music distribution in the late 1990s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4b/Todd_Rundgren_performs_%40_WorkPlay.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nelly Furtado]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nelly Kim Furtado is a Canadian singer and songwriter. Furtado first gained fame with her debut album, Whoa, Nelly! (2000), which was a critical and commercial success that spawned two top 10 singles on the Billboard Hot 100, 'I'm Like a Bird' and 'Turn Off the Light'. The first of the two singles won her a Grammy Award for Best Female Pop Vocal Performance. In 2003, she released her second album, Folklore, which was preceded by the lead single, 'Powerless '.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/aa/Nelly_Furtado_at_Radio_Regenbogen_Award_2017_%286%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bill Wyman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-wyman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bill Wyman is an English musician, record producer, songwriter and singer. He was the bass guitarist for the English rock and roll band the Rolling Stones from 1962 until 1993. Since 1997 he has recorded and toured with his own band, Bill Wyman's Rhythm Kings. He has worked producing records and films, and has scored music for film in films and television.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a3/Bill_Wyman_2009.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-wyman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Toto Cutugno]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/toto-cutugno/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Salvatore 'Toto' Cutugno is an Italian pop singer-songwriter and musician. He may be best known for his worldwide hit song, 'L'Italiano', released on his 1983 album of the same title. Cutugno also won the Eurovision Song Contest 1990 with the song 'Insieme: 1992', for which he wrote both lyrics and music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Toto_Cutugno.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/toto-cutugno/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>