<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Voice</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Voice</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 01:13:47 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Winehouse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Jade Winehouse was an English singer and songwriter. She was known for her deep, expressive contralto vocals and her eclectic mix of musical genres, including soul rhythm and blues, and jazz. Winehouse's debut album, Frank (2003), was a critical success in the UK and was nominated for the Mercury Prize. Her follow-up album, Back to Black (2006), led to five 2008 Grammy Awards, tying the then record for the most wins by a female artist in a single night, and made her the first British woman to win five Grammys, including three of the General Field 'Big Four' Grammy Awards: Best New Artist, Record of the Year and Song of the Year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Amy_Winehouse_f4962007_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Brown]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-brown-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Roger 'Joe' Brown, MBE is an English entertainer. He has worked as a rock and roll singer and guitarist for more than six decades. He was a stage and television performer in the late 1950s and has been a UK recording star since the early 1960s. He has made six films, presented specialist radio series for BBC Radio 2, appeared on the West End stage alongside Dame Anna Neagle and has written an autobiography. In recent years he has again concentrated on recording and performing music, playing two tours of around 100 shows every year and releasing an album almost every year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2d/Joe_Brown_On_Stage.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-brown-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Howie Day]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/howie-day/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Howard Kern 'Howie' Day is an American singer-songwriter. Beginning his career as a solo artist in the late 1990s, Day became known for his extensive touring and in-concert use of samplers and effects pedals in order to accompany himself. He self-financed and self-released his first album, Australia, in 2000.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/30/Howiedaycrouching.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/howie-day/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kelly Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kelly-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kelly Jones is a Welsh singer-songwriter. He is the lead singer and lead guitarist of the rock band Stereophonics.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fe/Kelly_jones_cardiff_2005.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kelly-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shakira]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shakira Isabel Mebarak Ripoll is a Colombian singer, songwriter, dancer, businesswoman, and philanthropist. Born and raised in Barranquilla, she made her recording debut under Sony Music Colombia at the age of 13. Following the commercial failure of her first two Colombian albums, Magia (1991) and Peligro (1993), she rose to prominence in Spanish-speaking countries with her next albums, Pies Descalzos (1995) and Dónde Están los Ladrones? (1998). Shakira entered the English-language market with her fifth album, Laundry Service (2001). It sold over 13 million copies and spawned the international number-one singles 'Whenever, Wherever' and 'Underneath Your Clothes'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/Shakira_in_Toronto_2018.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Max Cavalera]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/max-cavalera/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Massimiliano Antonio 'Max' Cavalera is a Brazilian singer, guitarist, and songwriter who currently plays in heavy metal bands Soulfly, Cavalera Conspiracy, and Killer Be Killed. In 1984, he co-founded the acclaimed thrash metal band Sepultura with his brother Igor Cavalera and was the band's lead singer and rhythm guitarist until he left in 1996. Cavalera was also involved in a short-lived side project called Nailbomb.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/64/Soulfly-max-2005.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/max-cavalera/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gail Ann Dorsey]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gail-ann-dorsey/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gail Ann Dorsey is an American musician. With a long career as a session musician mainly on bass guitar, she is perhaps best known for her lengthy residency in David Bowie's band, from 1995 to Bowie's death in 2016. Aside from playing bass, she sang lead vocals on live versions of 'Under Pressure' and dueted with Bowie on other songs, including 'The London Boys', 'Aladdin Sane (1913-1938-197?)', 'I Dig Everything', accompanying Bowie on clarinet, and a cover of Laurie Anderson's 'O Superman'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7e/Gail_Ann_Dorsey.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gail-ann-dorsey/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Will Oldham]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bonnie-"prince"-billy/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William 'Will' Oldham, better known by the stage name Bonnie 'Prince' Billy, is an American singer-songwriter and actor. From 1993 to 1997, he performed and recorded under variations of the Palace name, including Palace Brothers, Palace Songs, and Palace Music. After releasing material under his own name, he adopted the Bonnie 'Prince' Billy name for the majority of his output since 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/67/BonniePrinceBilly3_gobeirne.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bonnie-"prince"-billy/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Inoran]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/inoran/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kiyonobu Inoue , better known exclusively by his stage name Inoran, is a Japanese musician, singer and songwriter. He is best known as the rhythm guitarist and co-founder of the rock band Luna Sea. He started his solo career in 1997. Luna Sea disbanded in 2000, and he formed Fake? with Oblivion Dust vocalist Ken Lloyd a year later. In 2005 he left Fake? and founded Tourbillon with Luna Sea vocalist Ryuichi Kawamura and Hiroaki Hayama. He rejoined Luna Sea when they reunited in 2010, and in 2012 formed Muddy Apes with bassist Taka Hirose and guitarist Dean Tidey, both from Feeder, and 8otto's vocalist Maeson.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/37/INORAN2013.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/inoran/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ben Moody]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ben-moody/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Benjamin Robert 'Ben' Moody is an American musician, singer, songwriter, record producer, and actor. He is best known as co-founder, lead guitarist, and co-songwriter of rock band Evanescence from its inception in 1995 to his departure in October 2003. Since leaving Evanescence, Moody has collaborated with an array of performers vocally, instrumentally, and as a writer. He is currently a member of The Halo Method and We Are the Fallen.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Evanescence_2003_barcelona_ben_moody.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ben-moody/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>