<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Post Punk</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Post Punk</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:02:55 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Peter Hook]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-hook/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Peter Hook is an English singer, songwriter, composer, multi-instrumentalist and record producer. He is best known as the bassist and co-founder of English rock bands Joy Division and New Order. Hook often used the bass as a lead instrument, playing melodies on the high strings with a signature heavy chorus effect. In New Order, he would do this, leaving the actual basslines to keyboards or sequencers. This has often been cited as a defining characteristic of the New Order sound.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1f/Peter_Hook_Nocturnal_Culture_Night_13_2018_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-hook/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dado Villa-Lobos]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dado-villa-lobos/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dado Villa-Lobos is a Belgian-born Brazilian musician, best known as the ex-guitarist of post-punk band Legião Urbana. Along with singer Renato Russo and drummer Marcelo Bonfá, he was one of the founding members of that band, who formed in Brasília in 1982. Villa-Lobos remained with the band through all of their studio albums, until the group dissolved after the 1996 death of Russo. In 2005, he released his first solo album, Jardim de Cáctus, produced by Laufer.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e3/Dado_Villa-Lobos.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dado-villa-lobos/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Colin Newman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/colin-newman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Colin Newman is an English musician, record producer and record label owner. He is best known as the primary vocalist and songwriter for the post-punk band Wire.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3e/Colin_Newman.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/colin-newman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Barry Adamson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/barry-adamson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Barry Adamson is a Mercury-nominated English pop and rock musician, composer, writer, photographer and filmmaker. He came to prominence in the late 1970s as a member of the post-punk band Magazine and went on to work with Visage, The Birthday Party, Nick Cave and the Bad Seeds, and the electro musicians Pan Sonic. In addition to prolific solo work, Adamson has also remixed Grinderman, The Jon Spencer Blues Explosion, Recoil and Depeche Mode. He created the seven-minute opus Useless  remix for the latter band in 1997. He also worked on the soundtrack for David Lynch's surrealistic crime film Lost Highway.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7f/BarryAdamson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/barry-adamson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Yegor Letov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yegor-letov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Igor Fedorovich 'Yegor' Letov was a Russian poet, musician, singer-songwriter, audio engineer and conceptual art painter, best known as the founder and leader of the post-punk/psychedelic rock band Grazhdanskaya Oborona. He was also the founder of the conceptual art avant-garde project Kommunizm and psychedelic rock outfit Egor i Opizdenevshie. Letov collaborated with singer-songwriter Yanka Dyagileva and other Siberian underground artists as a record engineer and producer.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2e/Egor_Letov_2000-11-04_Nuernberg.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yegor-letov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Peter Murphy]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-murphy/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Peter John Joseph Murphy is a singer, songwriter, and musician. He was the vocalist of the goth rock band Bauhaus and later went on to release a number of solo albums, such as Love Hysteria, Deep, and Holy Smoke. Thin with prominent cheekbones, a baritone voice, and a penchant for gloomy poetics, he is often called the 'Godfather of Goth'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c6/Peter-murphy-kyoto-sf-np.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-murphy/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Lydon]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-lydon/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Joseph Lydon, also known by his stage name Johnny Rotten, is an English singer, songwriter and musician. He is best known as the lead singer of the late-1970s British punk band the Sex Pistols, which lasted from 1975 until 1978, and again for various revivals during the 1990s and 2000s. He is also the lead singer of post-punk band Public Image Ltd (PiL), which he founded and fronted from 1978 until 1993, and again since 2009. Since 2013, Lydon has held British, Irish and American citizenship.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6d/John_Lydon%2C_Primavera_Sound_Festival_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-lydon/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adrian Borland]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adrian-borland/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Adrian Kelvin Borland was an English singer, songwriter, guitarist and record producer, best known as the frontman of post-punk band The Sound.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3e/Adrian-borland-1369759928.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adrian-borland/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Molko]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-molko/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Molko is a Scottish-American musician and songwriter who is lead vocalist and guitarist of the band Placebo. He is known in particular for his distinctive nasal, high-pitched vocals, feminine/androgynous appearance, aggressive guitar style and unique tunings.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f9/Brian_Molko_in_the_European_Parliament_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-molko/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mick Harvey]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mick-harvey/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael John Harvey is an Australian musician, singer-songwriter, composer, arranger and record producer. A multi-instrumentalist, he is best known for his long-term collaborations with Nick Cave, with whom he formed The Boys Next Door, The Birthday Party and Nick Cave and the Bad Seeds.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/66/Mick_Harvey.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mick-harvey/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>