<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Fleetwood Mac</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Fleetwood Mac</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 23:54:38 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Danny Kirwan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/danny-kirwan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Daniel David Kirwan was a British musician whose greatest success came with his role as guitarist, singer and songwriter with the blues rock band Fleetwood Mac between 1968 and 1972. He released three albums as a solo artist from 1975 to 1979, recorded albums with Otis Spann, Chris Youlden, and Tramp, and worked with his former Fleetwood Mac colleagues Jeremy Spencer and Christine McVie on some of their solo projects.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/24/Fleetwood_Mac_Danny_Kirwan_6.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/danny-kirwan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Neil Finn]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-finn/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Neil Mullane Finn is a New Zealand singer-songwriter and musician who is currently a member of Fleetwood Mac. With his brother Tim Finn, he was the co-frontman for Split Enz, a project that he joined after it was initially founded by Tim and others, and then became the frontman for Crowded House. He has also recorded several successful solo albums and assembled diverse musicians for the 7 Worlds Collide project; contributor Ed O'Brien, also guitarist for Radiohead, has hailed Finn as popular music's 'most prolific writer of great songs'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/64/Neil_Finn_with_Split_Enz.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-finn/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lindsey Buckingham]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lindsey-buckingham/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lindsey Adams Buckingham is an American musician, singer, songwriter and producer, best known as lead guitarist and one of the vocalists of the music group Fleetwood Mac from 1975–1987 and 1997–2018. In addition to his tenure with Fleetwood Mac, Buckingham has released six solo albums and three live albums. As a member of Fleetwood Mac, he was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1998. In 2011, Buckingham was ranked 100th in Rolling Stone Magazine's 2011 list of 'The 100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time'. Buckingham is known for his fingerpicking guitar style.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8b/LindseyBuckingham.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lindsey-buckingham/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>