<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Recorder</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Recorder</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 13:12:59 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul McCartney]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir James Paul McCartney is an English singer, songwriter, musician, and record and film producer who gained worldwide fame as co-lead vocalist and bassist for the Beatles. His songwriting partnership with John Lennon remains the most successful in history. After the group disbanded in 1970, he pursued a solo career and formed the band Wings with his first wife, Linda, and Denny Laine.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/ACL18051018-122_%2843716152470%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kyle Gass]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kyle-gass/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kyle Richard Gass is an American musician, songwriter, singer, and actor best known as a member of Tenacious D, a Grammy-winning comedy band. He co-founded the bands Trainwreck and the Kyle Gass Band, with which he performs. He has acted in the films Elf and Kung Fu Panda as well as the TV shows Friends and Seinfeld.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f3/2017_Woodstock_203_Kyle_Gass_Band.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kyle-gass/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Paul Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-paul-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Richard Baldwin, better known by his stage name John Paul Jones, is an English musician and record producer who was the bassist and keyboardist for the rock band Led Zeppelin. Prior to forming the band with Jimmy Page in 1968, he was a session musician and arranger. After the death of drummer John Bonham in 1980, Led Zeppelin disbanded, and Jones developed a solo career. He has collaborated with musicians across a variety of genres, including Josh Homme and Dave Grohl with the supergroup Them Crooked Vultures.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/78/John_Paul_Jones_-_2010.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-paul-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ian Anderson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ian-anderson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ian Scott Anderson is a Scottish musician, singer and songwriter best known for his work as lead vocalist, flautist and acoustic guitarist of British rock band Jethro Tull. He is a multi-instrumentalist who, in addition to flute, plays keyboards, acoustic and bass guitar, bouzouki, balalaika, saxophone, harmonica, and a variety of whistles. His solo work began with the 1983 album Walk into Light; since then he has released another five works, including the sequel to the Jethro Tull album Thick as a Brick (1972) in 2012, entitled Thick as a Brick 2.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/24/Ian_Anderson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ian-anderson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lewis Brian Hopkin Jones was an English musician and composer, best known as the founder and original leader of the Rolling Stones. Initially a slide guitarist, Jones went on to play a wide variety of instruments on Rolling Stones recordings and in concerts, including rhythm guitar, lead guitar, sitar, dulcimer, various keyboard instruments such as piano and mellotron, marimba, wind instruments such as harmonica, recorder, saxophone, as well as drums, vocals and numerous others.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6b/Brian_Jones%2C_Statesboro%2C_Georgia%2C_May_4%2C_1965_%28377872218%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tim Rice-Oxley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tim-rice-oxley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e3/Tim_Rice-Oxley.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tim-rice-oxley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:38 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>