<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Opera</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Opera</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 04:55:21 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roger Waters]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roger-waters/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>George Roger Waters is an English songwriter, singer, bassist, and composer. In 1965, he co-founded the progressive rock band Pink Floyd. Waters initially served solely as the bassist, but following the departure of singer-songwriter Syd Barrett in 1968, he also became their lyricist, co-lead vocalist, and conceptual leader.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/03/Roger_Waters%2C_May_18_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roger-waters/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Carl Maria von Weber]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/carl-maria-von-weber/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Carl Maria von Weber was a German composer, conductor, virtuoso pianist, guitarist and critic who was one of the first significant composers of the Romantic era. Best known for his operas, he was a crucial figure in the development of German Romantische Oper.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/42/Caroline_Bardua_-_Bildnis_des_Komponisten_Carl_Maria_von_Weber.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/carl-maria-von-weber/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Heitor Villa-Lobos]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/heitor-villa-lobos/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Heitor Villa-Lobos was a Brazilian composer, conductor, cellist, and classical guitarist described as 'the single most significant creative figure in 20th-century Brazilian art music'. Villa-Lobos has become the best-known South American composer of all time. A prolific composer, he wrote numerous orchestral, chamber, instrumental and vocal works, totaling over 2000 works by his death in 1959. His music was influenced by both Brazilian folk music and by stylistic elements from the European classical tradition, as exemplified by his Bachianas Brasileiras and his Chôros. His Etudes for classical guitar (1929) were dedicated to Andrés Segovia, while his 5 Preludes (1940) were dedicated to his spouse Arminda Neves d'Almeida, a.k.a. 'Mindinha'. Both are important works in the classical guitar repertory.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a8/Heitor_Villa-Lobos_%28c._1922%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/heitor-villa-lobos/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:38 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>