<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Experimental Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Experimental Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:07:39 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alanis Morissette]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alanis Nadine Morissette is a Canadian-American singer, songwriter, record producer, and actress. Known for her emotive mezzo-soprano voice, Morissette began her career in Canada in the early 1990s with two mildly successful dance-pop albums. Afterwards, as part of a recording deal, she moved to Holmby Hills, Los Angeles and in 1995 released Jagged Little Pill, a more rock-oriented album which sold more than 33 million copies globally and is her most critically acclaimed work. Her follow-up album, Supposed Former Infatuation Junkie, was released in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Alanis_Morissette_5-19-2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Maureen Tucker]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/moe-tucker/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Maureen Ann 'Moe' Tucker is an American musician and singer best known for having been the drummer for the New York City-based rock band the Velvet Underground.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fa/The_Moe_Tucker_Band_%282%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/moe-tucker/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Bowie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-bowie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Robert Jones, known professionally as David Bowie, was an English singer-songwriter and actor. He was a leading figure in the music industry and is considered one of the most influential musicians of the 20th century, acclaimed by critics and musicians, particularly for his innovative work during the 1970s. His career was marked by reinvention and visual presentation, with his music and stagecraft having a significant impact on popular music. During his lifetime, his record sales, estimated at over 100 million records worldwide, made him one of the world's best-selling music artists. In the UK, he was awarded ten platinum album certifications, eleven gold and eight silver, and released eleven number-one albums. In the US, he received five platinum and nine gold certifications. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1996.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e8/David-Bowie_Chicago_2002-08-08_photoby_Adam-Bielawski-cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-bowie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Neil Young]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Neil Percival Young is a Canadian singer-songwriter. After embarking on a music career in the 1960s, he moved to Los Angeles, where he formed Buffalo Springfield with Stephen Stills, Richie Furay and others. Young had released two solo albums and three as a member of Buffalo Springfield by the time he joined Crosby, Stills & Nash in 1969. From his early solo albums and those with his backing band Crazy Horse, Young has recorded a steady stream of studio and live albums, sometimes warring with his recording company along the way.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bb/Neil_Young_-_Per_Ole_Hagen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Daniel Lanois]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daniel-lanois/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Daniel Roland Lanois is a Canadian record producer, guitarist, vocalist, and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fe/DanielLanois_7878.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daniel-lanois/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lou Reed]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lou-reed/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lewis Allan Reed was an American musician, singer, songwriter and poet. He was the lead guitarist, singer and principal songwriter for the rock band the Velvet Underground and had a solo career that spanned five decades. The Velvet Underground was not a commercial success during its existence, but became regarded as one of the most influential bands in the history of underground and alternative rock music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c9/Lou_Reed_Malaga%2C_Spain_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lou-reed/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Lydon]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-lydon/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Joseph Lydon, also known by his stage name Johnny Rotten, is an English singer, songwriter and musician. He is best known as the lead singer of the late-1970s British punk band the Sex Pistols, which lasted from 1975 until 1978, and again for various revivals during the 1990s and 2000s. He is also the lead singer of post-punk band Public Image Ltd (PiL), which he founded and fronted from 1978 until 1993, and again since 2009. Since 2013, Lydon has held British, Irish and American citizenship.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6d/John_Lydon%2C_Primavera_Sound_Festival_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-lydon/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Lennon]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-lennon/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Winston Ono Lennon was an English singer, songwriter and peace activist who gained worldwide fame as the founder, co-lead vocalist, and rhythm guitarist of the Beatles. His songwriting partnership with Paul McCartney remains the most successful in history. In 1969, he started the Plastic Ono Band with his second wife, Yoko Ono. After the Beatles disbanded in 1970, Lennon continued as a solo artist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/51/JohnLennonpeace.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-lennon/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Syd Barrett]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/syd-barrett/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roger Keith 'Syd' Barrett was an English singer, songwriter, and musician who co-founded the rock band Pink Floyd in 1965. Characterised for his English-accented singing and free-form writing style, Barrett named the group and was their original lead singer, guitarist and principal songwriter. His innovative use of guitar techniques, such as dissonance, distortion and feedback, proved influential to many musicians.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Syd_barrett.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/syd-barrett/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dustin Kensrue]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dustin-kensrue/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Dustin Michael Kensrue is a musician, songwriter and former worship leader. He is the lead vocalist and rhythm guitarist in the rock band Thrice, as well as a solo artist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/60/Dustin_Kensrue.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dustin-kensrue/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>