<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Alternative Hip Hop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Alternative Hip Hop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 23:07:39 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jason Mraz]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-mraz/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jason Thomas Mraz is an American singer-songwriter. In 2002 he released his debut studio album, Waiting for My Rocket to Come, which contained the single 'The Remedy ' that reached #4 on the US Billboard chart. His second album, Mr. A-Z, released in 2005, peaked at number 5 on the Billboard 200 and sold over 100,000 copies in the US. In 2008 Mraz released his third studio album, We Sing. We Dance. We Steal Things. It debuted at number 3 on the Billboard 200. and was an international commercial success primarily due to the hit 'I'm Yours'. The song peaked at number 6 on the Billboard Hot 100, giving him his first top ten single, and spent a then-record 76 weeks on the Hot 100. His fourth album, Love Is a Four Letter Word, peaked at number 2 on the Billboard 200, his highest-charting album to date.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/Jason_Mraz_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-mraz/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Noize MC]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/noize-mc/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Noize MC is the stage name of Ivan Alexandrovich Alexeyev, a Russian singer, rapper and actor.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/52/Noize_MC_MRPL_City_2018.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/noize-mc/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Everlast]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/everlast/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Erik Francis Schrody, known by his stage name Everlast, is an American musician, singer, rapper, actor and songwriter, known for his solo work and as the front-man for hip hop group House of Pain. He was also part of the hip hop supergroup La Coka Nostra, which consists of members of House of Pain and other rappers. In 2000, he received a Grammy Award for Best Rock Performance by a Duo or Group with Vocal with Latin rock band Santana for 'Put Your Lights On'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ae/Houseofpain-2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/everlast/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>