<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Alternative Hip Hop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Alternative Hip Hop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 19:00:47 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jason Mraz]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-mraz/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jason Thomas Mraz is an American guitarist, singer and songwriter. In 2002 he released his debut studio album, Waiting for My Rocket to Come, which contained the single 'The Remedy ' that reached number 15 on the Billboard Hot 100, his first top-40 hit in the US. His second album, Mr. A-Z, released in 2005, peaked at number 5 on the Billboard 200 and sold over 100,000 copies in the US. In 2008 Mraz released his third studio album, We Sing. We Dance. We Steal Things. It debuted at number 3 on the Billboard 200 and was an international commercial success primarily due to the hit 'I'm Yours'. The song peaked at number 6 on the Billboard Hot 100, giving him his first top ten single, spent a then-record 76 weeks on the Hot 100, and was certified Diamond by the RIAA in 2019. His fourth album, Love Is a Four Letter Word, peaked at number 2 on the Billboard 200, his highest-charting album to date.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/Jason_Mraz_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-mraz/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adam Ant]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adam-ant/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stuart Leslie Goddard, better known as Adam Ant, is an English singer and musician. He gained popularity as the lead singer of new wave group Adam and the Ants and later as a solo artist, scoring 10 UK top ten hits from 1980 to 1983, including three UK No. 1 singles. He has also worked as an actor, appearing in over two dozen films and television episodes from 1985 to 2003.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/97/Adam_Ant_by_Aaron_Rubin_at_The_Masonic.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adam-ant/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Damon Albarn]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/damon-albarn/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Damon Albarn is an English musician, singer, songwriter, and record producer, best known as the frontman and primary lyricist of the rock band Blur and as the co-founder, lead vocalist, instrumentalist, and primary songwriter of the virtual band Gorillaz.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1a/Damon_Albarn_mg_6633.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/damon-albarn/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Noize MC]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/noize-mc/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/52/Noize_MC_MRPL_City_2018.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/noize-mc/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robert Hunter]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robert-hunter-(lyricist)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert C. Christie Hunter was an American lyricist, singer-songwriter, translator, and poet, best known for his work with the Grateful Dead. Born near San Luis Obispo, California, Hunter spent some time in his childhood in foster homes, as a result of his father's abandoning his family, and took refuge in reading and writing. He attended the University of Connecticut for a year before returning to Palo Alto, where he became friends with Jerry Garcia. Garcia and Hunter began a collaboration that lasted through the remainder of Garcia's life.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0a/Robert_Hunter_Town_Hall_2013-10-10.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robert-hunter-(lyricist)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Beck]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/beck/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Beck David Hansen is an American musician, singer, songwriter, and record producer. He rose to fame in the early 1990s with his experimental and lo-fi style, and became known for creating musical collages of wide-ranging genres. He has musically encompassed folk, funk, soul, hip hop, electronic, alternative rock, country, and psychedelia. He has released 14 studio albums, as well as several non-album singles and a book of sheet music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/31/Beck_Hansen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/beck/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Everlast]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/everlast/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Erik Francis Schrody, known by his stage name Everlast, is an American musician, singer, rapper, and songwriter, known for his solo work and as the frontman for hip hop group House of Pain. He was also part of the hip hop supergroup La Coka Nostra, which consists of members of House of Pain and other rappers. In 2000, he received a Grammy Award for Best Rock Performance by a Duo or Group with Vocal with Latin rock band Santana for 'Put Your Lights On'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/75/Everlast-11.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/everlast/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:36 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>