<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Dream Pop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Dream Pop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 15:20:42 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Richard Ashcroft]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-ashcroft/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Paul Ashcroft is an English singer and songwriter. He was the lead singer and occasional rhythm guitarist of the alternative rock band The Verve from their formation in 1990 until their original split in 1999. Songs he wrote for the band include 'Bitter Sweet Symphony', 'Lucky Man', and the UK number one 'The Drugs Don't Work'. He became a successful solo artist, releasing three UK top three solo albums. The Verve reformed in 2007 but again broke up by summer 2009. Ashcroft then founded a new band, RPA & The United Nations of Sound, and released a new album on 19 July 2010. Ashcroft released his fourth solo album, These People, on 20 May 2016.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/68/Richardashcroft.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-ashcroft/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bat for Lashes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bat-for-lashes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Natasha Khan, known professionally as Bat for Lashes, is a Pakistani British singer, songwriter, and multi-instrumentalist. She has released five studio albums: Fur and Gold (2006), Two Suns (2009), The Haunted Man (2012), The Bride (2016), and Lost Girls (2019). She has received three Mercury Prize nominations. Khan is also the vocalist for Sexwitch, a collaboration with the rock band Toy and producer Dan Carey.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/74/Bat_for_Lashes_2009.05.29_005.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bat-for-lashes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:38 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lana-del-rey/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Elizabeth Woolridge Grant, known professionally as Lana Del Rey, is an American singer-songwriter. Her music is noted for its stylized, cinematic quality and exploration of themes of sadness, tragic romance, glamor, and melancholia, containing many references to pop culture, particularly 1950s and 1960s Americana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f9/Lana_Del_Rey_at_KROQ_Weenie_Roast_2017_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lana-del-rey/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:37 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>