<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Power Pop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Power Pop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 04:55:21 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pete Shelley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-shelley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Pete Shelley was an English singer, songwriter and guitarist. He formed early punk band Buzzcocks with Howard Devoto in 1976, and became the lead singer and guitarist in 1977 when Devoto left. The group released their biggest hit 'Ever Fallen in Love ' in 1978. The band broke up in 1981 and reformed at the end of the decade. Shelley also had a solo career; his song 'Homosapien' charted in the US in 1981.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/05/Pete-shelley.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-shelley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Cassadee Pope]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/cassadee-pope/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Cassadee Blake Pope is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. Pope was the lead vocalist of the rock band Hey Monday, with whom she released two studio albums and three EPs. Pope embarked on a solo career in early 2012, and released the EP Cassadee Pope in May 2012. She took part in the third season of The Voice and became the first female winner on December 18, 2012. Her debut solo country album, Frame by Frame, was released on October 8, 2013 to a top 10 Billboard 200 charting. It debuted at No. 1 on Top Country Albums, with 43,000 copies sold in its first week.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ab/Cassadeepope2010.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/cassadee-pope/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tyson Ritter]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tyson-ritter/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tyson Jay Ritter is an American singer, songwriter, musician, actor, and model. He is best known as the lead vocalist, bassist, pianist, and songwriter of the multi-platinum selling American alternative rock band the All-American Rejects. As an actor, Ritter appeared as Dane on Amazon Video's Betas, recurred as rock musician Oliver Rome on NBC's Parenthood, and has had supporting roles in films, including The House Bunny (2008) and Miss You Already (2015). In 2018, Ritter played recurring characters on two television series on AMC, Preacher and Lodge 49. Ritter joined the main cast of Preacher for its final season in 2019.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d1/TYSON.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tyson-ritter/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Entwistle]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-entwistle/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John ‍Alec ‍Entwistle was an English musician and songwriter who was the bassist ‍for the rock band the Who. Nicknamed 'The Ox' and 'Thunderfingers', Entwistle's music career spanned over four decades. He was the band's only member with formal musical training and also provided backing and occasional lead vocals. Entwistle was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Who in 1990.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f5/John_Entwistle_in_1967_with_The_Who.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-entwistle/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Owsley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/owsley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Reese 'Will' Owsley III, known professionally as Owsley, was an American singer and songwriter. His two solo albums won critical acclaim, and his debut album was nominated for a Grammy Award, as was the song 'Threaten Me With Heaven'. Owsley was also a record producer, a recording engineer, and the guitarist in Amy Grant's touring band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b7/WillOwsleyStudio.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/owsley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Demi Lovato]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/demi-lovato/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Demetria Devonne Lovato is an American singer, songwriter, and actor. After appearing on the children's television series Barney & Friends (2002–2004), Lovato rose to prominence for their role as Mitchie Torres in the musical television film Camp Rock (2008) and its sequel Camp Rock 2: The Final Jam (2010); the former film's soundtrack contained 'This Is Me', Lovato's debut single and duet with Joe Jonas, which peaked at number nine on the Billboard Hot 100.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/66/Demi_Lovato_2015.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/demi-lovato/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Collingwood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-collingwood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Chris Collingwood is an American singer, songwriter, and artist. He is best known as the former lead vocalist and founding member of the power pop band Fountains of Wayne.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/68/Chris_Collingwood_in_concert.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-collingwood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:38 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ken Stringfellow]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ken-stringfellow/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kenneth Stuart Stringfellow is an American singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, arranger, and producer. Best known for his work with The Posies, R.E.M., and the re-formed Big Star, Stringfellow's discography includes more than 200 albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/05/Ken_Stringfellow_%28edit%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ken-stringfellow/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:37 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>