<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Power Pop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Power Pop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 19:48:27 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Entwistle]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-entwistle/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Alec Entwistle was an English bass guitarist, singer, songwriter, and film and music producer. In a music career that spanned more than 40 years, Entwistle was best known as the original bass guitarist for the English rock band the Who. He was the only member of the band to have formal musical training. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Who in 1990.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f5/John_Entwistle_in_1967_with_The_Who.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-entwistle/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tom Goss]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-goss/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Patrick Goss is an American singer-songwriter and actor. Goss has self-released five studio albums, one live album, two EPs, and multiple non-album singles. He has seen commercial success with his music featured on MTV's Logo TV. He won Best Gay Musician in DC from The Washington Blade, both in 2011 and 2012. Many of Goss' songs and music videos speak to LGBT issues such as marriage equality, Don't ask, don't tell (DADT), and gay subcultures such as bears. Goss tours internationally, often playing at LGBT establishments. In 2014, Goss landed his first starring role in a feature film—the gay-themed Out to Kill.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/98/Tom_Goss_2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tom-goss/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pete Shelley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-shelley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Pete Shelley was an English singer, songwriter and guitarist. He formed early punk band Buzzcocks with Howard Devoto in 1976, and became the lead singer and guitarist in 1977 when Devoto left. The group released their biggest hit 'Ever Fallen in Love ' in 1978. It broke up in 1981 and reformed at the end of the decade. Shelley also had a solo career; his song 'Homosapien' charted in the US in 1981.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/05/Pete-shelley.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-shelley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tyson Ritter]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tyson-ritter/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tyson Jay Ritter is an American singer, songwriter, musician, actor, and model. He is best known as the lead vocalist, bassist, pianist, and songwriter of the multi-platinum selling American alternative rock band the All-American Rejects. As an actor, Ritter appeared as Dane on Amazon Video's Betas, recurred as rock musician Oliver Rome on NBC's Parenthood, and has had supporting roles in films, including The House Bunny (2008) and Miss You Already (2015). In 2018 and 2019, Ritter played recurring characters on two television series on AMC, Preacher and Lodge 49.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d1/TYSON.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tyson-ritter/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ken Stringfellow]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ken-stringfellow/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kenneth Stuart Stringfellow is an American singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, arranger, and producer. Best known for his work with The Posies, R.E.M., and the re-formed Big Star, Stringfellow's discography includes more than 200 albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/05/Ken_Stringfellow_%28edit%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ken-stringfellow/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Owsley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/owsley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Reese 'Will' Owsley III, known professionally as Owsley, was an American singer and songwriter. His two solo albums won critical acclaim, and his debut album was nominated for a Grammy Award, as was the song 'Threaten Me With Heaven'. Owsley was also a record producer, a recording engineer, and the guitarist in Amy Grant's touring band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b7/WillOwsleyStudio.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/owsley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>