<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Electric Guitar</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Electric Guitar</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 14:32:18 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Alvin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Albert Alvin is an American singer-songwriter, guitarist, music producer and poet. He is a former and founding member of the roots rock band the Blasters. Alvin has recorded and performed as a solo artist since the late 1980s and has been involved in various side projects and collaborations. He has had brief stints as a member of the bands X and the Knitters.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Dave_Alvin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Willie Nelson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Willie Hugh Nelson is an American musician, actor, and activist. The critical success of the album Shotgun Willie (1973), combined with the critical and commercial success of Red Headed Stranger (1975) and Stardust (1978), made Nelson one of the most recognized artists in country music. He was one of the main figures of outlaw country, a subgenre of country music that developed in the late 1960s as a reaction to the conservative restrictions of the Nashville sound. Nelson has acted in over 30 films, co-authored several books, and has been involved in activism for the use of biofuels and the legalization of marijuana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/WillieNelson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Justin Hayward]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/justin-hayward/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Justin David Hayward is an English musician best known as songwriter, lead singer, and guitarist of the rock band The Moody Blues. Hayward became the group's principal lead guitarist and vocalist over the 1967–1974 period, and the most prolific songwriter and composer of several international hit singles for the band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/JustinHayward3.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/justin-hayward/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andrey Makarevich]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrey-makarevich/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Andrey Vadimovich Makarevich PAR is a Soviet and Russian rock musician and the founder of Russia's oldest still active rock band Mashina Vremeni.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/55/Andrey_Makarevich_2019_%282%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrey-makarevich/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gackt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gackt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gakuto Oshiro , better known by his mononymous stage name Gackt, is a Japanese musician, singer, songwriter, record producer and actor.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a4/Gackt_%22The_World_of_Gundam%22_at_Opening_Ceremony_of_the_28th_Tokyo_International_Film_Festival_%2822442056751%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gackt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gil Ofarim]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gil-ofarim/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gil Doron Reichstadt Ofarim is a German singer, songwriter, and occasional actor. As of 2017 he is also known as the lead singer of the bands Zoo Army and Acht.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d0/Gil_Ofarim_Musik.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gil-ofarim/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Scott Weiland]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-weiland/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Scott Richard Weiland was an American musician, singer and songwriter. During a career spanning three decades, Weiland was best known as the lead singer of the band Stone Temple Pilots from 1989 to 2002 and 2008 to 2013, making six records with them. He was also lead vocalist of supergroup Velvet Revolver from 2003 to 2008, recording two albums, and he recorded one album with another supergroup, Art of Anarchy. He also established himself as a solo artist, releasing three studio albums, two cover albums, and collaborations with several other musicians throughout his career.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/Scott_Weiland_3.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-weiland/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Svetlana Surganova]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/svetlana-surganova/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Svetlana Yakovlevna Surganova is a Russian rock musician, singer and poet. She was a founding member of the popular Russian rock band Nochnye Snaipery, providing vocals and playing violin. Presently she is a founding member of 'Surganova i Orkestr' band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/74/Swetlana_Surganowa.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/svetlana-surganova/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ezra Koenig]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ezra-koenig/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ezra Michael Koenig is an American musician, singer-songwriter, record producer, radio personality, and screenwriter. He is best known as the lead vocalist and guitarist of indie rock band Vampire Weekend. Additionally, Koenig is the creator of the Netflix animated comedy series Neo Yokio and also hosts the Apple Music radio talk show Time Crisis with Ezra Koenig. Time Crisis is airing its fourth season, as of 2019.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/EZRA_AT_PITCHFORK%21.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ezra-koenig/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vince Gill]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vince-gill/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vincent Grant Gill is an American country singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. He has achieved commercial success and fame both as frontman to the country rock band Pure Prairie League in the 1970s and as a solo artist beginning in 1983, where his talents as a vocalist and musician have placed him in high demand as a guest vocalist and a duet partner.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9c/VinceGillCrossroads2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vince-gill/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>