<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » 12 String Guitar</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » 12 String Guitar</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 15:23:51 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Crosby]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-crosby/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Van Cortlandt Crosby is an American singer-songwriter and musician. In addition to his solo career, he was a founding member of both the Byrds and Crosby, Stills & Nash.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bc/David_Crosby_2019_by_Glenn_Francis.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-crosby/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Van Morrison]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/van-morrison/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir George Ivan Morrison is a Northern Irish singer-songwriter, instrumentalist and record producer. His professional career began as a teenager in the late 1950s, playing a variety of instruments including guitar, harmonica, keyboards and saxophone for various Irish showbands, covering the popular hits of that time. Van Morrison rose to prominence in the mid-1960s as the lead singer of the Northern Irish R&B and rock band, Them, with whom he recorded the garage band classic 'Gloria'. His solo career began in 1967, under the pop-hit orientated guidance of Bert Berns with the release of the hit single 'Brown Eyed Girl'. After Berns's death, Warner Bros. Records bought out his contract and allowed him three sessions to record Astral Weeks (1968). Though this album gradually garnered high praise, it was initially a poor seller.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Van-Morrison.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/van-morrison/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Beck]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/beck/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Beck Hansen is an American musician, singer, songwriter, and record producer. He rose to fame in the early 1990s with his experimental and lo-fi style, and became known for creating musical collages of wide-ranging genres. He has musically encompassed folk, funk, soul, hip hop, electronic, alternative rock, country, and psychedelia. He has released 14 studio albums, as well as several non-album singles and a book of sheet music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/31/Beck_Hansen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/beck/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Mogis]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-mogis/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a9/Mikemogis.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-mogis/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>