<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » The Venus In Furs</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » The Venus In Furs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 22:26:45 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bernard Butler]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bernard-butler/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bernard Joseph Butler is an English musician, songwriter and record producer. He is best known as the first guitarist and lyricist with Suede, until his departure in 1994. He has been hailed by some critics as the greatest guitarist of his generation; BBC journalist Mark Savage called him 'one of Britain's most original and influential guitarists'. He was voted the 24th greatest guitarist of the last 30 years in a national 2010 BBC poll and is often seen performing with a 1961 cherry red Gibson ES-355 TD SV with a Bigsby vibrato tailpiece.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8e/The_Tears-2005-Roskilde-1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bernard-butler/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Gray]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-gray/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Gray is a British singer-songwriter. He released his first album in 1993 and received worldwide attention after the release of White Ladder six years later. It was the first of three UK chart-toppers in six years for Gray, of which the latter two also made the Top 17 in the United States. White Ladder became the fifth best-selling album of the 2000s in the UK. It is ranked the tenth best-selling album of the 21st century in the United Kingdom. Gray has been nominated for four Brit Awards – twice for Best British Male.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/91/David_Gray_-_Seattle_-_2010.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-gray/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jonny Greenwood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jonny-greenwood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jonathan Richard Guy Greenwood is an English musician and composer. He is the lead guitarist and keyboardist of the alternative rock band Radiohead, and has written a number of film scores.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/ce/Jonny_Greenwood.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jonny-greenwood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Thom Yorke]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/thom-yorke/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Edward Yorke is an English musician and the singer and main songwriter of the rock band Radiohead. A multi-instrumentalist, he mainly plays guitar and keyboards. Along with the other members of Radiohead, he was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 2019.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/08/Thom_Yorke.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/thom-yorke/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>