<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Protopunk</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Protopunk</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:27:46 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[James Williamson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-williamson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Robert Williamson is an American guitarist, songwriter, record producer and electronics engineer. He was a member of the iconic proto-punk rock band The Stooges, notably on the influential album Raw Power and in the reformed Stooges from 2009 to 2016. Between his stints in music, Williamson worked in Silicon Valley developing computer chips. Most recently he has continued as a solo artist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ee/Iggy_%26_the_Stooges_%40_Brussels_Summer_Festival_2012_%288371448222%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-williamson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Maureen Tucker]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/moe-tucker/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Maureen Ann 'Moe' Tucker is an American musician and singer best known for having been the drummer for the New York City-based rock band the Velvet Underground.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fa/The_Moe_Tucker_Band_%282%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/moe-tucker/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Todd Rundgren]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Todd Harry Rundgren is an American multi-instrumentalist, singer, songwriter, and record producer who has performed a diverse range of styles as a solo artist, and as a member of the band Utopia. He is known for his sophisticated and often-unorthodox music, flamboyant stage outfits, and his later experiments with interactive entertainment. He also produced music videos, pioneered forms of multimedia, and was an early adopter and promoter of various computer technologies, such as using the Internet as a means of music distribution in the late 1990s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4b/Todd_Rundgren_performs_%40_WorkPlay.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jonathan Richman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jonathan-richman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jonathan Michael Richman is an American singer, songwriter and guitarist. In 1970, he founded the Modern Lovers, an influential proto-punk band. Since the mid-1970s, Richman has worked either solo or with low-key, acoustic and electric, backing. Currently, he plays only acoustic to protect his hearing. He is known for his wide-eyed, unaffected and childlike outlook, and music that, while rooted in rock and roll, is influenced by music from around the world.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/32/2014JonathanRichman.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jonathan-richman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lou Reed]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lou-reed/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lewis Allan Reed was an American musician, singer, songwriter and poet. He was the lead guitarist, singer and principal songwriter for the rock band the Velvet Underground and had a solo career that spanned five decades. The Velvet Underground was not a commercial success during its existence, but became regarded as one of the most influential bands in the history of underground and alternative rock music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c9/Lou_Reed_Malaga%2C_Spain_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lou-reed/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Peel]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-peel/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Peel was a New York City-based musician who first recorded in the late 1960s with Harold Black, Billy Joe White, George Cori and Larry Adam performing as David Peel and The Lower East Side Band. His raw, acoustic 'street rock' with lyrics about marijuana and 'bad cops' appealed mostly to hippies and the disenfranchised.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d2/Peel-pot-parade-1994-arch.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-peel/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ivan Kral]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ivan-kral/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ivan Král is a Czech-born American composer, filmmaker, record producer, bass guitar player, and singer-songwriter. He works across genres including punk, rock, jazz, soul, country and film scores. His songs have been recorded by such artists as U2, Pearl Jam, Téléphone, Patti Smith, Iggy Pop, David Bowie, Simple Minds, First Aid Kit, and John Waite, among others.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/df/Ival_Kral_1978.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ivan-kral/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>