<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Harmonica</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Harmonica</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 01:03:45 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shakira]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shakira Isabel Mebarak Ripoll is a Colombian singer, songwriter, dancer, businesswoman, and philanthropist. Born and raised in Barranquilla, she made her recording debut under Sony Music Colombia at the age of 13. Following the commercial failure of her first two Colombian albums, Magia (1991) and Peligro (1993), she rose to prominence in Spanish-speaking countries with her next albums, Pies Descalzos (1995) and Dónde Están los Ladrones? (1998). Shakira entered the English-language market with her fifth album, Laundry Service (2001). It sold over 13 million copies and spawned the international number-one singles 'Whenever, Wherever' and 'Underneath Your Clothes'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/Shakira_in_Toronto_2018.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alanis Morissette]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alanis Nadine Morissette is a Canadian-American singer, songwriter, record producer, and actress. Known for her emotive mezzo-soprano voice, Morissette began her career in Canada in the early 1990s with two mildly successful dance-pop albums. Afterwards, as part of a recording deal, she moved to Holmby Hills, Los Angeles and in 1995 released Jagged Little Pill, a more rock-oriented album which sold more than 33 million copies globally and is her most critically acclaimed work. Her follow-up album, Supposed Former Infatuation Junkie, was released in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Alanis_Morissette_5-19-2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Serj Tankian]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Serj Tankian is an Armenian-American musician, singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, poet and political activist. He is best known as the lead vocalist, songwriter, keyboardist, and occasional live rhythm guitarist of the band System of a Down, formed in 1994.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/69/Serj_Tankian_Spirit_of_Burgas_Bulgaria_2010_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tadeusz Nalepa]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tadeusz-nalepa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tadeusz Nalepa – was a Polish composer, guitar player, vocalist, and lyricist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Dni_Miko%C5%82owa-Tadeusz_Nalepa_10stopni_w_lewo.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tadeusz-nalepa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lowell George]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lowell-george/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lowell Thomas George was an American singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, and record producer, who was the primary guitarist, vocalist, and songwriter for the rock band Little Feat.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/19/Little_Feat_Lowell_George.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lowell-george/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robert Smith]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robert-smith-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert James Smith is an English singer, songwriter, musician, and record producer. He is the lead singer, guitarist, multi-instrumentalist, primary songwriter, and only continuous member of the rock band the Cure, which he co-founded in 1976. He was also the lead guitarist for the band Siouxsie and the Banshees from 1982 to 1984, and was part of the short-lived group the Glove in 1983. He is known for his distinctive voice, guitar-playing style and stage look, the latter two of which were influential on the goth subculture that rose to prominence in the 1980s. Smith was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Cure in 2019.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7a/Robert_Smith_-_The_Cure_-_Roskilde_Festival_2012_-_Orange_Stage_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robert-smith-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[George Thorogood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-thorogood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>George Lawrence Thorogood is an American musician, singer and songwriter from Wilmington, Delaware. His 'high-energy boogie-blues' sound became a staple of 1980s rock radio, with hits like his original songs 'Bad to the Bone' and 'I Drink Alone'. He has also helped to popularize older songs by American icons, such as 'Move It on Over', 'Who Do You Love?', and 'House Rent Boogie/One Bourbon, One Scotch, One Beer'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/58/GeorgeThorogood.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-thorogood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[L.P.]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lp-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Laura Pergolizzi, known professionally as LP, is an American singer and songwriter. She has released five albums and three EPs. She has written songs for other artists including Cher, Rihanna, the Backstreet Boys, Leona Lewis, Mylène Farmer, and Christina Aguilera.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/db/LP_WTMD_LHCollins_sms_06062014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lp-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Willy DeVille]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willy-deville/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Willy DeVille was an American singer and songwriter. During his thirty-five-year career, first with his band Mink DeVille (1974–1986) and later on his own, Deville created original songs rooted in traditional American musical styles. He worked with collaborators from across the spectrum of contemporary music, including Jack Nitzsche, Doc Pomus, Dr. John, Mark Knopfler, Allen Toussaint, and Eddie Bo. Latin rhythms, blues riffs, doo-wop, Cajun music, strains of French cabaret, and echoes of early-1960s uptown soul can be heard in DeVille's work.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/08/2008-02-26_Willy_DeVille_IMG_8267.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willy-deville/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>