<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Funk</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Funk</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 20:58:33 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[George Benson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-benson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>George Washington Benson is an American guitarist, singer, and songwriter. He began his professional career at the age of 19 as a jazz guitarist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/74/George_Benson_1998.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-benson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Corey Glover]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/corey-glover/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Corey Glover is an American singer, guitarist and actor. He is the lead vocalist of the rock band Living Colour and has toured as the vocalist for the funk band Galactic. As an actor, he played Francis in the 1986 war movie Platoon.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d0/Loz_corey_mmm.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/corey-glover/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Matthieu Chedid]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/matthieu-chedid/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b2/Matthieu_Chedid_Cannes.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/matthieu-chedid/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Franti]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-franti/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Franti is an American rapper, musician, poet, activist, documentarian, and singer-songwriter, known for his participation in many musical projects, most with a political and social emphasis, including the Beatnigs and the Disposable Heroes of Hiphoprisy. He is the creator and lead vocalist of his current independent project, Michael Franti & Spearhead, a band that blends hip hop with a variety of other styles including funk, reggae, jazz, folk, and rock. He is also an outspoken supporter for a wide spectrum of peace and social justice issues, and he is especially an advocate for peace in the Middle East.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/31/Michael_Franti_and_Spearhead_%40_Fremantle_Park_%2817_4_2011%29_%285648770710%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-franti/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Eli "Paperboy" Reed]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eli-"paperboy"-reed/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Eli 'Paperboy' Reed is an American singer and songwriter. After graduating from Brookline [Massachusetts] High School in 2002 he moved to Clarksdale, Mississippi and immersed himself in the juke joint culture of the Deep South. After spending a year in Clarksdale he enrolled at The University of Chicago to study sociology. While in Chicago he hosted a radio show called 'We Got More Soul' on the college station WHPK and played organ and piano in the South Side Chicago church of the famed Soul/Gospel singer Mitty Collier. After one year of study in Chicago he returned home to Boston to focus on music, recording his first album Sings Walkin' & Talkin' & Other Smash Hits!</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/38/Eli-Paperboy-Reed.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eli-"paperboy"-reed/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Charles Pitts]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/charles-pitts/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f7/Skip_Pitts_2nd_vrsion.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/charles-pitts/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andre 3000]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andré-3000/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>André Lauren Benjamin, better known as André 3000, is an American rapper, singer, songwriter, actor, and record producer. He is best known for being a part of southern hip hop duo Outkast alongside fellow rapper Big Boi. Many publications, such as Billboard and Showbiz Cheatsheet have listed André 3000 as one of the top 10 rappers of all time. As an actor, Benjamin has made appearances in several films and television series, including Families, The Shield, Be Cool, Revolver, Semi-Pro, Four Brothers, and in the lead role of Jimi Hendrix in All Is by My Side. He currently plays Fredwynn on the AMC anthology series, Dispatches from Elsewhere.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b4/Andre_Benjamin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andré-3000/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sandra de Sá]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sandra-de-sá/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sandra Cristina Frederico de Sá is a Brazilian singer and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a8/Sandra_de_S%C3%A1_2010_reuni%C3%A3o_no_MinC.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sandra-de-sá/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Curtis Mayfield]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/curtis-mayfield/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Curtis Lee Mayfield was an American singer-songwriter, guitarist, and record producer, and one of the most influential musicians behind soul and politically conscious African-American music. He first achieved success and recognition with the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame-inducted group The Impressions during the civil rights movement of the late 1950s and 1960s, and later worked as a solo artist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9f/Curtis_Mayfield.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/curtis-mayfield/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jason Mraz]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-mraz/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jason Thomas Mraz is an American guitarist, singer and songwriter. In 2002 he released his debut studio album, Waiting for My Rocket to Come, which contained the single 'The Remedy ' that reached number 15 on the Billboard Hot 100, his first top-40 hit in the US. His second album, Mr. A-Z, released in 2005, peaked at number 5 on the Billboard 200 and sold over 100,000 copies in the US. In 2008 Mraz released his third studio album, We Sing. We Dance. We Steal Things. It debuted at number 3 on the Billboard 200 and was an international commercial success primarily due to the hit 'I'm Yours'. The song peaked at number 6 on the Billboard Hot 100, giving him his first top ten single, spent a then-record 76 weeks on the Hot 100, and was certified Diamond by the RIAA in 2019. His fourth album, Love Is a Four Letter Word, peaked at number 2 on the Billboard 200, his highest-charting album to date.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/Jason_Mraz_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-mraz/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>