<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Funk</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Funk</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 01:11:11 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tim Maia]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tim-maia/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tim Maia was a Brazilian musician, songwriter and businessman known for his iconoclastic, ironic, outspoken, and humorous musical style. Maia contributed to Brazilian music within a wide variety of musical genres, including soul, funk, bossa nova, disco, romantic ballads, pop, rock, jazz, baião and MPB. He introduced the soul style on the Brazilian musical scene. Along with Jorge Ben, Maia pioneered MPB's samba rock genre, combining samba, soul, and funk. He is internationally recognised as one of the biggest icons of the Brazilian music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/df/TIM_MAIA_SONIA_D%27ALMEIDA_1987.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tim-maia/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[George Benson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-benson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>George Benson is an American guitarist, singer, and songwriter. He began his professional career at the age of 21 as a jazz guitarist. Benson uses a rest-stroke picking technique similar to that of gypsy jazz players such as Django Reinhardt.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/74/George_Benson_1998.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-benson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[James Brown]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-brown/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Joseph Brown was an American singer, songwriter, dancer, musician, record producer and bandleader. A progenitor of funk music and a major figure of 20th-century music and dance, he is often referred to as the 'Godfather of Soul' and 'Soul Brother No. 1'. In a career that lasted over 50 years, he influenced the development of several music genres.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5d/Jamesbrown4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-brown/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Clayton-Thomas]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-clayton-thomas/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Clayton-Thomas is a Grammy Award-winning Canadian musician, singer, and songwriter, best known as the lead vocalist of the American band Blood, Sweat & Tears. Clayton-Thomas has been inducted into the Canadian Music Hall of Fame and in 2007 his jazz/rock composition 'Spinning Wheel' was enshrined in the Canadian Songwriter's Hall of Fame. In 2010 Clayton-Thomas received his star on Canada's Walk of Fame.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/03/DavidClayton-ThomasPerforming.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-clayton-thomas/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Louis Johnson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/louis-johnson-(bassist)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Louis Johnson was an American bass guitarist. Johnson was best known for his group The Brothers Johnson and his session playing on several hit albums of the 1970s and 1980s, including the best selling album of all time, Thriller.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/30/Louis_Johnson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/louis-johnson-(bassist)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marcus Miller]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marcus-miller/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Marcus Miller is an American jazz composer, producer and multi-instrumentalist, best known as a bass guitarist. He has worked with trumpeter Miles Davis, pianist Herbie Hancock, singer Luther Vandross, and saxophonist David Sanborn, among others.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8f/Marcus_Miller_-_Leverkusener_Jazztage_2017-7051.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marcus-miller/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Drew Fortier]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/drew-fortier/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Andrew Lawrence Fortier is an American musician, guitarist, filmmaker, actor, and author. He is best known for his work with Bang Tango, Stephen Shareaux, and Zen From Mars; which he cofounded, and includes members of Kik Tracee, Enuff Z'Nuff, Flipp, and Fear Factory. He was guitarist for the now late Chuck Mosley. He has directed and edited the documentary Attack of Life: The Bang Tango Movie as well as the upcoming David Ellefson produced horror film Dwellers which Fortier also wrote and stars in. He is the author of Dark, Depressing, and Hilarious which is an autobiography on his career thus far.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5e/Drew_Fortier_performing_with_Bang_Tango_in_Minnesota_2017.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/drew-fortier/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Matthieu Chedid]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/matthieu-chedid/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Matthieu Chedid, better known by his stage name -M-, is a French rock singer-songwriter and guitar player. He holds the gold place in number of Victoires de la Musique awards, with 13 awards.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b2/Matthieu_Chedid_Cannes.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/matthieu-chedid/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[André 3000]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andré-3000/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>André Lauren Benjamin, better known by his stage name André 3000, is an American musician and actor best known for being a part of hip hop duo Outkast alongside fellow rapper Big Boi. As an actor, Benjamin has made appearances in a number of films and television series, including Families, The Shield, Be Cool, Revolver, Semi-Pro, Four Brothers, and in the lead role of Jimi Hendrix in All Is by My Side. He is widely considered among the greatest rappers of all time.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b4/Andre_Benjamin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andré-3000/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Freddie King]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/freddie-king/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Freddie King was an American blues guitarist and singer. He recorded several hits for Federal Records in the early 1960s. His soulful and powerful voice and distinctive guitar style inspired many musicians, particularly guitarists. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 2012.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/87/Freddie_King_1975_6.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/freddie-king/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>