<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Pop Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Pop Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 11:07:50 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shakira]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shakira Isabel Mebarak Ripoll is a Colombian singer, songwriter, record producer, dancer, actress, and philanthropist. Born and raised in Barranquilla, Shakira has been referred to as the Queen of Latin Music and is noted for her versatility in music. She made her recording debut under Sony Music Colombia at the age of 13. Following the commercial failure of her first two Colombian albums, Magia (1991) and Peligro (1993), she rose to prominence in Hispanic countries with her next albums, Pies Descalzos (1995) and Dónde Están los Ladrones? (1998). Shakira entered the English-language market with her fifth album, Laundry Service (2001). It sold over 13 million copies, spawned the international number-one singles 'Whenever, Wherever' and 'Underneath Your Clothes', and propelled her reputation as a leading crossover artist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/86/Shakira_%26_Chris_Martin_-_Global_Citizen_Festival_Hamburg_04_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:49 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Madonna]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/madonna/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Madonna Louise Ciccone is an American singer-songwriter and actress. Referred to as the 'Queen of Pop', she is regarded as one of the most influential figures in popular culture. Madonna is noted for her continual reinvention and versatility in music production, songwriting, and visual presentation. Additionally she is recognized for pushing the boundaries of artistic expression in mainstream music while remaining completely in charge of every aspect of her career. Her works, which incorporate social, political, sexual, and religious themes, have generated both critical acclaim and controversy. Madonna is often cited as an influence by other artists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Madonna_Rebel_Heart_Tour_2015_-_Stockholm_%2823051472299%29_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/madonna/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Power]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-power/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Timothy Power is an English singer, songwriter and rhythm guitarist, best known as the frontman of 1990s Indie rock band Cast. He was previously the bassist and backing vocalist for the La's from 1986 to 1991. Following the dissolution of Cast in 2001, Power embarked on a solo career. In 2005, he briefly reunited with the La's, who split up again without releasing new material. Cast reformed in 2010, releasing the album Troubled Times in March 2012, followed by Kicking Up the Dust in April 2017. Power was born in Allerton, Liverpool.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/07/John_Timothy_Power.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-power/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andrew Ridgeley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrew-ridgeley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/Andrew_Ridgeley_circa_1984-1985.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrew-ridgeley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stig Rästa]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stig-rästa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ab/20150515_ESC_2015_Elina_Born_%26_Stig_R%C3%A4sta_6976.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stig-rästa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Willie Nelson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Willie Hugh Nelson is an American musician, actor, and activist. The critical success of the album Shotgun Willie (1973), combined with the critical and commercial success of Red Headed Stranger (1975) and Stardust (1978), made Nelson one of the most recognized artists in country music. He was one of the main figures of outlaw country, a subgenre of country music that developed in the late 1960s as a reaction to the conservative restrictions of the Nashville sound. Nelson has acted in over 30 films, co-authored several books, and has been involved in activism for the use of biofuels and the legalization of marijuana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/WillieNelson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nils Lofgren]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nils-lofgren/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nils Hilmer Lofgren is an American rock musician, recording artist, songwriter, and multi-instrumentalist. Along with his work as a solo artist, he has been a member of Bruce Springsteen's E Street Band since 1984, a member of Crazy Horse, and founder/frontman of the band Grin. Lofgren was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the E Street Band in 2014.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/36/Nils_Lofgren_Olbrich.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nils-lofgren/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alanis Morissette]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alanis Nadine Morissette is a Canadian-American singer, songwriter, record producer, and actress. Known for her emotive mezzo-soprano voice, Morissette began her career in Canada in the early 1990s with two mildly successful dance-pop albums. Afterward, as part of a recording deal, she moved to Holmby Hills, Los Angeles. In 1995, she released Jagged Little Pill, a more rock-oriented album which sold more than 33 million copies globally and is her most critically acclaimed work to date. This was made into a rock musical of the same name in 2017, which earned 15 Tony Award nominations including Best Musical. Her follow-up album, Supposed Former Infatuation Junkie, was released in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Alanis_Morissette_5-19-2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tracy Chapman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tracy-chapman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tracy Chapman is an American singer-songwriter, known for her hits 'Fast Car' and 'Give Me One Reason', along with other singles 'Talkin' 'bout a Revolution', 'Baby Can I Hold You', 'Crossroads', 'New Beginning', and 'Telling Stories'. She is a multi-platinum and four-time Grammy Award–winning artist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5e/Tracy_Chapman_3.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tracy-chapman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[k.d. lang]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/k.d.-lang/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kathryn Dawn Lang, known by her stylized stage name k.d. lang, is a Canadian pop and country singer-songwriter and occasional actress. Lang has won Juno Awards and Grammy Awards for her musical performances. Hits include the songs 'Constant Craving' and 'Miss Chatelaine'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/88/Pop_Conference_2016_-_Keynote_-_29_-_k.d._lang.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/k.d.-lang/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>