<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » The White Stripes</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » The White Stripes</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 21:22:37 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jack White]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-white/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Anthony White is an American singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist and producer. He is best known as the lead singer and guitarist of the duo the White Stripes, but has also had success in other bands and as a solo artist. White has enjoyed consistent critical and popular success and is widely credited as one of the key artists in the garage rock revival of the 2000s. He has won 12 Grammy Awards, and all three of his solo albums have reached number one on the Billboard charts. Rolling Stone ranked him number 70 on its 2010 list of 'The 100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time'. David Fricke's 2011 list ranked him at number 17.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/11/Jack_White_Ottawa.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-white/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Meg White]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/meg-white/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Megan Martha White is an American former musician and singer best known for her work as the drummer of Detroit rock duo the White Stripes. Her music career began when, on a whim, she played on her future White Stripes bandmate Jack White's drums in 1997. Inspired by her minimalist and untrained drumming style, he decided to form a band with her and they began performing two months later. The band quickly became a Detroit underground favorite before achieving international fame. White has been nominated for various awards as a part of the White Stripes, receiving four Grammy Awards.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/84/Meg_White.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/meg-white/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>