<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Harp</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Harp</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:12:56 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sarah McLachlan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sarah-mclachlan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sarah Ann McLachlan is a Canadian singer-songwriter known for her emotional ballads and mezzo-soprano vocal range. As of 2015 she had sold over 40 million albums worldwide. McLachlan's best-selling album to date is Surfacing, for which she won two Grammy Awards and four Juno Awards. In addition to her personal artistic efforts, she founded the Lilith Fair tour, which showcased female musicians on an unprecedented scale. The Lilith Fair concert tours took place from 1997 to 1999, and resumed in the summer of 2010.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/SarahMclachlanJLC2005.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sarah-mclachlan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sophie Hunger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sophie-hunger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e7/Sophie_Hunger_2009.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sophie-hunger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Mayall]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-mayall/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Mayall, OBE is an English blues singer, guitarist, organist and songwriter, whose musical career spans over sixty years. In the 1960s, he was the founder of John Mayall & the Bluesbreakers, a band which has counted among its members some of the most famous blues and blues rock musicians.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e7/John_Mayall_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-mayall/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Lee]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-lee/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Lynn Hartzler is an American singer, songwriter, and pianist. She is the co-founder and lead vocalist of the rock band Evanescence. Alongside her contributions with the band, Lee has also participated on other musical projects including Nightmare Revisited and Muppets: The Green Album from Walt Disney Records. She has performed collaborations with artists such as Korn, Seether, and David Hodges. Lee composed the soundtrack to the films War Story (2014) and Indigo Grey: The Passage (2015) with cellist Dave Eggar, and the song 'Speak to Me' for the film Voice from the Stone (2017). She possesses a mezzo-soprano vocal range.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0e/Amy_Lynn_Lee_in_2015.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-lee/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lewis Brian Hopkin Jones was an English musician and composer, best known as the founder and original leader of the Rolling Stones. Initially a slide guitarist, Jones went on to play a wide variety of instruments on Rolling Stones recordings and in concerts, including rhythm guitar, lead guitar, sitar, dulcimer, various keyboard instruments such as piano and mellotron, marimba, wind instruments such as harmonica, recorder, saxophone, as well as drums, vocals and numerous others.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6b/Brian_Jones%2C_Statesboro%2C_Georgia%2C_May_4%2C_1965_%28377872218%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jon Anderson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jon-anderson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Roy Anderson, known professionally as Jon Anderson, is an English-American singer and songwriter best known as the former lead singer of the progressive rock band Yes, which he formed in 1968 with bassist Chris Squire. He was a member of the band across three tenures until 2008. Anderson was also a member of Yes Featuring Jon Anderson, Trevor Rabin, Rick Wakeman.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d8/Jon_Anderson_-_Vicenza_29-11-07_5.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jon-anderson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:38 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>