<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Fiddle</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Fiddle</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 20:40:49 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tim O'Brien]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tim-o'brien/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tim O'Brien is an American country and bluegrass musician. In addition to singing, he plays guitar, fiddle, mandolin, banjo, bouzouki and mandocello. He has released more than ten studio albums, in addition to charting a duet with Kathy Mattea entitled 'The Battle Hymn of Love', a No. 9 hit on the Billboard Hot Country Singles & Tracks charts in 1990. In November 2013 he was inducted into the West Virginia Music Hall of Fame.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/99/Tim_O_Brien.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tim-o'brien/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Hartford]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-hartford/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Cowan Hartford was an American folk, country, and bluegrass composer and musician known for his mastery of the fiddle and banjo, as well as for his witty lyrics, unique vocal style, and extensive knowledge of Mississippi River lore. His most successful song is 'Gentle on My Mind', which won three Grammy Awards and was listed in 'BMI's Top 100 Songs of the Century'. Hartford performed with a variety of ensembles throughout his career, and is perhaps best known for his solo performances where he would interchange the guitar, banjo, and fiddle from song to song. He also invented his own shuffle tap dance move, and clogged on an amplified piece of plywood while he played and sang.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bc/Image-John_Hartford_playing_at_Merlefest%2C_North_Carolina_%282000%29-fls.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-hartford/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Swarbrick]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-swarbrick/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Cyril Eric Swarbrick was an English folk musician and singer-songwriter. He has been described by Ashley Hutchings as 'the most influential [British] fiddle player bar none' and his style has been copied or developed by almost every British and many world folk violin players who have followed him. He was one of the most highly regarded musicians produced by the second British folk revival, contributing to some of the most important groups and projects of the 1960s, and he became a much sought-after session musician, which led him throughout his career to work with many of the major figures in folk and folk rock music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/87/Dave_Swarbrick.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-swarbrick/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sam Bush]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sam-bush/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Charles Samuel Bush is an American mandolinist who is considered an originator of progressive bluegrass music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/33/Sam_Bush_%282006%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sam-bush/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Woody Guthrie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/woody-guthrie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Woodrow Wilson Guthrie was an American singer-songwriter, one of the most significant figures in American folk music; his music, including songs, such as 'This Land Is Your Land', has inspired several generations both politically and musically. He wrote hundreds of political, folk, and children's songs, along with ballads and improvised works. His album of songs about the Dust Bowl period, Dust Bowl Ballads, is included on Mojo magazine's list of 100 Records That Changed The World. Many of his recorded songs are archived in the Library of Congress. Songwriters such as Bob Dylan, Phil Ochs, Johnny Cash, Bruce Springsteen, Robert Hunter, Harry Chapin, John Mellencamp, Pete Seeger, Andy Irvine, Joe Strummer, Billy Bragg, Jerry Garcia, Jay Farrar, Bob Weir, Jeff Tweedy, Bob Childers, Sammy Walker, Tom Paxton, AJJ, Brian Fallon, and Sixto Rodríguez have acknowledged Guthrie as a major influence. He frequently performed with the slogan 'This machine kills fascists' displayed on his guitar.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/25/Woody_Guthrie.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/woody-guthrie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Denver]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-denver/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Henry John Deutschendorf Jr., known professionally as John Denver, was an American singer-songwriter, record producer, actor, activist, and humanitarian, whose greatest commercial success was as a solo singer. After traveling and living in numerous locations while growing up in his military family, Denver began his music career with folk music groups during the late 1960s. Starting in the 1970s, he was one of the most popular acoustic artists of the decade and one of its best-selling artists. By 1974, he was one of America's best-selling performers, and AllMusic has described Denver as 'among the most beloved entertainers of his era'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b0/John_Denver_1975.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-denver/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Martie Maguire]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/martie-maguire/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Martha 'Martie' Elenor Maguire is an American musician who is a founding member of both the female alternative country band Dixie Chicks and country bluegrass duo Court Yard Hounds. She won awards in national fiddle championships while still a teenager. Erwin is accomplished on several other instruments, including the mandolin, viola, double bass and guitar. She has written and co-written a number of the band's songs, some of which have become chart-topping hits. She also contributes her skills in vocal harmony and backing vocals, as well as orchestrating string arrangements for the band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/24/Martie_Maguire_in_2010.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/martie-maguire/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Charlie Daniels]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/charlie-daniels/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Charles Edward Daniels is an American singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist known for his contributions to Southern rock, country, and bluegrass music. He is best known for his number-one country hit 'The Devil Went Down to Georgia'. Daniels has been active as a singer and musician since the 1950s. He was inducted into the Cheyenne Frontier Days Hall of Fame in 2002, the Grand Ole Opry in 2008, the Musicians Hall of Fame and Museum in 2009, and the Country Music Hall of Fame in 2016.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/55/CharlieDaniels265-1000.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/charlie-daniels/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Clarence "Gatemouth" Brown]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/clarence-"gatemouth"-brown/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Clarence 'Gatemouth' Brown was an American musician from Louisiana and Texas known for his work as a blues musician, as well as other styles of music. He spent his career fighting purism by synthesizing old blues, country, jazz, Cajun music and R&B styles. His work also encompasses rock and roll, rock music, folk music, electric blues, and Texas blues.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/48/Clarence_%22_Gatemouth_%22_Brown.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/clarence-"gatemouth"-brown/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andrew Bird]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrew-bird/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Andrew Wegman Bird is an American indie rock multi-instrumentalist, singer, and songwriter. Since 1996, he has released 15 studio albums, as well as several live albums and EPs, spanning various genres including swing music, indie rock, and folk music. He is primarily known for his unique style of violin playing, accompanied by loop and effect pedals, whistling, and voice. In the '90s, he sang and played violin in several jazz ensembles, including Squirrel Nut Zippers and Kevin O'Donnell's Quality Six. He went on to start his own swing ensemble, Andrew Bird's Bowl of Fire, which released three albums between 1998 and 2001. Weather Systems (2003) was his first solo album, and a departure from jazz music into indie music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0d/Andrew-Bird.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrew-bird/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>