<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 01:13:47 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Ford]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-ford/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David James Ford is an English singer-songwriter, guitarist and songwriter. He first achieved prominence with the indie rock group Easyworld, who released an independent mini-album, ...Better Ways to Self Destruct and two full-length albums on Jive Records before disbanding in 2004.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/67/David_Ford%2C_Toronto.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-ford/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Axel Rudi Pell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/axel-rudi-pell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Axel Rudi Pell is a German heavy metal guitar player who currently works as a lead guitarist for an unnamed backing band he founded as a solo work. He started off with the band Steeler (1984–88) before leaving to start his solo career in 1989. During this time, he has played with such drummers as Jörg Michael and Mike Terrana, and singers Johnny Gioeli, Jeff Scott Soto, and Rob Rock.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/ca/Axel_Rudi_Pell.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/axel-rudi-pell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kelly Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kelly-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kelly Jones is a Welsh singer-songwriter. He is the lead singer and lead guitarist of the rock band Stereophonics.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fe/Kelly_jones_cardiff_2005.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kelly-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shakira]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shakira Isabel Mebarak Ripoll is a Colombian singer, songwriter, dancer, businesswoman, and philanthropist. Born and raised in Barranquilla, she made her recording debut under Sony Music Colombia at the age of 13. Following the commercial failure of her first two Colombian albums, Magia (1991) and Peligro (1993), she rose to prominence in Spanish-speaking countries with her next albums, Pies Descalzos (1995) and Dónde Están los Ladrones? (1998). Shakira entered the English-language market with her fifth album, Laundry Service (2001). It sold over 13 million copies and spawned the international number-one singles 'Whenever, Wherever' and 'Underneath Your Clothes'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/Shakira_in_Toronto_2018.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Max Cavalera]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/max-cavalera/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Massimiliano Antonio 'Max' Cavalera is a Brazilian singer, guitarist, and songwriter who currently plays in heavy metal bands Soulfly, Cavalera Conspiracy, and Killer Be Killed. In 1984, he co-founded the acclaimed thrash metal band Sepultura with his brother Igor Cavalera and was the band's lead singer and rhythm guitarist until he left in 1996. Cavalera was also involved in a short-lived side project called Nailbomb.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/64/Soulfly-max-2005.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/max-cavalera/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Cosey Fanni Tutti]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/cosey-fanni-tutti/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Cosey Fanni Tutti is an English performance artist, musician, and writer, best known for her time in the avant-garde groups Throbbing Gristle and Chris & Cosey.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/CoseyFanniTutti2009.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/cosey-fanni-tutti/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Willie Nelson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Willie Hugh Nelson is an American musician, actor, and activist. The critical success of the album Shotgun Willie (1973), combined with the critical and commercial success of Red Headed Stranger (1975) and Stardust (1978), made Nelson one of the most recognized artists in country music. He was one of the main figures of outlaw country, a subgenre of country music that developed in the late 1960s as a reaction to the conservative restrictions of the Nashville sound. Nelson has acted in over 30 films, co-authored several books, and has been involved in activism for the use of biofuels and the legalization of marijuana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/WillieNelson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Arjen Anthony Lucassen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/arjen-anthony-lucassen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Arjen Anthony Lucassen is a Dutch singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist musician and record producer best known for his long-running progressive metal/rock opera project Ayreon.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4b/Arjen_Anthony_Lucassen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/arjen-anthony-lucassen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Hackett]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-hackett/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen Richard Hackett is an English musician, songwriter, singer, and producer who gained prominence as the lead guitarist of the progressive rock band Genesis from 1971 to 1977. Hackett contributed to six Genesis studio albums, three live albums, seven singles and one EP before he left to pursue a solo career. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of Genesis in 2010.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c3/Steve_Hackett.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-hackett/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Linda Ronstadt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/linda-ronstadt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Linda Maria Ronstadt is a retired American popular music singer known for singing in a wide range of genres including rock, country, light opera, and Latin. She has earned 10 Grammy Awards, three American Music Awards, two Academy of Country Music awards, an Emmy Award, and an ALMA Award, and many of her albums have been certified gold, platinum or multiplatinum in the United States and internationally. She has also earned nominations for a Tony Award and a Golden Globe award. She was awarded the Latin Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award by The Latin Recording Academy in 2011 and also awarded the Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award by The Recording Academy in 2016. She was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in April 2014. On July 28, 2014, she was awarded the National Medal of Arts and Humanities. In 2019, she will receive a joint star with Dolly Parton and Emmylou Harris on the Hollywood Walk of Fame for their work as the group Trio.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/50/LindaRonstadtPerforming.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/linda-ronstadt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>