<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Megadeth</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Megadeth</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:25:03 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Mustaine]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-mustaine/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Scott Mustaine is an American guitarist, singer, songwriter, actor and author. He is best known as the co-founder, lead vocalist, guitarist and primary songwriter of the American heavy metal band Megadeth, as well as the original lead guitarist of the American band Metallica.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/41/Megadeth_performing_in_San_Antonio%2C_Texas_%2827420120171%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-mustaine/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Broderick]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-broderick/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher Alan 'Chris' Broderick is an American musician, best known as the former guitarist of the American heavy metal band Megadeth. He is also formerly the lead guitarist and keyboardist for Jag Panzer, appearing on four of Jag Panzer's albums The Age of Mastery, Thane to the Throne, Mechanized Warfare and Casting the Stones before moving on to Megadeth, replacing Glen Drover. Before joining Megadeth and while still in Jag Panzer, he was also a touring guitarist for Nevermore between 2001 and 2003 and then again between 2006 and 2007. He is now the lead guitarist for Act of Defiance, which he formed with fellow ex-Megadeth bandmate, Shawn Drover.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7b/Megadeth_%40_Arena_Joondalup_%2812_12_2010%29_%285272639477%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-broderick/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marty Friedman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marty-friedman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Martin Adam 'Marty' Friedman is an American guitarist, known for his tenure as the lead guitarist for heavy metal band Megadeth which spanned nearly the full decade of the 1990s. He is also known for playing alongside Jason Becker in Cacophony until 1989, as well as his 13 solo albums and tours. Friedman has resided in Tokyo, Japan since 2003, where he has appeared on over 700 Japanese television programs such as Rock Fujiyama, Hebimeta-san, Kouhaku uta gassen and Jukebox English. He has released albums with several record labels, including Avex Trax, Universal, EMI, Prosthetic and Shrapnel Records.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/76/Marty_Friedman_13.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marty-friedman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>