<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Flute</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Flute</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 20:55:42 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lowell George]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lowell-george/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/19/Little_Feat_Lowell_George.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lowell-george/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Denny Laine]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/denny-laine/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Denny Laine is an English musician, singer, and songwriter, known as a founder of two major British rock bands: the Moody Blues, with whom he played from 1964 to 1966, and Wings, with whom he played from 1971 to 1981. Laine has worked with a variety of artists and groups over a six decade career, and continues to record and perform as a solo artist. In 2018, Laine was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Moody Blues.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c4/Denny_Laine_-_Wings_-_1976.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/denny-laine/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stephan Micus]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stephan-micus/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stephan Micus is a German musician and composer whose musical style is heavily influenced by his study of traditional instruments and musical techniques from Japan, India, South America, and other countries around the world. With the exception of his album The Music of Stones (1989), he plays all of the instruments on his recordings, combining styles from different countries and using the instruments in unprecedented ways in each of his pieces. He often uses layers of a single instrument to create unusual combinations of sounds. He is one of the only ECM Records artists whose records are not produced by Manfred Eicher. He has mixed instruments from around the world, or used whatever was at hand: stones, ordinary flowerpots tuned with water, and his voice—singing improvised syllables over ten years before others made this approach fashionable.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f1/Stephan_Micus.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stephan-micus/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ian McDonald]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ian-mcdonald/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ian McDonald is an English multi-instrumental musician, best known as a founding member of progressive rock band King Crimson in 1969, and of Foreigner in 1976. He is well regarded as a rock session musician, predominantly as a saxophonist. McDonald also plays keyboards, flute, vibraphone and guitar.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8c/Ian_McDonald_%282009%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ian-mcdonald/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nina Nesbitt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nina-nesbitt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nina Lindberg Nesbitt is a Scottish singer and songwriter. She has two top 40 singles, and is known for her single 'Stay Out', which peaked at 21 on the UK Singles Chart in April 2013.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Nina_Nesbitt_2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nina-nesbitt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amandine Bourgeois]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amandine-bourgeois/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amandine Bourgeois is a French singer. She was the winner of the sixth edition of the French version of the Pop Idol series Nouvelle Star in 2008. On 26 July 2014, Bourgeois participated in the television game show Fort Boyard.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/be/Amandine_Bourgeois%2C_ESC2013_press_conference_05.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amandine-bourgeois/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Duplantier]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-duplantier/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Andrew Duplantier is a French-American musician and record producer, best known as the rhythm guitarist and vocalist of metal band Gojira, which he formed with his younger brother Mario. He is also the former bassist of Cavalera Conspiracy, to which he was invited by Max Cavalera.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e0/W0840-Hellfest2013_Gojira_JosephDuplantier_71163.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-duplantier/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alanis Morissette]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alanis Nadine Morissette is a Canadian-American singer, songwriter, musician, and actress. Known for her emotive mezzo-soprano voice, Morissette began her career in Canada in the early 1990s with two mildly successful dance-pop albums. Afterward, as part of a recording deal, she moved to Holmby Hills, Los Angeles. In 1995, she released Jagged Little Pill, a more rock-oriented album which sold more than 33 million copies globally and is her most critically acclaimed work to date. This was made into a rock musical of the same name in 2017, which earned 15 Tony Award nominations including Best Musical. Her more experimental follow-up album, electronic-infused Supposed Former Infatuation Junkie, was released in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Alanis_Morissette_5-19-2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mick Ronson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mick-ronson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Ronson was an English guitarist, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, arranger, and producer. He achieved critical and commercial success working with David Bowie as one of the Spiders from Mars. He was a session musician who recorded five studio albums with Bowie followed by four with Ian Hunter, and also worked as a sideman in touring bands with Van Morrison and Bob Dylan.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6f/Mick_Ronson_1981_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mick-ronson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[India.Arie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/india-arie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>India Arie Simpson, also known as India.Arie, is an American singer and songwriter. She has sold over 3.3 million records in the US and 10 million worldwide. She has won four Grammy Awards from her 23 nominations, including Best R&B Album.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c5/India.Arie_in_2004_by_Chris_Hakkens.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/india-arie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>