<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Flute</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Flute</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:25:03 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andrea Bocelli]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrea-bocelli/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Andrea Bocelli is an Italian opera singer, songwriter, and record producer. Celine Dion has said that 'if God would have a singing voice, he must sound a lot like Andrea Bocelli,' and David Foster, a record producer, often describes Bocelli's voice as the most beautiful in the world.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/15/AndreaBocelliMar10.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrea-bocelli/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alanis Morissette]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alanis Nadine Morissette is a Canadian-American singer, songwriter, record producer, and actress. Known for her emotive mezzo-soprano voice, Morissette began her career in Canada in the early 1990s with two mildly successful dance-pop albums. Afterwards, as part of a recording deal, she moved to Holmby Hills, Los Angeles and in 1995 released Jagged Little Pill, a more rock-oriented album which sold more than 33 million copies globally and is her most critically acclaimed work. Her follow-up album, Supposed Former Infatuation Junkie, was released in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Alanis_Morissette_5-19-2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lowell George]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lowell-george/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lowell Thomas George was an American singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, and record producer, who was the primary guitarist, vocalist, and songwriter for the rock band Little Feat.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/19/Little_Feat_Lowell_George.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lowell-george/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Duplantier]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-duplantier/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Andrew Duplantier is a French musician best known as the rhythm guitarist and vocalist of metal band Gojira. He is also the former bassist of Cavalera Conspiracy, to which he was invited by Max Cavalera.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e0/W0840-Hellfest2013_Gojira_JosephDuplantier_71163.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-duplantier/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amandine Bourgeois]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amandine-bourgeois/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amandine Bourgeois is a French singer. She was the winner of the sixth edition of the French version of the Pop Idol series Nouvelle Star in 2008. On 26 July 2014, Bourgeois participated in the television game show Fort Boyard.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/be/Amandine_Bourgeois%2C_ESC2013_press_conference_05.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amandine-bourgeois/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lewis Brian Hopkins Jones was an English musician, best known as the founder and original leader of the Rolling Stones. Initially a slide guitarist, Jones would go on to play a wide variety of instruments on Rolling Stones recordings and in concerts, such as rhythm and lead guitar, sitar, dulcimer, various keyboard instruments such as piano and mellotron, marimba, wind instruments such as harmonica, recorder, saxophone, as well as drums, vocals and numerous others.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6b/Brian_Jones%2C_Statesboro%2C_Georgia%2C_May_4%2C_1965_%28377872218%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ian Anderson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ian-anderson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ian Scott Anderson is a Scottish-born musician, singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist best known for his work as the lead vocalist, flautist and acoustic guitarist of British rock band Jethro Tull. Anderson plays several other musical instruments, including keyboards, bass guitar, bouzouki, balalaika, saxophone, harmonica, and a variety of whistles. His solo work began with the 1983 album Walk into Light, and since then he has released another five works, including the sequel to the Jethro Tull album Thick as a Brick (1972) in 2012, entitled Thick as a Brick 2.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/24/Ian_Anderson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ian-anderson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stephan Micus]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stephan-micus/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stephan Micus is a German classical and world musician and composer whose musical style is heavily influenced by his study of traditional instruments and musical techniques from Japan, India, South America, and other countries around the world. With the exception of his album The Music of Stones (1989), he plays all of the instruments on his recordings, combining styles from different countries and using the instruments in unprecedented ways in each of his pieces. He often uses layers of a single instrument to create unusual combinations of sounds. He is one of the only ECM Records artists whose records are not produced by Manfred Eicher. He has mixed instruments from around the world, or used whatever was at hand: stones, ordinary flowerpots tuned with water, and his voice—singing improvised syllables over ten years before others made this approach fashionable.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f1/Stephan_Micus.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stephan-micus/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nina Nesbitt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nina-nesbitt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nina Lindberg Nesbitt is a Scottish singer and songwriter. She has two top 40 singles, and is known for her single 'Stay Out', which peaked at 21 on the UK Singles Chart in April 2013.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Nina_Nesbitt_2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nina-nesbitt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[India.Arie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/india-arie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>India Arie Simpson, also known as India.Arie, is an American singer and songwriter. She has sold over 3.3 million records in the US and 10 million worldwide. She has won four Grammy Awards from her 21 nominations, including Best R&B Album.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c5/India.Arie_in_2004_by_Chris_Hakkens.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/india-arie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>