<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Cello</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Cello</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:49:34 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brendon Urie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brendon-urie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brendon Boyd Urie is an American singer, songwriter, and musician, best known as the lead vocalist of Panic! at the Disco, of which he is the only member remaining.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fb/Panic_at_the_Disco_Im_Park_2016_%2811_von_11%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brendon-urie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Trent Reznor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Trent Reznor is an American singer, songwriter, musician, record producer, and film score composer. He is the founder, lead vocalist, and principal songwriter of the industrial rock band Nine Inch Nails, which he founded in 1988 and of which he was the sole official member until adding long-time collaborator Atticus Ross as a permanent member in 2016. His first release under the Nine Inch Nails name, the 1989 album Pretty Hate Machine, was a commercial and critical success. He has since released nine Nine Inch Nails studio albums. He left Interscope Records in 2007 and was an independent recording artist until signing with Columbia Records in 2012.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d5/Trent_Reznor-FEB2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roy Wood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-wood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roy Wood is an English singer-songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. He was particularly successful in the 1960s and 1970s as member and co-founder of The Move, Electric Light Orchestra and Wizzard. As a songwriter, he contributed a number of hits to the repertoire of these bands. Collectively, hit records by The Move, Electric Light Orchestra, Wizzard, and Wood's own solo singles demonstrated an impressive chart run for an individual, both as composer and performer. Altogether he had more than 20 singles in the UK Singles Chart under various guises, including three UK No. 1 hits.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0f/Roy_Wood_TopPop.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-wood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lewis Brian Hopkins Jones was an English musician, best known as the founder and original leader of the Rolling Stones. Initially a slide guitarist, Jones would go on to play a wide variety of instruments on Rolling Stones recordings and in concerts, such as rhythm and lead guitar, sitar, dulcimer, various keyboard instruments such as piano and mellotron, marimba, wind instruments such as harmonica, recorder, saxophone, as well as drums, vocals and numerous others.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6b/Brian_Jones%2C_Statesboro%2C_Georgia%2C_May_4%2C_1965_%28377872218%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lights]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lights/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lights Poxleitner-Bokan, known mononymously as Lights, is a Canadian musician, singer, songwriter, author, and illustrator. She is known for her gold-certified albums The Listening and Siberia as well as singles 'Drive My Soul', 'February Air', 'Ice', 'Second Go', 'Toes', and 'Up We Go'. She released her fourth studio album, Skin & Earth, in 2017 accompanied by a graphic novel of the same name.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/LIGHTS_IMG_6799_%2815999651243%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lights/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul McCartney]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir James Paul McCartney is an English singer, songwriter, musician, composer, and record and film producer who gained worldwide fame as co-lead vocalist and bassist for the Beatles. His songwriting partnership with John Lennon remains the most successful in history. After the group disbanded in 1970, he pursued a successful solo career and formed the band Wings with his first wife, Linda, and Denny Laine.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d6/Paul_McCartney_in_October_2018.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vladimir Kuzmin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vladimir-kuzmin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vladimir Borisovich Kuzmin is a Russian rock singer, guitarist, and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b9/%D0%9A%D1%83%D0%B7%D1%8C%D0%BC%D0%B8%D0%BD-%D0%9A%D0%B0%D0%BC%D0%B5%D0%BD%D1%81%D0%BA_21-10-12_cr.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vladimir-kuzmin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>