<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Experimental Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Experimental Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 01:13:48 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Serj Tankian]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Serj Tankian is an Armenian-American musician, singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, poet and political activist. He is best known as the lead vocalist, songwriter, keyboardist, and occasional live rhythm guitarist of the band System of a Down, formed in 1994.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/69/Serj_Tankian_Spirit_of_Burgas_Bulgaria_2010_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:32 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bill Nelson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-nelson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Nelson is an English singer, guitarist, songwriter, producer, painter, video artist, writer and experimental musician. He rose to prominence as the chief songwriter, vocalist and guitarist of the rock group Be-Bop Deluxe, which he formed in 1972. Nelson has been described as 'one of the most underrated guitarists of the seventies art rock movement'. In 2015, he was recognised with the Visionary award at the Progressive Music Awards.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c9/Be_Bop_Deluxe2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-nelson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ilya Lagutenko]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ilya-lagutenko/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ilya Igorevich Lagutenko is the founder and lead singer of MTV Award-winning band Mumiy Troll.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e8/%D0%98%D0%BB%D1%8C%D1%8F_%D0%9B%D0%B0%D0%B3%D1%83%D1%82%D0%B5%D0%BD%D0%BA%D0%BE_2016_2_%281%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ilya-lagutenko/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Scott Walker]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-walker-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Scott Walker was an American-born British singer-songwriter, composer and record producer. Walker was known for his distinctive baritone voice and an unorthodox career path which took him from 1960s teen pop icon to 21st-century avant-garde musician. Walker's success was largely in the United Kingdom, where his first three solo albums reached the top ten. He lived in the UK from 1965 and became a UK citizen in 1970.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bf/Fenklup1968ScottWalker.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/scott-walker-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Lennon]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-lennon/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Winston Ono Lennon was an English singer, songwriter and peace activist who gained worldwide fame as the founder, co-lead vocalist, and rhythm guitarist of the Beatles. His songwriting partnership with Paul McCartney remains the most successful in history. In 1969, he started the Plastic Ono Band with his second wife, Yoko Ono. After the Beatles disbanded in 1970, Lennon continued as a solo artist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/51/JohnLennonpeace.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-lennon/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Glenn Branca]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glenn-branca/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Glenn Branca was an American avant-garde composer and guitarist known for his use of volume, alternative guitar tunings, repetition, droning, and the harmonic series. Branca received a 2009 Foundation for Contemporary Arts Grants to Artists Award.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8c/Glenn_Branca.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/glenn-branca/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:31 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Buckethead]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Patrick Carroll, known professionally as Buckethead, is an American multi-instrumental musician who has received critical acclaim for his innovative electric guitar playing. His music spans many genres, including progressive metal, funk, blues, bluegrass, ambient, and avant-garde music. He performs primarily as a solo artist, though he has collaborated extensively with a wide variety of high-profile artists such as Bill Laswell, Bootsy Collins, Bernie Worrell, Iggy Pop, Les Claypool, Serj Tankian, Bill Moseley, Mike Patton, Viggo Mortensen, That 1 Guy, Bassnectar, and was a member of Guns N' Roses from 2000 to 2004. He has released 306 studio albums, four special releases, and one EP. He has also performed on more than 50 other albums by other artists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Neumos_seattle_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Frank Zappa]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/frank-zappa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Frank Vincent Zappa was an American multi-instrumentalist musician, composer, and bandleader. His work is characterized by nonconformity, free-form improvisation, sound experiments, musical virtuosity, and satire of American culture. In a career spanning more than 30 years, Zappa composed rock, pop, jazz, jazz fusion, orchestral and musique concrète works, and produced almost all of the 60-plus albums that he released with his band the Mothers of Invention and as a solo artist. Zappa also directed feature-length films and music videos, and designed album covers. He is considered one of the most innovative and stylistically diverse rock musicians of his era.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c4/Zappa_16011977_01_300.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/frank-zappa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shannon Wright]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shannon-wright/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shannon Wright is an American singer-songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e0/Shannon_Wright-5.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shannon-wright/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 23:01:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>