<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Psychedelic Pop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Psychedelic Pop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:01:35 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kevin Parker]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kevin-parker/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kevin Richard Parker is an Australian singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist and record producer, best known for his musical project Tame Impala, for which he writes, records, and produces the music. At the ARIA Music Awards of 2015 he won two awards, Engineer of the Year and Producer of the Year, for his work on Tame Impala's album Currents (2015).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/08/Tame_Impala_Performing_in_NYC_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kevin-parker/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Bowie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-bowie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Robert Jones, known professionally as David Bowie, was an English singer-songwriter and actor. He was a leading figure in the music industry and is considered one of the most influential musicians of the 20th century, acclaimed by critics and musicians, particularly for his innovative work during the 1970s. His career was marked by reinvention and visual presentation, with his music and stagecraft having a significant impact on popular music. During his lifetime, his record sales, estimated at over 100 million records worldwide, made him one of the world's best-selling music artists. In the UK, he was awarded ten platinum album certifications, eleven gold and eight silver, and released eleven number-one albums. In the US, he received five platinum and nine gold certifications. He was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1996.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e8/David-Bowie_Chicago_2002-08-08_photoby_Adam-Bielawski-cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-bowie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Donovan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/donovan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Donovan is a Scottish singer, songwriter and guitarist. He developed an eclectic and distinctive style that blended folk, jazz, pop, psychedelia, and world music. He has lived in Scotland, Hertfordshire (England), London, California, and since at least 2008 in County Cork, Ireland, with his family. Emerging from the British folk scene, Donovan reached fame in the United Kingdom in early 1965 with live performances on the pop TV series Ready Steady Go!.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/68/Donovan_Washington_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/donovan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Syd Barrett]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/syd-barrett/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roger Keith 'Syd' Barrett was an English singer, songwriter, and musician who co-founded the rock band Pink Floyd in 1965. Characterised for his English-accented singing and free-form writing style, Barrett named the group and was their original lead singer, guitarist and principal songwriter. His innovative use of guitar techniques, such as dissonance, distortion and feedback, proved influential to many musicians.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Syd_barrett.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/syd-barrett/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>