<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Drum Kit</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Drum Kit</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:04:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Winehouse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Jade Winehouse was an English singer and songwriter. She was known for her deep, expressive contralto vocals and her eclectic mix of musical genres, including soul rhythm and blues, and jazz. Winehouse's debut album, Frank (2003), was a critical success in the UK and was nominated for the Mercury Prize. Her follow-up album, Back to Black (2006), led to five 2008 Grammy Awards, tying the then record for the most wins by a female artist in a single night, and made her the first British woman to win five Grammys, including three of the General Field 'Big Four' Grammy Awards: Best New Artist, Record of the Year and Song of the Year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Amy_Winehouse_f4962007_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mark Ronson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-ronson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Mark Daniel Ronson is a British–American musician, DJ, songwriter and record producer. Ronson is best known for his collaborations with artists such as Amy Winehouse, Lady Gaga, Adele, Lily Allen, Miley Cyrus, Queens of the Stone Age, and Bruno Mars. He has received seven Grammy Awards, including Producer of the Year for Winehouse's album Back to Black and two for Record of the Year singles 'Rehab' and 'Uptown Funk'. He received an Academy Award, a Golden Globe Award and a Grammy Award for co-writing the song 'Shallow' for the film A Star is Born (2018).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/ce/Mark_Ronson_and_Jennifer_Su%2C_2011_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-ronson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Shinoda]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Kenji Shinoda is an American musician, singer, songwriter, rapper, record producer, and graphic designer. He co-founded Linkin Park in 1996 and is the band's rhythm guitarist, primary songwriter, keyboardist, producer, and co-lead vocalist. Shinoda later created a hip-hop-driven side project, Fort Minor, in 2004. He has also served as a producer for tracks and albums by Lupe Fiasco, Styles of Beyond and the X-Ecutioners.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/Mike_Shinoda_4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ringo Starr]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ringo-starr/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir Richard Starkey, known professionally as Ringo Starr, is an English musician, singer, songwriter and actor who gained worldwide fame as the drummer for the Beatles. He occasionally sang lead vocals with the group, usually for one song on each album, including 'With a Little Help from My Friends', 'Yellow Submarine', 'Good Night', 'Boys', and their cover of 'Act Naturally'. He also wrote and sang the Beatles' songs 'Don't Pass Me By' and 'Octopus's Garden', and is credited as a co-writer of others, including 'What Goes On'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Ringo_Starr_and_all_his_band_%288470866906%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ringo-starr/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hunter Hayes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hunter-hayes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Hunter Easton Hayes is an American country music singer, songwriter, and multi-instrumentalist. He is proficient at more than 30 instruments and is signed to Warner Music Nashville.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fd/Hunter_Hayes.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hunter-hayes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anssi Kela]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anssi-kela/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Anssi Kela is a Finnish singer-songwriter multi-instrumentalist who has published six albums. During his career, Kela has sold over 230,000 records in Finland. He received four Emma awards in 2002.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/63/Anssi_Kela.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anssi-kela/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Rocket Summer]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/the-rocket-summer/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>The Rocket Summer is the solo-project of Bryce Avary who is based in Dallas–Fort Worth, Texas. Avary is a multi-instrumentalist, singer-songwriter, and producer. He writes and produces every song on his records, and plays every instrument on them.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d1/Bryce_The_Rocket_Summer.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/the-rocket-summer/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Phil Collins]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/phil-collins/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Philip David Charles Collins is an English drummer, singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, and actor. He was the drummer and later became singer of the rock band Genesis, and is also a solo artist. Between 1982 and 1989, Collins scored three UK and seven US number-one singles in his solo career. When his work with Genesis, his work with other artists, as well as his solo career is totalled, he had more US Top 40 singles than any other artist during the 1980s. His most successful singles from the period include 'In the Air Tonight', 'Against All Odds ', 'One More Night', 'Sussudio', 'Two Hearts' and 'Another Day in Paradise'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1a/Phil_Collins_Duesseldorf.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/phil-collins/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Wilson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-wilson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Douglas Wilson is an American musician, singer, songwriter, and record producer who co-founded the Beach Boys. After signing with Capitol Records in 1962, Wilson wrote or co-wrote more than two dozen Top 40 hits for the group. In addition to his unorthodox approaches to pop composition and mastery of recording techniques, Wilson is known for his lifelong struggles with mental illness. He is often referred to as a genius and is widely acknowledged as one of the most innovative and significant songwriters of the late 20th century.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ad/Brian_Wilson_Jan_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-wilson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>