<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Drum Kit</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Drum Kit</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:08:37 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Winehouse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Jade Winehouse was an English singer and songwriter. She was known for her deep, expressive contralto vocals and her eclectic mix of musical genres, including soul rhythm and blues, and jazz. Winehouse's debut album, Frank (2003), was a critical success in the UK and was nominated for the Mercury Prize. Her follow-up album, Back to Black (2006), led to five 2008 Grammy Awards, tying the then record for the most wins by a female artist in a single night, and made her the first British woman to win five Grammys, including three of the General Field 'Big Four' Grammy Awards: Best New Artist, Record of the Year and Song of the Year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Amy_Winehouse_f4962007_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ben Moody]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ben-moody/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Benjamin Robert 'Ben' Moody is an American musician, singer, songwriter, record producer, and actor. He is best known as co-founder, lead guitarist, and co-songwriter of rock band Evanescence from its inception in 1995 to his departure in October 2003. Since leaving Evanescence, Moody has collaborated with an array of performers vocally, instrumentally, and as a writer. He is currently a member of The Halo Method and We Are the Fallen.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Evanescence_2003_barcelona_ben_moody.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ben-moody/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kevin Parker]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kevin-parker/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kevin Richard Parker is an Australian singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist and record producer, best known for his musical project Tame Impala, for which he writes, records, and produces the music. At the ARIA Music Awards of 2015 he won two awards, Engineer of the Year and Producer of the Year, for his work on Tame Impala's album Currents (2015).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/08/Tame_Impala_Performing_in_NYC_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kevin-parker/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mark Ronson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-ronson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Mark Daniel Ronson is a British–American musician, DJ, songwriter and record producer. Ronson is best known for his collaborations with artists such as Amy Winehouse, Lady Gaga, Adele, Lily Allen, Miley Cyrus, Queens of the Stone Age, and Bruno Mars. He has received seven Grammy Awards, including Producer of the Year for Winehouse's album Back to Black and two for Record of the Year singles 'Rehab' and 'Uptown Funk'. He received an Academy Award, a Golden Globe Award and a Grammy Award for co-writing the song 'Shallow' for the film A Star is Born (2018).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/ce/Mark_Ronson_and_Jennifer_Su%2C_2011_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-ronson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shannon Leto]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shannon-leto/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shannon Leto is an American musician and songwriter best known as the drummer of rock band Thirty Seconds to Mars. He co-founded the group in 1998 in Los Angeles, California, with his younger brother Jared. Their debut album, 30 Seconds to Mars (2002), was released to positive reviews but only to limited success. The band achieved worldwide fame with the release of their second album A Beautiful Lie (2005). Their following releases, This Is War (2009) and Love, Lust, Faith and Dreams (2013), received further critical and commercial success. As of September 2014, the band has sold over 15 million albums worldwide.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d0/Shannon_Leto_-_2009_Buzz_Bake_Sale.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shannon-leto/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Shinoda]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Kenji Shinoda is an American musician, singer, songwriter, rapper, record producer, and graphic designer. He co-founded Linkin Park in 1996 and is the band's rhythm guitarist, primary songwriter, keyboardist, producer, and co-lead vocalist. Shinoda later created a hip-hop-driven side project, Fort Minor, in 2004. He has also served as a producer for tracks and albums by Lupe Fiasco, Styles of Beyond and the X-Ecutioners.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/Mike_Shinoda_4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ross Lynch]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ross-lynch/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ross Shor Lynch is an American singer, songwriter, musician and actor. He was the lead vocalist of the pop rock band R5 and one half of the band The Driver Era, with his brother, Rocky Lynch. As an actor, he is known for his debut role as Austin Moon on the Disney Channel original series Austin & Ally, and for his role as Brady in the Teen Beach Movie series.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c0/Ross_Lynch_2013.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ross-lynch/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul Stanley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-stanley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul Stanley is an American musician, singer, songwriter, and painter, best known for being the rhythm guitarist and co-lead vocalist of the rock band Kiss. He is the writer or co-writer of many of the band's highest-charting hits. Stanley established The Starchild character for his Kiss persona.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f7/W0868-Hellfest2013_Kiss_PaulStanley_69963.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-stanley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ringo Starr]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ringo-starr/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir Richard Starkey, known professionally as Ringo Starr, is an English musician, singer, songwriter and actor who gained worldwide fame as the drummer for the Beatles. He occasionally sang lead vocals with the group, usually for one song on each album, including 'With a Little Help from My Friends', 'Yellow Submarine', 'Good Night', 'Boys', and their cover of 'Act Naturally'. He also wrote and sang the Beatles' songs 'Don't Pass Me By' and 'Octopus's Garden', and is credited as a co-writer of others, including 'What Goes On'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Ringo_Starr_and_all_his_band_%288470866906%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ringo-starr/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>