<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Drum Kit</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Drum Kit</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:08:39 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Winehouse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Jade Winehouse was an English singer and songwriter. She was known for her deep, expressive contralto vocals and her eclectic mix of musical genres, including soul, rhythm and blues and jazz.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Amy_Winehouse_f4962007_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:49 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ben Moody]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ben-moody/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Evanescence_2003_barcelona_ben_moody.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ben-moody/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mark Ronson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-ronson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Mark Daniel Ronson is a British-American musician, DJ, songwriter, and record producer. He is best known for his collaborations with artists such as Amy Winehouse, Adele, Lady Gaga, Lily Allen, Robbie Williams, Miley Cyrus, Queens of the Stone Age, and Bruno Mars. He has received seven Grammy Awards, including Producer of the Year for Winehouse's album Back to Black and two for Record of the Year singles 'Rehab' and 'Uptown Funk'. He received an Academy Award, a Golden Globe Award and a Grammy Award for co-writing the song 'Shallow' for the film A Star is Born (2018).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/ce/Mark_Ronson_and_Jennifer_Su%2C_2011_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-ronson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American singer, songwriter, and musician best known as the lead vocalist and rhythm guitarist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. He also had a solo career and contributed to soundtracks. Cornell was also the founder and frontman of Temple of the Dog, a one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ab/Chris_Cornell.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Madonna]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/madonna/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Madonna Louise Ciccone is an American singer-songwriter and actress. Referred to as the 'Queen of Pop', she is regarded as one of the most influential figures in popular culture. Madonna is noted for her continual reinvention and versatility in music production, songwriting, and visual presentation. Additionally she is recognized for pushing the boundaries of artistic expression in mainstream music while remaining completely in charge of every aspect of her career. Her works, which incorporate social, political, sexual, and religious themes, have generated both critical acclaim and controversy. Madonna is often cited as an influence by other artists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Madonna_Rebel_Heart_Tour_2015_-_Stockholm_%2823051472299%29_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/madonna/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Gilmour]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-gilmour/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Jon Gilmour is an English musician who was a member of rock band Pink Floyd. He joined as guitarist and co-lead vocalist in 1968 shortly before the departure of founder member Syd Barrett. Pink Floyd achieved international success with the concept albums The Dark Side of the Moon (1973), Wish You Were Here (1975), Animals (1977), and The Wall (1979). By the early 1980s, they had become one of the highest-selling and most acclaimed acts in music history; by 2012, they had sold more than 250 million records worldwide, including 75 million in the United States. Following the departure of Roger Waters in 1985, Pink Floyd continued under Gilmour's leadership and released three more studio albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/19/David_Gilmour_in_Munich_July_2006-ed-.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-gilmour/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kevin Parker]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kevin-parker/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kevin Richard Parker is an Australian singer, songwriter, musician, and record producer, best known for his musical project Tame Impala, for which he writes, performs, records, and produces the music. Parker has released four Tame Impala albums: Innerspeaker (2010), Lonerism (2012), Currents (2015), and The Slow Rush (2020). He was won 12 ARIA Music Awards and a Brit Award, and has received four Grammy Award nominations.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/08/Tame_Impala_Performing_in_NYC_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kevin-parker/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Parish]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-parish/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5d/John_Parish.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-parish/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul Stanley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-stanley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul Stanley is an American singer, songwriter and painter, best known for being the co-founder, rhythm guitarist and co-lead vocalist of the rock band Kiss. He is the writer or co-writer of many of the band's highest-charting hits. Stanley established The Starchild character for his Kiss persona and is known for his distinctive, wide-ranging voice.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f7/W0868-Hellfest2013_Kiss_PaulStanley_69963.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-stanley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Charlie Simpson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/charlie-simpson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Charles Robert Simpson is an English singer, songwriter and musician. He is the youngest member of multi-BRIT Award-winning band Busted and he is also the lead vocalist and the rhythm guitarist in the British post-hardcore band Fightstar. AllMusic has noted that Simpson is 'perhaps the only pop star to make the convincing transition from fresh-faced boy bander to authentic hard rock frontman'. Simpson is a multi-instrumentalist, playing guitar, keyboard, piano and drums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1b/CSimspon270409.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/charlie-simpson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:45:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>