<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Queens Of The Stone Age</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Queens Of The Stone Age</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 13:58:34 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nick Oliveri]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nick-oliveri/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nick Steven Oliveri is an American multi-instrumentalist, singer and songwriter from Los Angeles, California. He is perhaps best known as a former member of Kyuss and later Queens of the Stone Age from 1998 to 2004. Oliveri is also a solo artist and frequent contributor to his friends' albums and tours, including Winnebago Deal, Mark Lanegan Band, Masters of Reality, Turbonegro and Moistboyz, among many others. He is currently the frontman of his project, Mondo Generator, a punk and metal hybrid that he formed in 1997. He has also worked periodically with the Dwarves since 1993.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/42/Nick_Oliveri_with_cigarette_2009-01-07.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nick-oliveri/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Josh Homme]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/josh-homme/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joshua Michael Homme is an American singer, musician, songwriter, and record producer. He is best known as the founder, primary songwriter, and only continuous member of the rock band Queens of the Stone Age, which he formed in 1996 and in which he sings lead vocals and plays guitar, as well as occasionally playing bass and drums. He also co-founded Eagles of Death Metal in 1998, playing drums and bass for their studio recordings and occasionally performing live with them.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/79/Josh_Homme_mg_5648.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/josh-homme/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>