<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Sonic Youth</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Sonic Youth</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 13:58:34 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kim Gordon]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kim-gordon/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kim Althea Gordon is an American musician, singer and songwriter, best known as the bassist, guitarist, and vocalist of alternative rock band Sonic Youth. Born in Rochester, New York, she was raised in Los Angeles, California, where her father was a professor at the University of California, Los Angeles. After graduating from Los Angeles's Otis College of Art and Design, she moved to New York City to begin an art career. There, she formed Sonic Youth with Thurston Moore in 1981. She and Moore married in 1984, and the band released a total of six albums on independent labels before the end of the 1980s. They would subsequently release nine studio albums on the major label DGC Records, beginning with Goo in 1990. Gordon was also a founding member of the musical project Free Kitten, which she formed with Julia Cafritz in 1993.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9d/Sonic_Youth_2009_%283709306067%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kim-gordon/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Thurston Moore]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/thurston-moore/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thurston Joseph Moore is an American musician best known as a member of Sonic Youth. He has also participated in many solo and group collaborations outside Sonic Youth, as well as running the Ecstatic Peace! record label. Moore was ranked 34th in Rolling Stone's 2004 edition of the '100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time.' In May 2012, Spin published a staff-selected list of the top 100 rock guitarists, and ranked Moore and his Sonic Youth bandmate Lee Ranaldo together at number 1.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f9/Thurston_Moore_at_the_Brooklyn_Book_Festival.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/thurston-moore/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:36 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>