<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Pink Floyd</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Pink Floyd</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:03:07 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roger Waters]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roger-waters/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>George Roger Waters is an English songwriter, singer, bassist, and composer. In 1965, he co-founded the progressive rock band Pink Floyd. Waters initially served solely as the bassist, but following the departure of singer-songwriter Syd Barrett in 1968, he also became their lyricist, co-lead vocalist, and conceptual leader.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/03/Roger_Waters%2C_May_18_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roger-waters/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Gilmour]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-gilmour/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Jon Gilmour is an English guitarist, singer and songwriter who was a member of the progressive rock band Pink Floyd. He joined the group as guitarist and co-lead vocalist in 1968 shortly before the departure of founding member Syd Barrett. Pink Floyd achieved international success with the concept albums The Dark Side of the Moon, Wish You Were Here, Animals, and The Wall. By the early 1980s, they had become one of the best-selling and most acclaimed acts in music history; by 2012, the band had sold more than 250 million records worldwide, including 75 million units sold in the United States. Following the departure of Roger Waters in 1985, Gilmour assumed leadership of Pink Floyd, and released three more studio albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/19/David_Gilmour_in_Munich_July_2006-ed-.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-gilmour/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Syd Barrett]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/syd-barrett/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roger Keith 'Syd' Barrett was an English singer, songwriter, and musician who co-founded the rock band Pink Floyd in 1965. Characterised for his English-accented singing and free-form writing style, Barrett named the group and was their original lead singer, guitarist and principal songwriter. His innovative use of guitar techniques, such as dissonance, distortion and feedback, proved influential to many musicians.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Syd_barrett.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/syd-barrett/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>