<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Pink Floyd</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Pink Floyd</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 22:24:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roger Waters]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roger-waters/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>George Roger Waters is an English songwriter, singer, bassist, and composer. In 1965, he co-founded the progressive rock band Pink Floyd. Waters initially served solely as the bassist, but following the departure of singer-songwriter Syd Barrett in 1968, he also became their lyricist, co-lead vocalist, and conceptual leader.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/03/Roger_Waters%2C_May_18_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roger-waters/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Syd Barrett]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/syd-barrett/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roger Keith 'Syd' Barrett was an English singer, songwriter, musician and painter who co-founded the rock band Pink Floyd in 1965. Barrett was their original frontman and primary songwriter, becoming known for his whimsical take on psychedelia, English-accented singing, literary influences, and stream-of-consciousness writing style. As a guitarist, he was influential for his free-form playing and for employing dissonance, distortion, echo, feedback, and other studio effects.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Syd_barrett.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/syd-barrett/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Gilmour]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-gilmour/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Jon Gilmour is an English songwriter, guitarist, and singer who was a member of rock band Pink Floyd. He joined as guitarist and co-lead vocalist in 1968 shortly before the departure of founder member Syd Barrett. Pink Floyd achieved international success with the concept albums The Dark Side of the Moon (1973), Wish You Were Here (1975), Animals (1977), and The Wall (1979). By the early 1980s, they had become one of the highest-selling and most acclaimed acts in music history; by 2012, they had sold more than 250 million records worldwide, including 75 million in the United States. Following the departure of Roger Waters in 1985, Pink Floyd continued under Gilmour's leadership and released three more studio albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/19/David_Gilmour_in_Munich_July_2006-ed-.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-gilmour/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>