<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Electric Bass Guitar</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Electric Bass Guitar</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 21:49:54 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mariusz Duda]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mariusz-duda/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Mariusz Duda is a Polish musician and composer best known as the bassist and vocalist in the band Riverside.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/Mariusz_Duda_%28Riverside%292.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mariusz-duda/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pete Quaife]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-quaife/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Peter Alexander Greenlaw Quaife was an English musician, artist and author. He was a founding member and the original bass guitarist for the Kinks, from 1963 until 1969. He also sang backing vocals on some of their records.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8e/Kinks_helmfrid-sofa3.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pete-quaife/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Buckethead]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Patrick Carroll, known professionally as Buckethead, is an American musician, songwriter, and multi-instrumentalist. He received critical acclaim for his innovative electric guitar playing. His music spans genres, including progressive metal, funk, blues, bluegrass, ambient, and avant-garde music. He performs primarily as a solo artist, although he collaborated with a wide variety of artists such as Bill Laswell, Bootsy Collins, Bernie Worrell, Iggy Pop, Les Claypool, Serj Tankian, Bill Moseley, Mike Patton, Viggo Mortensen, That 1 Guy, Bassnectar, and Skating Polly. He was also a member of Guns N' Roses from 2000 to 2004. He has 315 studio albums, four special releases, and one EP. He performed on more than fifty albums by other artists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Neumos_seattle_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robert Hunter]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robert-hunter-(lyricist)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert C. Christie Hunter was an American lyricist, singer-songwriter, translator, and poet, best known for his work with the Grateful Dead. Born near San Luis Obispo, California, Hunter spent some time in his childhood in foster homes, as a result of his father's abandoning his family, and took refuge in reading and writing. He attended the University of Connecticut for a year before returning to Palo Alto, where he became friends with Jerry Garcia. Garcia and Hunter began a collaboration that lasted through the remainder of Garcia's life.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0a/Robert_Hunter_Town_Hall_2013-10-10.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robert-hunter-(lyricist)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marcus Miller]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marcus-miller/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Henry Marcus Miller Jr. is an American film composer, jazz composer, record producer, arranger, and multi-instrumentalist, best known as a bassist. He has worked with trumpeter Miles Davis, pianist Herbie Hancock, singer Luther Vandross, and saxophonist David Sanborn, among others.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8f/Marcus_Miller_-_Leverkusener_Jazztage_2017-7051.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marcus-miller/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>