<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Soul Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Soul Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 13:01:12 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Richie Havens]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richie-havens/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Pierce Havens was an American singer-songwriter and guitarist. His music encompassed elements of folk, soul, and rhythm and blues. He had an intense and rhythmic guitar style, and played soulful covers of pop and folk songs. He was the opening act at Woodstock.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2c/Richie_Havens_1972_Hamburg.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richie-havens/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ruthie Foster]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ruthie-foster/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ruthie Cecelia Foster is an American singer-songwriter of blues and folk music. She mixes a wide palette of American song forms, from gospel and blues to jazz, folk and soul. She has often been compared to Bonnie Raitt and Aretha Franklin.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/65/Ruthie_Foster3_-_1-24-07_-_Photo_by_Anthony_Pepitone.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ruthie-foster/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Terry Callier]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/terry-callier/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Terrence Orlando 'Terry' Callier was an American soul, folk and jazz guitarist and singer-songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/00/Terrycallier.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/terry-callier/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Todd Rundgren]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Todd Harry Rundgren is an American multi-instrumentalist, singer, songwriter, and record producer who has performed a diverse range of styles as a solo artist and as a member of the band Utopia. He is known for his sophisticated and often unorthodox music, his occasionally lavish stage shows, and his later experiments with interactive entertainment. He also produced music videos and was an early adopter and promoter of various computer technologies, such as using the Internet as a means of music distribution in the late 1990s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4b/Todd_Rundgren_performs_%40_WorkPlay.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tracy Chapman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tracy-chapman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tracy Chapman is an American singer-songwriter, known for her hits 'Fast Car' and 'Give Me One Reason', along with other singles 'Talkin' 'bout a Revolution', 'Baby Can I Hold You', and 'Crossroads'. She is a multi-platinum and four-time Grammy Award–winning artist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5e/Tracy_Chapman_3.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tracy-chapman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marie Lindberg]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marie-lindberg/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e5/Marie_Lindberg_augusti_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marie-lindberg/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Maxwell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/maxwell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gerald Maxwell Rivera, known mononymously as Maxwell, is an American singer-songwriter, record producer, and multi-instrumentalist. Along with fellow musicians D'Angelo and Erykah Badu, Maxwell has been credited as an originator of the 'neo soul' movement that rose to prominence during the late 1990s. He released his debut studio album Maxwell's Urban Hang Suite in 1996 to widespread critical acclaim and commercial success. The album was certified 2x Platinum and it was the first of four consecutive Platinum-selling studio albums. Maxwell released Embrya in 1998, Now in 2001 and BLACKsummers'night in 2009. BLACKsummers'night was nominated for 6 Grammy Awards, including Song of the Year for 'Pretty Wings'. Maxwell released his fifth studio album blackSUMMERS'night in 2016. He has won 3 Grammy Awards out of 13 nominations, 6 Soul Train Music Awards and 2 NAACP Image Awards. Maxwell was presented with the Lifetime Achievement Award for 'his innovative contributions to the music industry as a singer, songwriter, and producer' by the Congressional Black Caucus Foundation and Congressional Black Caucus in 2019.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/aa/Maxwell_%28musician%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/maxwell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Eli "Paperboy" Reed]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eli-"paperboy"-reed/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Eli 'Paperboy' Reed is an American singer and songwriter. After graduating from Brookline [Massachusetts] High School in 2002 he moved to Clarksdale, Mississippi and immersed himself in the juke joint culture of the Deep South. After spending a year in Clarksdale he enrolled at The University of Chicago to study sociology. While in Chicago he hosted a radio show called 'We Got More Soul' on the college station WHPK and played organ and piano in the South Side Chicago church of the famed Soul/Gospel singer Mitty Collier. After one year of study in Chicago he returned home to Boston to focus on music, recording his first album Sings Walkin' & Talkin' & Other Smash Hits!</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/38/Eli-Paperboy-Reed.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eli-"paperboy"-reed/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Charles Pitts]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/charles-pitts/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f7/Skip_Pitts_2nd_vrsion.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/charles-pitts/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Janis Joplin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/janis-joplin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Janis Lyn Joplin was an American singer-songwriter who sang rock, soul and blues music. One of the most successful and widely known rock stars of her era, she was noted for her powerful mezzo-soprano vocals and 'electric' stage presence.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/79/Janis_Joplin_in_1969_%28cropped%29.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/janis-joplin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>