<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Soul Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Soul Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 23:39:00 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Winehouse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Jade Winehouse was an English singer and songwriter. She was known for her deep, expressive contralto vocals and her eclectic mix of musical genres, including soul rhythm and blues, and jazz. Winehouse's debut album, Frank (2003), was a critical success in the UK and was nominated for the Mercury Prize. Her follow-up album, Back to Black (2006), led to five 2008 Grammy Awards, tying the then record for the most wins by a female artist in a single night, and made her the first British woman to win five Grammys, including three of the General Field 'Big Four' Grammy Awards: Best New Artist, Record of the Year and Song of the Year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Amy_Winehouse_f4962007_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Richie Havens]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richie-havens/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Pierce Havens was an American singer-songwriter and guitarist. His music encompassed elements of folk, soul, and rhythm and blues. He had an intense and rhythmic guitar style, and played soulful covers of pop and folk songs. He was the opening act at the 1969 Woodstock Festival.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2c/Richie_Havens_1972_Hamburg.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richie-havens/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ruthie Foster]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ruthie-foster/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ruthie Cecelia Foster is an American singer-songwriter of blues and folk music. She mixes a wide palette of American song forms, from gospel and blues to jazz, folk and soul. She has often been compared to Bonnie Raitt and Aretha Franklin.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/65/Ruthie_Foster3_-_1-24-07_-_Photo_by_Anthony_Pepitone.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ruthie-foster/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Meshell Ndegeocello]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/meshell-ndegeocello/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michelle Lynn Johnson, better known as Meshell Ndegeocello, is an American singer-songwriter, rapper, and bassist. She has gone by the name Meshell Suhaila Bashir-Shakur which is used as a writing credit on some of her later work. Her music incorporates a wide variety of influences, including funk, soul, jazz, hip hop, reggae and rock. She has received significant critical acclaim throughout her career, and although she has never won a Grammy Award, she has been nominated ten times. She has been credited for helping to have 'sparked the neo-soul movement.'</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/62/Meshell_Ndegeocello_Wikipedia.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/meshell-ndegeocello/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Todd Rundgren]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Todd Harry Rundgren is an American multi-instrumentalist, singer, songwriter, and record producer who has performed a diverse range of styles as a solo artist, and as a member of the band Utopia. He is known for his sophisticated and often-unorthodox music, flamboyant stage outfits, and his later experiments with interactive entertainment. He also produced music videos, pioneered forms of multimedia, and was an early adopter and promoter of various computer technologies, such as using the Internet as a means of music distribution in the late 1990s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4b/Todd_Rundgren_performs_%40_WorkPlay.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/todd-rundgren/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Willy DeVille]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willy-deville/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Willy DeVille was an American singer and songwriter. During his thirty-five-year career, first with his band Mink DeVille (1974–1986) and later on his own, Deville created original songs rooted in traditional American musical styles. He worked with collaborators from across the spectrum of contemporary music, including Jack Nitzsche, Doc Pomus, Dr. John, Mark Knopfler, Allen Toussaint, and Eddie Bo. Latin rhythms, blues riffs, doo-wop, Cajun music, strains of French cabaret, and echoes of early-1960s uptown soul can be heard in DeVille's work.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/08/2008-02-26_Willy_DeVille_IMG_8267.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willy-deville/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tim Maia]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tim-maia/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tim Maia was a Brazilian musician, songwriter and businessman known for his iconoclastic, ironic, outspoken, and humorous musical style. Maia contributed to Brazilian music within a wide variety of musical genres, including soul, funk, bossa nova, disco, romantic ballads, pop, rock, jazz, baião and MPB. He introduced the soul style on the Brazilian musical scene. Along with Jorge Ben, Maia pioneered MPB's samba rock genre, combining samba, soul, and funk. He is internationally recognised as one of the biggest icons of the Brazilian music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/df/TIM_MAIA_SONIA_D%27ALMEIDA_1987.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tim-maia/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hozier]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hozier/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Andrew John Hozier-Byrne, known professionally as Hozier, is an Irish musician, singer, and songwriter from County Wicklow. He had his international breakthrough after releasing his debut single 'Take Me to Church', which had been certified multi-platinum in several countries, including the US, the UK, and Canada.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f9/Hozier_Troubadour_West_Hollywood.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hozier/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Thomas McClary]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/thomas-mcclary/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas McClary is an American guitarist, singer, songwriter, and record producer best known as the founder and lead guitarist of The Commodores. McClary is credited with having created the signature sound of The Commodores' original music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/11/Thomas_McClary.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/thomas-mcclary/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[James Brown]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-brown/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Joseph Brown was an American singer, songwriter, dancer, musician, record producer and bandleader. A progenitor of funk music and a major figure of 20th-century music and dance, he is often referred to as the 'Godfather of Soul' and 'Soul Brother No. 1'. In a career that lasted over 50 years, he influenced the development of several music genres.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5d/Jamesbrown4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-brown/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>