<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Reggae</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Reggae</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 14:17:31 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Leonid Agutin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/leonid-agutin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3e/Leonid_Agutin%27s_rehearsal_at_Laima_Rendez_Vous_Jurmala_2017_.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/leonid-agutin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Earl "Chinna" Smith]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/earl-"chinna"-smith/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b4/ChinnaSmith.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/earl-"chinna"-smith/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sinéad O'Connor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sinéad-o'connor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sinéad Marie Bernadette O'Connor is an Irish singer-songwriter who rose to fame in the late 1980s with her debut album The Lion and the Cobra. O'Connor achieved worldwide success in 1990 with a new arrangement of Prince's song 'Nothing Compares 2 U.'</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ad/FIL_2013_-_Sin%C3%A9ad_O%27Connor_08.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sinéad-o'connor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Manolito]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/manu-chao/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Manu Chao is a French-born Spanish musician. He sings in French, Spanish, English, Italian, Arabic, Catalan, Galician, Portuguese, Greek and occasionally in other languages. Chao began his musical career in Paris, busking and playing with groups such as Hot Pants and Los Carayos, which combined a variety of languages and musical styles. With friends and his brother Antoine Chao, he founded the band Mano Negra in 1987, achieving considerable success, particularly in Europe. He became a solo artist after its breakup in 1995, and since then tours regularly with his live band, Radio Bemba.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/35/Manu_Chao_Live_at_Princep_Ghat_02.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/manu-chao/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jason Newsted]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-newsted/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jason Curtis Newsted is an American musician who was the bassist of American heavy metal band Metallica from 1986 to 2001. Beginning his career with thrash metal band Flotsam and Jetsam from 1981 to 1986, he successfully auditioned with Metallica to succeed the deceased Cliff Burton. Newsted performed on the albums ...And Justice for All (1988), Metallica (1991), Load (1996), and Reload (1997), the most album appearances among Metallica's bassists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/68/13-06-09_RaR_Newsted_10.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-newsted/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Peter Tosh]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-tosh/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Peter Tosh, OM was a Jamaican reggae musician. Along with Bob Marley and Bunny Wailer, he was one of the core members of the band the Wailers (1963–1976), after which he established himself as a successful solo artist and a promoter of Rastafari. He was murdered in 1987 during a home invasion.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5b/BushDoctor1978.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-tosh/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Samuel Rosa]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/samuel-rosa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/15/Samuel_Rosa.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/samuel-rosa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jason Mraz]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-mraz/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jason Thomas Mraz is an American guitarist, singer and songwriter. In 2002 he released his debut studio album, Waiting for My Rocket to Come, which contained the single 'The Remedy ' that reached number 15 on the Billboard Hot 100, his first top-40 hit in the US. His second album, Mr. A-Z, released in 2005, peaked at number 5 on the Billboard 200 and sold over 100,000 copies in the US. In 2008 Mraz released his third studio album, We Sing. We Dance. We Steal Things. It debuted at number 3 on the Billboard 200 and was an international commercial success primarily due to the hit 'I'm Yours'. The song peaked at number 6 on the Billboard Hot 100, giving him his first top ten single, spent a then-record 76 weeks on the Hot 100, and was certified Diamond by the RIAA in 2019. His fourth album, Love Is a Four Letter Word, peaked at number 2 on the Billboard 200, his highest-charting album to date.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/Jason_Mraz_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-mraz/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lenny Kravitz]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lenny-kravitz/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Leonard Albert Kravitz is an American singer, songwriter, musician, record producer, and actor. His style incorporates elements of rock, blues, soul, R&B, funk, jazz, reggae, hard rock, psychedelic, pop, folk, and ballads.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ac/Lenny_Kravitz_by_Gage_Skidmore.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lenny-kravitz/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bob Marley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-marley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Nesta Marley was a Jamaican singer, songwriter, and musician. Considered one of the pioneers of reggae, his musical career was marked by fusing elements of reggae, ska, and rocksteady, as well as his distinctive vocal and songwriting style. Marley's contributions to music increased the visibility of Jamaican music worldwide, and made him a global figure in popular culture for over a decade. Over the course of his career Marley became known as a Rastafari icon, and he infused his music with a sense of spirituality. He is also considered a global symbol of Jamaican music and culture and identity, and was controversial in his outspoken support for the legalization of marijuana, while he also advocated for Pan-Africanism.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5e/Bob-Marley.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-marley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>