<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Reggae</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Reggae</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:37:01 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Winehouse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Jade Winehouse was an English singer and songwriter. She was known for her deep, expressive contralto vocals and her eclectic mix of musical genres, including soul rhythm and blues, and jazz. Winehouse's debut album, Frank (2003), was a critical success in the UK and was nominated for the Mercury Prize. Her follow-up album, Back to Black (2006), led to five 2008 Grammy Awards, tying the then record for the most wins by a female artist in a single night, and made her the first British woman to win five Grammys, including three of the General Field 'Big Four' Grammy Awards: Best New Artist, Record of the Year and Song of the Year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Amy_Winehouse_f4962007_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Fermin Muguruza]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fermin-muguruza/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Fermin Muguruza is a Basque rock musician, singer, songwriter, producer, record label manager, and co-founder of the ska punk band Kortatu, active from 1983 to 1988, and of the crossover group Negu Gorriak, active from 1990 to 1996.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fe/FerminMuguruza.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fermin-muguruza/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Aston Barrett]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/aston-barrett/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Aston Francis Barrett, often called 'Family Man' or 'Fams' for short, is a Jamaican musician and Rastafarian.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2c/Aston_Barrett.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/aston-barrett/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lenny Kravitz]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lenny-kravitz/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Leonard Albert Kravitz is an American singer, songwriter, actor, record producer, and multi-instrumentalist. His 'retro' style incorporates elements of rock, blues, soul, R&B, funk, jazz, reggae, hard rock, psychedelic, pop, folk, and ballads.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/28/Lenny_Kravitz_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lenny-kravitz/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Peter Tosh]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-tosh/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Peter Tosh, OM was a Jamaican reggae musician. Along with Bob Marley and Bunny Wailer, he was one of the core members of the band the Wailers (1963–1976), after which he established himself as a successful solo artist and a promoter of Rastafari. He was murdered in 1987 during a home invasion.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5b/BushDoctor1978.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/peter-tosh/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Leonid Agutin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/leonid-agutin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Leonid Nikolayevich Agutin is a Russian pop musician and songwriter, Meritorious Artist of Russia (2008). He has been active since the 1990s. He has released ten albums and three compilation albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3e/Leonid_Agutin%27s_rehearsal_at_Laima_Rendez_Vous_Jurmala_2017_.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/leonid-agutin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sting]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sting/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gordon Matthew Thomas Sumner, known as Sting, is an English musician and actor. He was the principal songwriter, lead singer, and bassist for the new wave rock band the Police from 1977 to 1984, and launched a solo career in 1985. He has included elements of rock, jazz, reggae, classical, new-age and worldbeat in his music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Sting_-_Deutscher_Radiopreis_Hamburg_2016_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sting/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bob Marley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-marley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Nesta Marley, was a Jamaican singer and songwriter. Considered one of the pioneers of reggae, his musical career was marked by blending elements of reggae, ska, and rocksteady, as well as forging a smooth and distinctive vocal and songwriting style. Marley's contributions to music increased the visibility of Jamaican music worldwide, and made him a global figure in popular culture for over a decade. Over the course of his career Marley became known as a Rastafari icon, and the singer sought to infuse his music with a sense of spirituality. He is also considered a global symbol of Jamaican culture and identity, and was controversial in his outspoken support for the legalization of marijuana, while he also advocated for Pan-Africanism.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5e/Bob-Marley.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-marley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ali Campbell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ali-campbell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alistair Ian Campbell is an English singer and songwriter who was the lead singer and a member of the English reggae band UB40. As part of UB40, Campbell sold over 70 million records worldwide and toured the globe for 30 years. In 2008, Campbell left UB40 due to a dispute with band management so he then embarked on a solo career. In 2012, Campbell was announced as one of the three judges on the judging panel of the TV show, New Zealand's Got Talent. In August 2014, Campbell announced that he had reunited with former UB40 band mates Astro and Mickey to record a new album, Silhouette, released on 6 October 2014.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8c/Ali_Campbell_at_Raggamuffin_2009_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ali-campbell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Manu Chao]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/manu-chao/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Manu Chao is a French musician of Spanish descent. He sings in French, Spanish, English, Italian, Arabic, Catalan, Galician, Portuguese, Greek and occasionally in other languages. Chao began his musical career in Paris, busking and playing with groups such as Hot Pants and Los Carayos, which combined a variety of languages and musical styles. With friends and his brother Antoine Chao, he founded the band Mano Negra in 1987, achieving considerable success, particularly in Europe. He became a solo artist after its breakup in 1995, and since then tours regularly with his live band, Radio Bemba.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/43/Manu_Chao_at_2007_Coachella_Valley_Music_and_Arts_Festival.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/manu-chao/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>