<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Reggae</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Reggae</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:04:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Winehouse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Jade Winehouse was an English singer and songwriter. She was known for her deep, expressive contralto vocals and her eclectic mix of musical genres, including soul rhythm and blues, and jazz. Winehouse's debut album, Frank (2003), was a critical success in the UK and was nominated for the Mercury Prize. Her follow-up album, Back to Black (2006), led to five 2008 Grammy Awards, tying the then record for the most wins by a female artist in a single night, and made her the first British woman to win five Grammys, including three of the General Field 'Big Four' Grammy Awards: Best New Artist, Record of the Year and Song of the Year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Amy_Winehouse_f4962007_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lenny Kravitz]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lenny-kravitz/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Leonard Albert Kravitz is an American singer, songwriter, actor, record producer, and multi-instrumentalist. His 'retro' style incorporates elements of rock, blues, soul, R&B, funk, jazz, reggae, hard rock, psychedelic, pop, folk, and ballads.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/28/Lenny_Kravitz_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lenny-kravitz/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Leonid Agutin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/leonid-agutin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Leonid Nikolayevich Agutin is a Russian pop musician and songwriter, Meritorious Artist of Russia (2008). He has been active since the 1990s. He has released ten albums and three compilation albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3e/Leonid_Agutin%27s_rehearsal_at_Laima_Rendez_Vous_Jurmala_2017_.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/leonid-agutin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sting]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sting/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gordon Matthew Thomas Sumner, known as Sting, is an English musician and actor. He was the principal songwriter, lead singer, and bassist for the new wave rock band the Police from 1977 to 1984, and launched a solo career in 1985. He has included elements of rock, jazz, reggae, classical, new-age and worldbeat in his music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Sting_-_Deutscher_Radiopreis_Hamburg_2016_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sting/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bob Marley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-marley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Nesta Marley, was a Jamaican singer and songwriter. Considered one of the pioneers of reggae, his musical career was marked by blending elements of reggae, ska, and rocksteady, as well as forging a smooth and distinctive vocal and songwriting style. Marley's contributions to music increased the visibility of Jamaican music worldwide, and made him a global figure in popular culture for over a decade.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5e/Bob-Marley.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-marley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Manu Chao]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/manu-chao/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Manu Chao is a French musician of Spanish descent. He sings in French, Spanish, English, Italian, Arabic, Catalan, Galician, Portuguese, Greek and occasionally in other languages. Chao began his musical career in Paris, busking and playing with groups such as Hot Pants and Los Carayos, which combined a variety of languages and musical styles. With friends and his brother Antoine Chao, he founded the band Mano Negra in 1987, achieving considerable success, particularly in Europe. He became a solo artist after its breakup in 1995, and since then tours regularly with his live band, Radio Bemba.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/43/Manu_Chao_at_2007_Coachella_Valley_Music_and_Arts_Festival.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/manu-chao/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jason Mraz]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-mraz/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jason Thomas Mraz is an American singer-songwriter. In 2002 he released his debut studio album, Waiting for My Rocket to Come, which contained the single 'The Remedy ' that reached #4 on the US Billboard chart. His second album, Mr. A-Z, released in 2005, peaked at number 5 on the Billboard 200 and sold over 100,000 copies in the US. In 2008 Mraz released his third studio album, We Sing. We Dance. We Steal Things. It debuted at number 3 on the Billboard 200. and was an international commercial success primarily due to the hit 'I'm Yours'. The song peaked at number 6 on the Billboard Hot 100, giving him his first top ten single, and spent a then-record 76 weeks on the Hot 100. His fourth album, Love Is a Four Letter Word, peaked at number 2 on the Billboard 200, his highest-charting album to date.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/Jason_Mraz_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jason-mraz/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sinéad O'Connor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sinéad-o'connor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sinéad Marie Bernadette O’Connor is an Irish singer-songwriter who rose to fame in the late 1980s with her debut album The Lion and the Cobra. O’Connor achieved worldwide success in 1990 with a new arrangement of Prince’s song 'Nothing Compares 2 U'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ad/FIL_2013_-_Sin%C3%A9ad_O%27Connor_08.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sinéad-o'connor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>