<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Alternative Country</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Alternative Country</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:38:12 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Alvin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Albert Alvin is an American singer-songwriter, guitarist, music producer and poet. He is a former and founding member of the roots rock band the Blasters. Alvin has recorded and performed as a solo artist since the late 1980s and has been involved in various side projects and collaborations. He has had brief stints as a member of the bands X and the Knitters.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Dave_Alvin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Willie Nelson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Willie Hugh Nelson is an American musician, actor, and activist. The critical success of the album Shotgun Willie (1973), combined with the critical and commercial success of Red Headed Stranger (1975) and Stardust (1978), made Nelson one of the most recognized artists in country music. He was one of the main figures of outlaw country, a subgenre of country music that developed in the late 1960s as a reaction to the conservative restrictions of the Nashville sound. Nelson has acted in over 30 films, co-authored several books, and has been involved in activism for the use of biofuels and the legalization of marijuana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/WillieNelson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Israel Nash]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/israel-nash/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Israel Nash is the recording and performing stage name moniker of American singer, songwriter, and guitarist Israel Nash Gripka.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d2/I_n_gripka-light_of_day_2012.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/israel-nash/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Teddy Thompson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/teddy-thompson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Teddy Thompson is a British folk and rock musician. He is the son of folk-rock musicians Richard and Linda Thompson and brother of singer Kamila Thompson. He released his first album in 2000.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0b/Teddy_Thompson_2-17-04_-_Photo_by_Anthony_Pepitone.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/teddy-thompson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Black Francis]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/black-francis/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Charles Thompson IV is an American singer, songwriter, and guitarist. He is best known as the frontman of the influential alternative rock band Pixies, with whom he performs under the stage name Black Francis. Following the band's breakup in 1993, he embarked on a solo career under the name Frank Black. After releasing two albums with record label 4AD and one with American Recordings, he left the label and formed a new band, Frank Black and the Catholics. He re-adopted the name Black Francis in 2007.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fc/Pixies-Frank_Black.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/black-francis/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Earle]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-earle/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen Fain Earle is an American rock, country and folk singer-songwriter, record producer, author and actor. Earle began his career as a songwriter in Nashville and released his first EP in 1982.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a2/Steve_Earle_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-earle/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jay Bennett]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jay-bennett/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jay Walter Bennett was an American guitarist, multi-instrumentalist, engineer, producer, and singer-songwriter, best known as a member of the band Wilco from 1994 to 2001.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f0/JayBennettKenCoomer.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jay-bennett/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:11 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Emily Robison]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emily-robison/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Emily Burns Strayer is an American songwriter, singer, multi-instrumentalist, and a founding member of the country band the Dixie Chicks. Strayer plays banjo, dobro, guitar, lap steel, bass, mandolin, accordion, and sitar. Initially in her career with the Dixie Chicks, she limited her singing to harmony with backing vocals, but within her role in the Court Yard Hounds, she has taken on the role of lead vocalist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e9/Emily_Robison_with_dobro.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emily-robison/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:11 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Emmylou Harris]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emmylou-harris/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Emmylou Harris is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. She has released dozens of albums and singles over the course of her career and won 14 Grammys, the Polar Music Prize, and numerous other honors, including induction into the Country Music Hall of Fame. In 2018 she was presented the Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/55/Emmylou_Harris_with_guitar.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emmylou-harris/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:11 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Luke Winslow-King]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/luke-winslow-king/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Luke Winslow-King Balzuweit is an American guitarist, multi-instrumentalist, singer, composer, and lyricist based out of Cadillac, Michigan, who plays vintage blues and jazz music and is known for his slide guitar work. He is a music traditionalist, playing a mixture of 'people's music' and improvisational jazz based in collective improvisation, with influences from New Orleans, where he was based for 15 years, that includes jazz, Delta blues, ragtime, pre-war American folk, with influences from diverse sources like Béla Bartók and Antonín Dvořák's String Quartet No. 12  and Woody Guthrie.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5b/Luke_Winslow-King_Rudolstadt_06.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/luke-winslow-king/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:11 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>