<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Folk Pop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Folk Pop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 20:52:10 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marit Larsen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marit-larsen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Marit Elisabeth Larsen is a Norwegian singer and songwriter. She began playing violin at age of 5 and played it until the age of 8. She gained international fame during her teenage years as a member of the pop duo M2M with childhood friend Marion Raven. She then pursued her own music career, releasing her debut solo album Under the Surface in 2006. Her second album, The Chase, was released in Norway in October 2008. Her third album, titled Spark was released in Norway, Denmark, Sweden and Finland on 18 November 2011, and in Germany, Austria and Switzerland on 16 December 2011. Her fourth studio album When the Morning Comes was released on 20 October 2014. Larsen toured in its support within Norway with her own concerts, played songs from the album in Germany and Switzerland at public festivals and was the opening act at two of Johannes Oerding's concerts in November 2015.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/44/2015_Marit_Larsen_-_by_2eight_-_DSC3575.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marit-larsen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ed Sheeran]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ed-sheeran/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Edward Christopher Sheeran is an English singer, songwriter, record producer, musician, actor, and businessman. After first recording music in 2004, he began gaining attention through YouTube. In early 2011, Sheeran independently released the extended play, No. 5 Collaborations Project. He signed with Asylum Records the same year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/Ed_Sheeran-6886_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ed-sheeran/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nina Nesbitt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nina-nesbitt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nina Lindberg Nesbitt is a Scottish singer and songwriter. She has two top 40 singles, and is known for her single 'Stay Out', which peaked at 21 on the UK Singles Chart in April 2013.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Nina_Nesbitt_2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nina-nesbitt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Yui]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yui-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Yui, stylized as YUI or yui, is a Japanese singer-songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, and actress. In her solo career, she sold more than 5 million physical copies in Japan. She is popular in Japan and in surrounding countries, ranking number one in 2011 Count Down TV 'Dearest Female Artist' and Music Station 'Artist You Most Want to Marry' polls, as well as Radio Television Hong Kong's 'Most Popular Japanese Artist'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b3/Yui_the_MTV_Music_Awards_2006.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yui-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sufjan Stevens]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sufjan-stevens/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sufjan Stevens is an American singer, songwriter, and multi-instrumentalist. He has released eight solo studio albums and multiple collaborative albums with other artists. Stevens has received Academy Award and Grammy Award nominations.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/84/Sufjan_Stevens_playing_banjo_edit1_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sufjan-stevens/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shawn Mendes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shawn-mendes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shawn Peter Raul Mendes is a Canadian singer and songwriter. He gained a following in 2013, posting song covers on the video-sharing application Vine. The following year, he caught the attention of artist manager Andrew Gertler and Island Records A&R Ziggy Chareton, which led to him signing a deal with the record label. Mendes's self-titled debut EP was released in 2014, followed by his debut studio album Handwritten in 2015. Handwritten debuted atop the US Billboard 200, making Mendes one of five artists ever to debut at number one before the age of 18. The single 'Stitches' reached number one in the UK and the top 10 in the US and Canada.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a4/191125_Shawn_Mendes_at_the_2019_American_Music_Awards.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shawn-mendes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tomáš Klus]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tomáš-klus/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3c/T_Klus_2014.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tomáš-klus/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bob Dylan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-dylan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bob Dylan is an American singer-songwriter, author and visual artist. Often regarded as one of the greatest songwriters of all time, Dylan has been a major figure in popular culture during a career spanning nearly 60 years. Much of his most celebrated work dates from the 1960s, when songs such as 'Blowin' in the Wind' (1963) and 'The Times They Are a-Changin'' (1964) became anthems for the civil rights and anti-war movements. His lyrics during this period incorporated a range of political, social, philosophical, and literary influences, defying pop music conventions and appealing to the burgeoning counterculture.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/28/Joan_Baez_Bob_Dylan_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-dylan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Denver]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-denver/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Henry John Deutschendorf Jr., known professionally as John Denver, was an American singer-songwriter, activist, and humanitarian whose greatest commercial success was as a solo singer. After traveling and living in numerous locations while growing up in his military family, Denver began his music career with folk music groups during the late 1960s. Starting in the 1970s, he was one of the most popular acoustic artists of the decade and one of its best-selling artists. By 1974, he was one of America's best-selling performers; AllMusic has called Denver 'among the most beloved entertainers of his era'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b0/John_Denver_1975.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-denver/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Niall Horan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/niall-horan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Niall James Horan is an Irish singer and songwriter. He rose to prominence as a member of the boy band One Direction, formed in 2010 on the British singing competition The X Factor. The group released five albums and went on to become one of the best-selling boy bands of all time. Following the band's hiatus in 2016, Horan signed a recording deal as a solo artist with Capitol Records.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e3/Niall_Horan_Portrait.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/niall-horan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>