<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Folk Pop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Folk Pop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 19:59:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ed Sheeran]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ed-sheeran/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Edward Christopher Sheeran, is an English singer, songwriter, guitarist, record producer, and actor. In early 2011, Sheeran independently released the extended play, No. 5 Collaborations Project. After signing with Asylum Records, his debut album, +, was released in September 2011. It topped the UK and Australian charts, reached number five in the US, and has since been certified eight-times platinum in the UK. The album contains the single 'The A Team', which earned him the Ivor Novello Award for Best Song Musically and Lyrically. In 2012, Sheeran won the Brit Awards for Best British Male Solo Artist and British Breakthrough Act. 'The A Team' was nominated for Song of the Year at the 2013 Grammy Awards, where he performed the song with Elton John.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/55/Ed_Sheeran_2013.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ed-sheeran/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Laura Marling]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/laura-marling/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Laura Beatrice Marling is a British folk singer-songwriter. She won the Brit Award for Best British Female Solo Artist at the 2011 Brit Awards, and was nominated for the same award at the 2012, 2014, 2016, and 2018 Brit Awards.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/75/Laura_Marling_-_First_Avenue_-_5_5_17_%2834106214720%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/laura-marling/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shawn Mendes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shawn-mendes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shawn Peter Raul Mendes is a Canadian singer, songwriter and model. He gained a following in 2013, posting song covers on the video-sharing application Vine. The following year, he caught the attention of artist manager Andrew Gertler and Island Records A&R Ziggy Chareton, which led to him signing a deal with the record label. He has since released three studio albums, headlined three world tours, and received several awards.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b4/Shawn_Mendes_at_The_Queen%27s_Birthday_Party_%28cropped_2%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shawn-mendes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nina Nesbitt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nina-nesbitt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nina Lindberg Nesbitt is a Scottish singer and songwriter. She has two top 40 singles, and is known for her single 'Stay Out', which peaked at 21 on the UK Singles Chart in April 2013.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Nina_Nesbitt_2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nina-nesbitt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Øystein Sunde]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/øystein-sunde/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Øystein Olaf Sunde is a Norwegian folk singer and guitarist. He is known for his high-speed guitar and banjo style and his satirical lyrics. Although often regarded as a comedian, Sunde is a versatile jazz guitarist who has played with several Dixieland bands and jazz combos over the years.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/04/Sunde01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/øystein-sunde/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bob Dylan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-dylan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bob Dylan is an American singer-songwriter, author, and visual artist who has been a major figure in popular culture for more than fifty years. Much of his most celebrated work dates from the 1960s, when songs such as 'Blowin' in the Wind' (1963) and 'The Times They Are a-Changin'' (1964) became anthems for the civil rights movement and anti-war movement. His lyrics during this period incorporated a wide range of political, social, philosophical, and literary influences, defied pop-music conventions and appealed to the burgeoning counterculture.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/28/Joan_Baez_Bob_Dylan_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bob-dylan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>