<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Surf Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Surf Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:49:34 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jack Johnson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-johnson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jack Hody Johnson is an American singer-songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, actor, record producer, documentary filmmaker and former professional surfer. Johnson is known primarily for his work in the soft rock and acoustic genres. In 2001, he achieved commercial success after the release of his debut album, Brushfire Fairytales. Johnson has reached number one on the Billboard 200 chart with his albums Sing-A-Longs and Lullabies for the Film Curious George in 2006, Sleep Through the Static in 2008, To the Sea in 2010 and From Here to Now to You in 2013. His album In Between Dreams peaked at number two on the chart in 2005 and again in 2013.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4f/Bonnaroo08_jackjohnson2_lg.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jack-johnson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dick Dale]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dick-dale/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Anthony Monsour, known professionally as Dick Dale, was an American rock guitarist. He was a pioneer of surf music, drawing on Middle Eastern music scales and experimenting with reverberation. Dale was known as 'The King of the Surf Guitar', which was also the title of his second studio album.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/aa/Dick_Dale.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dick-dale/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:38 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Marks]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-marks/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Lee Marks is an American guitarist who was an early member of the Beach Boys. Marks was a neighborhood friend of the original band members while growing up in Hawthorne, California, and was a frequent participant at the Wilson family Sunday night singalongs. Following his initial departure from the group, Marks fronted the Marksmen and performed and recorded as a session musician.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1f/David_Marks_2019_by_Glenn_Francis.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-marks/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:38 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>