<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » System Of A Down</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » System Of A Down</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 19:07:34 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Serj Tankian]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Serj Tankian is an Armenian-American musician, singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, poet and political activist. He is best known as the lead vocalist, songwriter, keyboardist, and occasional live rhythm guitarist of the band System of a Down, formed in 1994.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/69/Serj_Tankian_Spirit_of_Burgas_Bulgaria_2010_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shavo Odadjian]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shavo-odadjian/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shavarsh 'Shavo' Odadjian is an Armenian-American musician, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, music video director, and painter. He is best known as the bassist, backing vocalist and occasional songwriter of the Grammy Award-winning metal band System of a Down. During the band's hiatus from 2006 to 2010, Odadjian collaborated with Wu-Tang Clan founder RZA on a project called AcHoZeN, which contributed a number of songs to the motion picture Babylon A.D. A compilation album was released in 2015. Odadjian is also credited with the musical scoring of the film, alongside The Rza and Hans Zimmer. He originally used Gibson Thunderbird basses, a Fender Jazz Bass, an Ibanez BTB bass guitar, and a Music Man StingRay, but has since moved on to Warwick basses.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c0/System_Of_A_Down_%40_Claremont_Showgrounds_%285_3_2012%29_%286859500592%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shavo-odadjian/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Daron Malakian]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daron-malakian/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Daron Vartan Malakian is an Armenian-American musician, singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, and record producer. He is best known as the guitarist, songwriter and second vocalist of the metal band System of a Down and as the lead vocalist, lead guitarist and songwriter of the band Scars on Broadway. Daron Malakian is known for his distinctive playing and is ranked 14th in Loudwire's list of Top 50 Hard Rock + Metal Guitarists of All Time and number 11 in MusicRadar's poll, The 20 Greatest Metal Guitarists Ever. He is placed 30th in Guitar World's list of The 100 Greatest Heavy Metal Guitarists of All Time.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/DM-photo.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daron-malakian/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>