<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Musician</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Musician</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:04:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shakira]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shakira Isabel Mebarak Ripoll is a Colombian singer, songwriter, dancer, businesswoman, and philanthropist. Born and raised in Barranquilla, she made her recording debut under Sony Music Colombia at the age of 13. Following the commercial failure of her first two Colombian albums, Magia (1991) and Peligro (1993), she rose to prominence in Spanish-speaking countries with her next albums, Pies Descalzos (1995) and Dónde Están los Ladrones? (1998). Shakira entered the English-language market with her fifth album, Laundry Service (2001). It sold over 13 million copies and spawned the international number-one singles 'Whenever, Wherever' and 'Underneath Your Clothes'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/Shakira_in_Toronto_2018.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Winehouse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Jade Winehouse was an English singer and songwriter. She was known for her deep, expressive contralto vocals and her eclectic mix of musical genres, including soul rhythm and blues, and jazz. Winehouse's debut album, Frank (2003), was a critical success in the UK and was nominated for the Mercury Prize. Her follow-up album, Back to Black (2006), led to five 2008 Grammy Awards, tying the then record for the most wins by a female artist in a single night, and made her the first British woman to win five Grammys, including three of the General Field 'Big Four' Grammy Awards: Best New Artist, Record of the Year and Song of the Year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Amy_Winehouse_f4962007_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Willie Nelson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Willie Hugh Nelson is an American musician, actor, and activist. The critical success of the album Shotgun Willie (1973), combined with the critical and commercial success of Red Headed Stranger (1975) and Stardust (1978), made Nelson one of the most recognized artists in country music. He was one of the main figures of outlaw country, a subgenre of country music that developed in the late 1960s as a reaction to the conservative restrictions of the Nashville sound. Nelson has acted in over 30 films, co-authored several books, and has been involved in activism for the use of biofuels and the legalization of marijuana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/WillieNelson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Alvin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Albert Alvin is an American singer-songwriter, guitarist, music producer and poet. He is a former and founding member of the roots rock band the Blasters. Alvin has recorded and performed as a solo artist since the late 1980s and has been involved in various side projects and collaborations. He has had brief stints as a member of the bands X and the Knitters.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Dave_Alvin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nikita Dzhigurda]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nikita-dzhigurda/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nikita Borisovich Dzhigurda or Mykyta Borysovych Dzhyhurda is a Ukrainian-Russian movie actor, singer, and cult media icon.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7b/%D0%94%D0%B6%D0%B8%D0%B3%D1%83%D1%80%D0%B4%D0%B0_%D0%9D%D0%B8%D0%BA%D0%B8%D1%82%D0%B0.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nikita-dzhigurda/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Linda Ronstadt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/linda-ronstadt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Linda Maria Ronstadt is a retired American popular music singer known for singing in a wide range of genres including rock, country, light opera, and Latin. She has earned 10 Grammy Awards, three American Music Awards, two Academy of Country Music awards, an Emmy Award, and an ALMA Award, and many of her albums have been certified gold, platinum or multiplatinum in the United States and internationally. She has also earned nominations for a Tony Award and a Golden Globe award. She was awarded the Latin Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award by The Latin Recording Academy in 2011 and also awarded the Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award by The Recording Academy in 2016. She was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in April 2014. On July 28, 2014, she was awarded the National Medal of Arts and Humanities. In 2019, she will receive a joint star with Dolly Parton and Emmylou Harris on the Hollywood Walk of Fame for their work as the group Trio.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/50/LindaRonstadtPerforming.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/linda-ronstadt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Grand]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-grand/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steve Grand is an American singer, songwriter and model from Lemont, Illinois, a Chicago suburb. He became an overnight internet celebrity and the music video of his first hit 'All-American Boy' went viral on YouTube in less than a week in July 2013. This attention landed Grand on Good Morning America, CNN and other national media. In addition to being a musician, Grand has become an active figure in the LGBT equality movement. He released his debut album titled All American Boy financed by a successful Kickstarter public funding campaign. The follow-up album Not the End of Me was released in 2018.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/36/Steve_Grand_-_1032013.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-grand/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andrea Bocelli]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrea-bocelli/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Andrea Bocelli is an Italian opera singer, songwriter, and record producer. Celine Dion has said that 'if God would have a singing voice, he must sound a lot like Andrea Bocelli,' and David Foster, a record producer, often describes Bocelli's voice as the most beautiful in the world.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/15/AndreaBocelliMar10.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andrea-bocelli/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alanis Morissette]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alanis Nadine Morissette is a Canadian-American singer, songwriter, record producer, and actress. Known for her emotive mezzo-soprano voice, Morissette began her career in Canada in the early 1990s with two mildly successful dance-pop albums. Afterwards, as part of a recording deal, she moved to Holmby Hills, Los Angeles and in 1995 released Jagged Little Pill, a more rock-oriented album which sold more than 33 million copies globally and is her most critically acclaimed work. Her follow-up album, Supposed Former Infatuation Junkie, was released in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/82/Alanis_Morissette_5-19-2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alanis-morissette/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[James Williamson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-williamson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Robert Williamson is an American guitarist, songwriter, record producer and electronics engineer. He was a member of the iconic proto-punk rock band The Stooges, notably on the influential album Raw Power and in the reformed Stooges from 2009 to 2016. Between his stints in music, Williamson worked in Silicon Valley developing computer chips. Most recently he has continued as a solo artist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ee/Iggy_%26_the_Stooges_%40_Brussels_Summer_Festival_2012_%288371448222%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-williamson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>