<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Rhythm And Blues</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Rhythm And Blues</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 23:39:00 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Winehouse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Jade Winehouse was an English singer and songwriter. She was known for her deep, expressive contralto vocals and her eclectic mix of musical genres, including soul rhythm and blues, and jazz. Winehouse's debut album, Frank (2003), was a critical success in the UK and was nominated for the Mercury Prize. Her follow-up album, Back to Black (2006), led to five 2008 Grammy Awards, tying the then record for the most wins by a female artist in a single night, and made her the first British woman to win five Grammys, including three of the General Field 'Big Four' Grammy Awards: Best New Artist, Record of the Year and Song of the Year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Amy_Winehouse_f4962007_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Elvis Presley]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elvis-presley/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Elvis Aaron Presley, also known mononymously as Elvis, was an American singer and actor. Regarded as one of the most significant cultural icons of the 20th century, he is often referred to as the 'King of Rock and Roll' or simply 'the King'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2d/PresleyPromo1954PhotoOnly.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elvis-presley/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nile Rodgers]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nile-rodgers/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nile Gregory Rodgers Jr. is an American record producer, songwriter, musician, composer, arranger and guitarist. The co-founder of Chic, he has written, produced, and performed on records that have cumulatively sold more than 500 million albums and 75 million singles worldwide. He is a Rock and Roll Hall of Fame inductee, a three-time Grammy Award-winner, and the chairman of the Songwriters Hall of Fame. Known for his 'chucking' guitar style, Rolling Stone wrote in 2014 that 'the full scope of Nile Rodgers' career is still hard to fathom.'</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/46/Nilerodgers.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nile-rodgers/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ronnie Lane]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ronnie-lane/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ronald Frederick 'Ronnie' Lane was an English musician, songwriter, and producer who is best known as the bass guitarist and founding member of two prominent English rock and roll bands: Small Faces (1965–69) and subsequently Faces (1969–73). With Small Faces he was nicknamed 'Plonk'. After their breakup, reorganisation and Lane's losing the band's frontman slot to Rod Stewart, he earned the nickname 'Three-Piece'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f7/Ronnie_Lane.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ronnie-lane/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ike Turner]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ike-turner/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Izear Luster 'Ike' Turner Jr. was an American musician, bandleader, songwriter, arranger, talent scout, and record producer. An early pioneer of fifties rock and roll, he is best known for his work in the 1960s and 1970s with his then-wife Tina Turner in the Ike & Tina Turner Revue.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b9/Iketurner1997.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ike-turner/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nelly Furtado]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nelly Kim Furtado is a Canadian singer and songwriter. Furtado first gained fame with her debut album, Whoa, Nelly! (2000), which was a critical and commercial success that spawned two top 10 singles on the Billboard Hot 100, 'I'm Like a Bird' and 'Turn Off the Light'. The first of the two singles won her a Grammy Award for Best Female Pop Vocal Performance. In 2003, she released her second album, Folklore, which was preceded by the lead single, 'Powerless '.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/aa/Nelly_Furtado_at_Radio_Regenbogen_Award_2017_%286%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Willy DeVille]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willy-deville/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Willy DeVille was an American singer and songwriter. During his thirty-five-year career, first with his band Mink DeVille (1974–1986) and later on his own, Deville created original songs rooted in traditional American musical styles. He worked with collaborators from across the spectrum of contemporary music, including Jack Nitzsche, Doc Pomus, Dr. John, Mark Knopfler, Allen Toussaint, and Eddie Bo. Latin rhythms, blues riffs, doo-wop, Cajun music, strains of French cabaret, and echoes of early-1960s uptown soul can be heard in DeVille's work.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/08/2008-02-26_Willy_DeVille_IMG_8267.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willy-deville/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bill Wyman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-wyman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Bill Wyman is an English musician, record producer, songwriter and singer. He was the bass guitarist for the English rock and roll band the Rolling Stones from 1962 until 1993. Since 1997 he has recorded and toured with his own band, Bill Wyman's Rhythm Kings. He has worked producing records and films, and has scored music for film in films and television.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a3/Bill_Wyman_2009.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-wyman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Miguel]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/miguel-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Miguel Jontel Pimentel is an American R&B singer, songwriter and record producer. Raised in San Pedro, California, he began pursuing a music career at age thirteen. After signing to Jive Records in 2007, Miguel released his debut studio album, All I Want Is You, in November 2010. Although it was underpromoted upon its release, the album became a sleeper hit and helped Miguel garner commercial standing.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fb/Miguel_2019_by_Glenn_Francis.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/miguel-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>