<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Rhythm And Blues</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Rhythm And Blues</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:04:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Winehouse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Jade Winehouse was an English singer and songwriter. She was known for her deep, expressive contralto vocals and her eclectic mix of musical genres, including soul rhythm and blues, and jazz. Winehouse's debut album, Frank (2003), was a critical success in the UK and was nominated for the Mercury Prize. Her follow-up album, Back to Black (2006), led to five 2008 Grammy Awards, tying the then record for the most wins by a female artist in a single night, and made her the first British woman to win five Grammys, including three of the General Field 'Big Four' Grammy Awards: Best New Artist, Record of the Year and Song of the Year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Amy_Winehouse_f4962007_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nelly Furtado]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nelly Kim Furtado is a Canadian singer and songwriter. Furtado first gained fame with her debut album, Whoa, Nelly! (2000), which was a critical and commercial success that spawned two top 10 singles on the Billboard Hot 100, 'I'm Like a Bird' and 'Turn Off the Light'. The first of the two singles won her a Grammy Award for Best Female Pop Vocal Performance. In 2003, she released her second album, Folklore, which was preceded by the lead single, 'Powerless '.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/aa/Nelly_Furtado_at_Radio_Regenbogen_Award_2017_%286%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shawn Mendes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shawn-mendes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shawn Peter Raul Mendes is a Canadian singer, songwriter and model. He gained a following in 2013, posting song covers on the video-sharing application Vine. The following year, he caught the attention of artist manager Andrew Gertler and Island Records A&R Ziggy Chareton, which led to him signing a deal with the record label. He has since released three studio albums, headlined three world tours, and received several awards.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b4/Shawn_Mendes_at_The_Queen%27s_Birthday_Party_%28cropped_2%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shawn-mendes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Evgeny Margulis]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/evgeny-margulis/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Evgeny Shulimovich Margulis is a Russian rock and blues musician. He was a member of the bands, Mashina Vremeni and Voskreseniye and currently performs with his solo project. He is considered a 'guru' of the Moscow rock ‘n’ roll and one of the best Blues guitarists, bass guitarists and bluesmen in Russia. In 1999 he was awarded with the title of Meritorious Artist</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e3/%D0%95%D0%B2%D0%B3%D0%B5%D0%BD%D0%B8%D0%B9_%D0%9C%D0%B0%D1%80%D0%B3%D1%83%D0%BB%D0%B8%D1%81_cropped_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/evgeny-margulis/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian McKnight]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-mcknight/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Kelly McKnight is an American singer-songwriter, actor, arranger, record producer, and multi-instrumentalist. McKnight is most recognized for his strong falsetto and belting range. McKnight's work has earned him 16 Grammy Awards nominations, albeit never been awarded one. He is third only to Morten Lindberg and Snoop Dogg for the record of most Grammy nominations without a win.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ac/Brian_McKnight.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-mcknight/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Elton John]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elton-john/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir Elton Hercules John is an English singer, songwriter, pianist, and composer. He has worked with lyricist Bernie Taupin since 1967; they have collaborated on more than 30 albums. John has sold more than 300 million records, making him one of the world's best-selling music artists. He has more than fifty Top 40 hits, as well as seven consecutive number-one albums in the United States, 58 Billboard Top 40 singles, 27 Top 10 singles, four of which peaked at number two and nine of which reached number one. His tribute single 'Candle in the Wind 1997', rewritten in dedication to Diana, Princess of Wales, sold over 33 million copies worldwide and is the best-selling single in the history of the UK and US singles charts. He has also produced records and occasionally acted in films. John owned Watford F.C. from 1976 to 1987 and from 1997 to 2002, and is an honorary Life President of the club.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/80/Elton_John_2011_Shankbone_2_%28cropped%29.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/elton-john/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anhayla]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anhayla/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Anhayla Rene Stanley, better known by her stage name Anhayla, is an American singer, songwriter, and guitarist. She is known for covering popular R&B and hip hop songs presented on her YouTube channel, Anhaylarene. Anhayla was endorsed by Crafter guitars in 2013.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1a/Anhayla_performing_at_Hippodrome_in_Richmond%2C_VA.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anhayla/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brandon Heath]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brandon-heath/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brandon Heath Knell is an American contemporary Christian musician, singer, and songwriter from Nashville, Tennessee. He has released six studio albums: Don't Get Comfortable (2006), What If We (2008), Leaving Eden (2011), Blue Mountain (2012), No Turning Back (2015), and Faith Hope Love Repeat (2017). He is best known for the No. 1 singles: 'I'm Not Who I Was' and 'Give Me Your Eyes'. He was nominated four times at the Dove Awards of 2008 and won in the 'New Artist of the Year' category. His second album was nominated for 'Gospel Album of the Year' at the 51st Grammy Awards of 2009.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b8/Brandon_Heath_-_Revelation_Tour_2009.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brandon-heath/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adele]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adele/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Adele Laurie Blue Adkins is an English singer-songwriter. After graduating from the BRIT School in 2006, Adele signed a recording contract with XL Recordings. In 2007, she received the Brit Awards Critics' Choice award and won the BBC Sound of 2008 poll. Her debut album, 19, was released in 2008 to commercial and critical success. It is certified eight times platinum in the UK, and three times platinum in the US. The album contains her first song, 'Hometown Glory', written when she was 16, which is based on her home suburb of West Norwood in London. An appearance she made on Saturday Night Live in late 2008 boosted her career in the US. At the 51st Grammy Awards in 2009, Adele received the awards for Best New Artist and Best Female Pop Vocal Performance.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f3/Adele_-_Live_2016%2C_Glasgow_SSE_Hydro_03.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adele/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>