<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Music Of Latin America</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Music Of Latin America</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:57:44 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Manolito]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/manu-chao/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Manu Chao is a French-born Spanish musician. He sings in French, Spanish, English, Italian, Arabic, Catalan, Galician, Portuguese, Greek and occasionally in other languages. Chao began his musical career in Paris, busking and playing with groups such as Hot Pants and Los Carayos, which combined a variety of languages and musical styles. With friends and his brother Antoine Chao, he founded the band Mano Negra in 1987, achieving considerable success, particularly in Europe. He became a solo artist after its breakup in 1995, and since then tours regularly with his live band, Radio Bemba.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/35/Manu_Chao_Live_at_Princep_Ghat_02.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/manu-chao/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Willy DeVille]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willy-deville/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Willy DeVille was an American singer and songwriter. During his thirty-five-year career, first with his band Mink DeVille (1974–1986) and later on his own, Deville created original songs rooted in traditional American musical styles. He worked with collaborators from across the spectrum of contemporary music, including Jack Nitzsche, Doc Pomus, Dr. John, Mark Knopfler, Allen Toussaint, and Eddie Bo. Latin rhythms, blues riffs, doo-wop, Cajun music, strains of French cabaret, and echoes of early-1960s uptown soul can be heard in DeVille's work.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/08/2008-02-26_Willy_DeVille_IMG_8267.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willy-deville/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Fernando Olvera]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fernando-olvera/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d9/Man%C3%A1_-_Rock_in_Rio_Madrid_2012_-_06.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fernando-olvera/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Iñigo Muguruza Ugarte]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/iñigo-muguruza-ugarte/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Inigo-muguruza-photo-dani-blanco1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/iñigo-muguruza-ugarte/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Carlos Santana]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/carlos-santana/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Carlos Humberto Santana Barragán audio (help·info) is a Mexican-American guitarist who rose to fame in the late 1960s and early 1970s with his band Santana, which pioneered a fusion of rock 'n' roll and Latin American jazz. Its sound featured his melodic, blues-based lines set against Latin and African rhythms played on percussion instruments not generally heard in rock, such as timbales and congas. He experienced a resurgence of popularity and critical acclaim in the late 1990s. In 2015, Rolling Stone magazine listed him at No. 20 on their list of the 100 greatest guitarists. He has received 10 Grammy Awards and three Latin Grammy Awards, and was inducted along with his namesake band into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/93/Carlos_Santana_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/carlos-santana/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>