<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Beat Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Beat Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 13:38:44 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Buddy Holly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buddy-holly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Charles Hardin Holley, known professionally as Buddy Holly, was an American singer-songwriter who was a central and pioneering figure of mid-1950s rock and roll. He was born in Lubbock, Texas, to a musical family during the Great Depression, and learned to play guitar and sing alongside his siblings. His style was influenced by gospel music, country music, and rhythm and blues acts, which he performed in Lubbock with his friends from high school.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/14/Buddy_Holly_cropped.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buddy-holly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gerry Marsden]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gerry-marsden/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gerard Marsden MBE was an English singer-songwriter, musician and television personality, best known for being leader of the Merseybeat band Gerry and the Pacemakers. He was the younger brother of fellow band member Freddie Marsden.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/89/Gerry_Marsden-bw.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gerry-marsden/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Lennon]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-lennon/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Winston Ono Lennon was an English singer, songwriter, musician and peace activist who achieved worldwide fame as the founder, co-lead vocalist, and rhythm guitarist of the Beatles. His songwriting partnership with Paul McCartney remains the most successful in history. In 1969, he started the Plastic Ono Band with his second wife, Yoko Ono. After the Beatles disbanded in 1970, Lennon continued his career as a solo artist and as Ono's collaborator.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/90/John_Lennon_portrait.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-lennon/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>