<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Nirvana</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Nirvana</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 19:59:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Krist Novoselic]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/krist-novoselic/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Krist Anthony Novoselic (; is an American musician and political activist, best known as the bassist and a founding member of the grunge band Nirvana. Nirvana achieved massive success, earning multiple gold and platinum awards and touring around the world at sold-out shows.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7d/Krist_Novoselic_15A.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/krist-novoselic/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kurt Cobain]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kurt-cobain/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kurt Donald Cobain was an American singer, songwriter, and musician, best known as the guitarist and frontman of the rock band Nirvana. He is remembered as one of the most iconic and influential rock musicians in the history of alternative music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/19/Nirvana_around_1992.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kurt-cobain/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Grohl]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-grohl/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Eric Grohl is an American singer, songwriter, musician and director. He is the founder, lead vocalist, rhythm guitarist and primary songwriter of the rock band Foo Fighters since 1994, and was the best known and longest-serving drummer for Nirvana from late 1990 to early 1994, when Nirvana disbanded following the death of Kurt Cobain. Grohl is also the drummer and co-founder of the rock supergroup Them Crooked Vultures, and wrote the music and performed all the instruments for his short-lived side projects Late! and Probot. He has also recorded and frequently tours with rock band Queens of the Stone Age.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8e/Dave_Grohl_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-grohl/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>