<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Violin</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Violin</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:52:56 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jean-Jacques Goldman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jean-jacques-goldman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jean-Jacques Goldman is a French singer-songwriter and music producer. He is hugely popular in the French-speaking world. Since the death of Johnny Hallyday in 2017 he has been the highest grossing living French pop rock act. Born in Paris and active in the music scene since 1975, he had a highly successful solo career in the 1980s, and was part of the trio Fredericks Goldman Jones, releasing another string of hits in the 1990s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8c/Jean-Jacques_Goldman_-_may_2002.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jean-jacques-goldman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sergey Shnurov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sergey-shnurov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sergey Vladimirovich Shnurov is a Russian musician and songwriter, best known as Shnur, of the ska-punk band Leningrad which he formed in 1997 and was the frontman of till the end of 2008. In December 2008 the group disbanded, Shnur with some of its members forming Rubl.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6f/Sergei_Shnurov.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sergey-shnurov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Neil Young]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Neil Percival Young is a Canadian singer-songwriter. After embarking on a music career in the 1960s, he moved to Los Angeles, where he formed Buffalo Springfield with Stephen Stills, Richie Furay and others. Young had released two solo albums and three as a member of Buffalo Springfield by the time he joined Crosby, Stills & Nash in 1969. From his early solo albums and those with his backing band Crazy Horse, Young has recorded a steady stream of studio and live albums, sometimes warring with his recording company along the way.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bb/Neil_Young_-_Per_Ole_Hagen.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neil-young/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Svetlana Surganova]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/svetlana-surganova/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Svetlana Yakovlevna Surganova is a Russian rock musician, singer and poet. She was a founding member of the popular Russian rock band Nochnye Snaipery, providing vocals and playing violin. Presently she is a founding member of 'Surganova i Orkestr' band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/74/Swetlana_Surganowa.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/svetlana-surganova/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul McCartney]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir James Paul McCartney is an English singer, songwriter, musician, composer, and record and film producer who gained worldwide fame as co-lead vocalist and bassist for the Beatles. His songwriting partnership with John Lennon remains the most successful in history. After the group disbanded in 1970, he pursued a successful solo career and formed the band Wings with his first wife, Linda, and Denny Laine.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d6/Paul_McCartney_in_October_2018.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-mccartney/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joe Dassin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-dassin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Ira Dassin was an American-born French singer-songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c9/Joe_Dassin_1970.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joe-dassin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robbie Williams]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-williams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Peter Williams is an English singer-songwriter and entertainer. He found fame as a member of the pop group Take That from 1989 to 1995, but achieved greater commercial success with his solo career, beginning in 1997. Williams has released seven UK number one singles and ten out of his eleven studio albums have reached number one in the UK. He is the best-selling British solo artist in the United Kingdom and the best selling non-Latino artist in Latin America. Six of his albums are among the top 100 biggest-selling albums in the United Kingdom–four albums in the top 60–and in 2006 he entered the Guinness Book of World Records for selling 1.6 million tickets of his Close Encounters Tour in a single day.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/Robbie_Williams.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-williams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vladimir Kuzmin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vladimir-kuzmin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vladimir Borisovich Kuzmin is a Russian rock singer, guitarist, and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b9/%D0%9A%D1%83%D0%B7%D1%8C%D0%BC%D0%B8%D0%BD-%D0%9A%D0%B0%D0%BC%D0%B5%D0%BD%D1%81%D0%BA_21-10-12_cr.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vladimir-kuzmin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[George Harrison]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-harrison/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>George Harrison was an English musician, singer-songwriter, and music and film producer who achieved international fame as the lead guitarist of the Beatles. Sometimes called 'the quiet Beatle', Harrison embraced Indian culture and helped broaden the scope of popular music through his incorporation of Indian instrumentation and Hindu-aligned spirituality in the Beatles' work. Although the majority of the band's songs were written by John Lennon and Paul McCartney, most Beatles albums from 1965 onwards contained at least two Harrison compositions. His songs for the group included 'Taxman', 'Within You Without You', 'While My Guitar Gently Weeps', 'Here Comes the Sun' and 'Something'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/42/George_Harrison_1974.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-harrison/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 00:45:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>