<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Violin</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Violin</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 00:37:01 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ben Moody]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ben-moody/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Benjamin Robert 'Ben' Moody is an American musician, singer, songwriter, record producer, and actor. He is best known as co-founder, lead guitarist, and co-songwriter of rock band Evanescence from its inception in 1995 to his departure in October 2003. Since leaving Evanescence, Moody has collaborated with an array of performers vocally, instrumentally, and as a writer. He is currently a member of The Halo Method and We Are the Fallen.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5f/Evanescence_2003_barcelona_ben_moody.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ben-moody/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robert Smith]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robert-smith-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert James Smith is an English singer, songwriter, musician, and record producer. He is the lead singer, guitarist, multi-instrumentalist, primary songwriter, and only continuous member of the rock band the Cure, which he co-founded in 1976. He was also the lead guitarist for the band Siouxsie and the Banshees from 1982 to 1984, and was part of the short-lived group the Glove in 1983. He is known for his distinctive voice, guitar-playing style and stage look, the latter two of which were influential on the goth subculture that rose to prominence in the 1980s. Smith was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame as a member of the Cure in 2019.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7a/Robert_Smith_-_The_Cure_-_Roskilde_Festival_2012_-_Orange_Stage_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robert-smith-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tony Sheridan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tony-sheridan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tony Sheridan was an English rock and roll singer-songwriter and guitarist who spent much of his adult life in Germany. He was best known as an early collaborator of the Beatles, one of two non-Beatles to receive label performance credit on a record with the group, and the only non-Beatle to appear as lead singer on a Beatles recording which charted as a single.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/08/TonySheridan.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tony-sheridan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jean-Jacques Goldman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jean-jacques-goldman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jean-Jacques Goldman is a French singer-songwriter and music producer. He is hugely popular in the French-speaking world. Since the death of Johnny Hallyday in 2017 he has been the highest grossing living French pop rock act. Born in Paris and active in the music scene since 1975, he had a highly successful solo career in the 1980s, and was part of the trio Fredericks Goldman Jones, releasing another string of hits in the 1990s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8c/Jean-Jacques_Goldman_-_may_2002.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jean-jacques-goldman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Damon Albarn]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/damon-albarn/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Damon Albarn is an English musician, singer, songwriter, and record producer, best known as the lead singer of the rock band Blur and as the co-founder, lead vocalist, instrumentalist, and principal songwriter of the virtual band Gorillaz.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1a/Damon_Albarn_mg_6633.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/damon-albarn/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Les Paul]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/les-paul/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lester William Polsfuss, known as Les Paul, was an American jazz, country, and blues guitarist, songwriter, luthier, and inventor. He was one of the pioneers of the solid-body electric guitar, and his techniques served as inspiration for the Gibson Les Paul. Paul taught himself how to play guitar, and while he is mainly known for jazz and popular music, he had an early career in country music. He is credited with many recording innovations. Although he was not the first to use the technique, his early experiments with overdubbing, delay effects such as tape delay, phasing effects and multitrack recording were among the first to attract widespread attention.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/80/Les_Paul_live_3.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/les-paul/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joan Wasser]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joan-as-police-woman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Joan Wasser, known by her stage name Joan As Police Woman, is an American musician, singer-songwriter and producer. She began her career playing violin with the Dambuilders and played with Black Beetle, Antony and the Johnsons, and Those Bastard Souls. Since 2004 she has released her solo material as Joan As Police Woman. She has released five regular studio albums, one EP, a number of singles and a collection of covers. Throughout her career, she has regularly collaborated with other artists as a writer, performer and arranger.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/91/Joan_As_Police_Woman_%285436379667%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joan-as-police-woman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sergey Shnurov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sergey-shnurov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sergey Vladimirovich Shnurov is a Russian musician and songwriter, best known as Shnur, of the ska-punk band Leningrad which he formed in 1997 and was the frontman of till the end of 2008. In December 2008 the group disbanded, Shnur with some of its members forming Rubl.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6f/Sergei_Shnurov.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sergey-shnurov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tracy Bonham]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tracy-bonham/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tracy Bonham is an American alternative rock musician, best known for her 1996 single 'Mother Mother'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a4/Tracy_Bonham.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tracy-bonham/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>