<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Indie Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Indie Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:04:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Cat Power]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/cat-power/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Charlyn Marie  'Chan' Marshall, better known by her stage name Cat Power, is an American singer-songwriter, musician, occasional actress, and model. Cat Power was originally the name of Marshall's first band, but has become her stage name as a solo artist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/Cat_Power_%28Victoria%2C_London%29_2018.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/cat-power/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kevin Devine]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kevin-devine/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kevin Devine is an American songwriter and musician from Staten Island, New York, who is known for his introspective and political themes. He is a contemporary member of the underground indie rock and indie folk musical scenes, and his influences range from older indie artists such as Neutral Milk Hotel, Elliott Smith and Pavement to more mainstream and well known acts such as Nirvana and Bob Dylan. In 2013, Kevin Devine rejoined his previous band, Miracle of 86, for a series of reunion shows.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/53/KevinDevine2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kevin-devine/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Beatie Wolfe]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/beatie-wolfe/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Beatie Wolfe is an Anglo-American singer-songwriter, described as 'a pioneering songwriter' known for 'seeing music differently' and creating new tangible formats for music, which include the 'World's First 3D Interactive Album App' for her debut album 8ight, a musical jacket for her second album Montagu Square and the world's first live 360 AR stream for her third album Raw Space. These musical innovations have gained Wolfe critical acclaim with Highsnobiety naming Wolfe as one of '10 Ways Music Will Change in 2017' and Wired (magazine) featuring Wolfe as one of 22 changing the world.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b0/Beatie_Wolfe_portrait.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/beatie-wolfe/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gustavo Cerati]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gustavo-cerati/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gustavo Adrián Cerati was an Argentine singer-songwriter, composer and producer, considered one of the most important and influential figures of Ibero-American rock. Cerati along with his band Soda Stereo, were one of the most popular and influential Spanish-language rock and pop groups of the 1980s and '90s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c8/Concierto_Gustavo_Cerati_%284120623383%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gustavo-cerati/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nilüfer Yanya]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nilüfer-yanya/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nilüfer Yanya is an English singer, songwriter, composer and musician.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/68/Turning_Tides_Festival_Gruf_Rhys_and_Nilufer_Yanya_%2848292221827%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nilüfer-yanya/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Yulia Chicherina]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yulia-chicherina/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Chicherina, officially Yulia Dmitrievna Chicherina, is a Russian pop-rock artist. She has been performing since 1997 and is part of the wave of Uralic rock along with Nautilus Pompilius and Chaif.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9d/Chicherina2012.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yulia-chicherina/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Neko Case]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neko-case/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Neko Richelle Case is an American singer-songwriter, best known for her solo career and her contributions as a member of the Canadian indie rock group the New Pornographers.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/61/Neko_Case_at_All_Points_West_%28edit%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/neko-case/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Albert Hammond, Jr.]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/albert-hammond-jr./]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Albert Hammond Jr. is an American guitarist, singer, songwriter and music producer. He is most famous for his role as rhythm and lead guitarist, as well as occasional keyboard player and backing vocalist, in the American rock band The Strokes. He is the son of singer-songwriter Albert Hammond. Hammond Jr. released his debut album Yours To Keep in 2006 and followed up with ¿Cómo Te Llama? in 2008, an EP, AHJ, in 2013, and a third album, Momentary Masters, released in 2015. He released his fourth solo album, Francis Trouble, through Red Bull Records on March 9, 2018.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/69/Domskibum2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/albert-hammond-jr./]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>