<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Bluegrass Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Bluegrass Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2019 01:44:48 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Victor Wooten]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/victor-wooten/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Victor Lemonte Wooten is an American bass guitarist, record producer, educator, and recipient of five Grammy Awards. He has been the bassist for Béla Fleck and the Flecktones since the group's formation in 1988 and a member of the band SMV with two other bassists, Stanley Clarke and Marcus Miller. Since 2017 he has played bass for the metal band Nitro.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5c/Victor_Wooten_Cosmopolite_2018_%28213614%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/victor-wooten/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jerry Garcia]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jerry-garcia/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jerome John 'Jerry' Garcia was an American singer-songwriter and guitarist, best known for his work as the lead guitarist and as a vocalist with the band the Grateful Dead, which came to prominence during the counterculture era in the 1960s. Although he disavowed the role, Garcia was viewed by many as the leader or 'spokesman' of the group.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e8/Grateful_Dead_-_Jerry_Garcia.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jerry-garcia/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Thile]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-thile/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher Scott Thile is an American mandolinist, singer, songwriter, composer, and radio personality, best known for his work in the progressive acoustic trio Nickel Creek and the acoustic folk and progressive bluegrass quintet Punch Brothers. He is a 2012 MacArthur Fellow. In October 2016, he became the host of the radio variety show A Prairie Home Companion, which in December 2017 was renamed Live from Here.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bc/Christhile.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-thile/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Hartford]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-hartford/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Cowan Hartford was an American folk, country, and bluegrass composer and musician known for his mastery of the fiddle and banjo, as well as for his witty lyrics, unique vocal style, and extensive knowledge of Mississippi River lore. His most successful song is 'Gentle on My Mind', which won three Grammy Awards and was listed in 'BMI's Top 100 Songs of the Century'. Hartford performed with a variety of ensembles throughout his career, and is perhaps best known for his solo performances where he would interchange the guitar, banjo, and fiddle from song to song. He also invented his own shuffle tap dance move, and clogged on an amplified piece of plywood while he played and sang.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bc/Image-John_Hartford_playing_at_Merlefest%2C_North_Carolina_%282000%29-fls.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-hartford/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sam Bush]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sam-bush/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Charles Samuel Bush is an American mandolinist who is considered an originator of progressive bluegrass music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/33/Sam_Bush_%282006%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sam-bush/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vince Gill]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vince-gill/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Vincent Grant Gill is an American country singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. He has achieved commercial success and fame both as frontman to the country rock band Pure Prairie League in the 1970s and as a solo artist beginning in 1983, where his talents as a vocalist and musician have placed him in high demand as a guest vocalist and a duet partner.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9c/VinceGillCrossroads2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/vince-gill/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alison Brown]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alison-brown/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Alison Brown is an American banjo player, guitarist, composer, and producer. She has won and has been nominated for several Grammy awards and is often compared to another banjo prodigy, Béla Fleck, for her unique style of playing. In her music, she blends jazz, bluegrass, rock, blues as well as other styles of music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/58/Alison-brown-fls.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alison-brown/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Butler]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-butler/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Charles Wiltshire-Butler, professionally known as John Butler, is an American-born Australian singer, songwriter, and music producer. He is the front man for the John Butler Trio, a roots and jam band, that formed in Fremantle, Western Australia in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/80/John_Butler_Cambridge.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-butler/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Emmylou Harris]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emmylou-harris/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Emmylou Harris is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. She has released dozens of albums and singles over the course of her career and won 14 Grammys, the Polar Music Prize, and numerous other honors, including induction into the Country Music Hall of Fame. In 2018 she was presented the Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/55/Emmylou_Harris_with_guitar.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emmylou-harris/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Doc Watson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/doc-watson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Arthel Lane 'Doc' Watson was an American guitarist, songwriter, and singer of bluegrass, folk, country, blues, and gospel music. Watson won seven Grammy awards as well as a Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award. Watson's fingerstyle guitar and flatpicking skills, as well as his knowledge of traditional American music, were highly regarded. He performed with his son, guitarist Merle Watson, for over 15 years until Merle's death in 1985 in an accident on the family farm.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/ba/Doc_Watson_Sugar_Grove.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/doc-watson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>