<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Britpop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Britpop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 22:33:50 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ilya Lagutenko]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ilya-lagutenko/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/23/Ilya_Lagutenko_%40_Park_Live_%28cropped%29.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ilya-lagutenko/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Richard Ashcroft]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-ashcroft/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Paul Ashcroft is an English singer and songwriter. He was the lead singer and occasional rhythm guitarist of the alternative rock band The Verve from their formation in 1990 until their original split in 1999. Songs he wrote for the band include 'Bitter Sweet Symphony', 'Lucky Man', and the UK number one 'The Drugs Don't Work'. He became a successful solo artist, releasing three UK top three solo albums. The Verve reformed in 2007 but again broke up by summer 2009. Ashcroft then founded a new band, RPA & The United Nations of Sound, and released a new album on 19 July 2010. Ashcroft released his fourth solo album, These People, on 20 May 2016.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/68/Richardashcroft.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-ashcroft/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Damon Albarn]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/damon-albarn/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Damon Albarn is an English musician, singer, songwriter, and record producer, best known as the frontman and primary lyricist of the rock band Blur and as the co-founder, lead vocalist, instrumentalist, and primary songwriter of the virtual band Gorillaz.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1a/Damon_Albarn_mg_6633.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/damon-albarn/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Harry Styles]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/harry-styles/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Harry Edward Styles is an English singer, songwriter, and actor. His musical career began in 2010 as a solo contestant on the British music competition series The X Factor. Following his elimination early on, he was brought back to join the boy band One Direction, which went on to become one of the best-selling boy bands of all time.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9e/Harry_Styles_November_2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/harry-styles/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alex James]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alex-james/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steven Alexander James, FRSA is an English musician and songwriter, as well as a journalist and cheesemaker. Best known as the bassist of the band Blur, he has also played with temporary bands Fat Les, Me Me Me, WigWam and Bad Lieutenant.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d0/Alex_James_2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alex-james/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robbie Williams]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-williams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Peter Williams is an English singer-songwriter and entertainer. He found fame as a member of the pop group Take That from 1990 to 1995, but achieved greater commercial success with his solo career, beginning in 1996. Williams has released seven UK number one singles and eleven out of his twelve studio albums have reached number one in the UK. Six of his albums are among the top 100 biggest-selling albums in the United Kingdom–four albums in the top 60–and in 2006 he entered the Guinness Book of World Records for selling 1.6 million tickets of his Close Encounters Tour in a single day.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/Robbie_Williams.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-williams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brett Anderson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brett-anderson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brett Lewis Anderson is an English singer-songwriter best known as the lead vocalist and primary lyricist of the band Suede. After Suede disbanded in 2003, he briefly fronted The Tears in 2004, and released four solo albums in which he also played guitar and keyboards. Anderson is known for his distinctive wide-ranging voice, poetic lyrics, energetic and charismatic stage presence and, during Suede's early days, an androgynous appearance. Suede reformed in 2010 and continue to record and tour. Along with bassist Mat Osman, Anderson is the remaining original members since the band's inception.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/98/BrettAndersonPark.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brett-anderson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:36 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>