<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Britpop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Britpop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:48:48 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brett Anderson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brett-anderson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brett Lewis Anderson is an English singer-songwriter best known as the lead vocalist and primary lyricist of the band Suede. After Suede disbanded in 2003, he briefly fronted The Tears in 2004, and has released four solo albums. Anderson is known for his distinctive wide-ranging voice and, during Suede's early days, an androgynous appearance. Suede reformed in 2010.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/98/BrettAndersonPark.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brett-anderson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ilya Lagutenko]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ilya-lagutenko/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ilya Igorevich Lagutenko is the founder and lead singer of MTV Award-winning band Mumiy Troll.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e8/%D0%98%D0%BB%D1%8C%D1%8F_%D0%9B%D0%B0%D0%B3%D1%83%D1%82%D0%B5%D0%BD%D0%BA%D0%BE_2016_2_%281%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ilya-lagutenko/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Alex James]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alex-james/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steven Alexander James, FRSA is an English musician and songwriter, as well as a journalist and cheesemaker. Best known as the bassist of the band Blur, he has also played with temporary bands Fat Les, Me Me Me, WigWam and Bad Lieutenant.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d0/Alex_James_2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/alex-james/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Harry Styles]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/harry-styles/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Harry Edward Styles is an English singer, songwriter, and actor. His musical career began in 2010 when he auditioned for the British singing competition The X Factor. He was eliminated early on, but was brought back to form the boy band One Direction. The band finished in third place and signed with Syco. They earned four number-one studio albums on the Billboard 200, and earned four top-five singles on the Billboard Hot 100. They embarked on four world tours and won a number of accolades. The band went on an indefinite hiatus in 2016.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9e/Harry_Styles_November_2014.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/harry-styles/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Yulia Chicherina]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yulia-chicherina/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Chicherina, officially Yulia Dmitrievna Chicherina, is a Russian pop-rock artist. She has been performing since 1997 and is part of the wave of Uralic rock along with Nautilus Pompilius and Chaif.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9d/Chicherina2012.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yulia-chicherina/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Robbie Williams]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-williams/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Peter Williams is an English singer-songwriter and entertainer. He found fame as a member of the pop group Take That from 1989 to 1995, but achieved greater commercial success with his solo career, beginning in 1997. Williams has released seven UK number one singles and ten out of his eleven studio albums have reached number one in the UK. He is the best-selling British solo artist in the United Kingdom and the best selling non-Latino artist in Latin America. Six of his albums are among the top 100 biggest-selling albums in the United Kingdom–four albums in the top 60–and in 2006 he entered the Guinness Book of World Records for selling 1.6 million tickets of his Close Encounters Tour in a single day.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/Robbie_Williams.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/robbie-williams/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>