<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Ben Granfelt Band</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Ben Granfelt Band</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 23:39:00 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lauri Porra]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lauri-porra/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lauri Porra is a Finnish bassist and composer, also known for his work in Stratovarius. Lauri Porra is a fourth generation musician, and the great-grandson of famous Finnish composer Jean Sibelius. He started to study music at age 6 when he started to play cello in a local music school. In 1993 he switched to bass guitar and continued his studies in the Helsinki Pop Jazz Conservatory (1994–2004). Additionally he has taken lessons on piano, double bass, trumpet and male vocals. During 1997-1999 he sang with the renowned YL male choir performing for instance with the London Symphony Orchestra. He has released four instrumental solo albums with the latest, ‘Entropia’, released in January 2018 on BIS-records. He has also composed music to movies, tv and media. In 2016 Lauri received Nordisk Popularauktors NPU-award and was nominated for HARPA Nordic film composer music award. Lauri´s own band Lauri Porra Flyover Ensemble has performed Lauri´s music on tours and various festivals. Lauri´s orchestral music has been performed by Finnish Radio Orchestra, Trondheim Symphony Orchestra, Lahti Symphony Orchestra and many others. Lauri is artistic partner of Vantaa Pops orchestra and artistic advisor of the Helsinki Festival.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/44/Lauri_Porra.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lauri-porra/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>