<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Folk Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Folk Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 23:20:45 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Petri Lindroos]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/petri-lindroos/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Petri Lindroos is a melodic death/folk metal guitarist and vocalist. He is currently the lead vocalist in Ensiferum and, prior to this, was a founder and lead vocalist for Norther.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/77/Petri_Lindroos.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/petri-lindroos/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Fenriz]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fenriz/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gylve Fenris Nagell, better known as Fenriz, is a Norwegian musician and politician who is best known as being one half of the metal duo Darkthrone, alongside Nocturno Culto. Although primarily a drummer, he has also performed bass, guitar, and vocals for Darkthrone and a number of other metal bands. Fenriz is known for his encyclopedic knowledge of many different forms of music, his eager support of other underground bands, and his lack of interest in the mainstream music business in general. Fenriz has had multiple solo projects, including the folk black metal project Isengard, the dark ambient project Neptune Towers and the doom metal project Valhall.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/67/Fenriz.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/fenriz/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ihsahn]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ihsahn/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ihsahn is a Norwegian composer, multi-instrumentalist, and vocalist. He is best known for his work with the Norwegian black metal band Emperor. Tveitan is also a founding member of Thou Shalt Suffer, where he played guitar and keyboard in addition to vocal duties, and Peccatum, a project in collaboration with his wife and fellow musician Heidi Solberg Tveitan, also known as Starofash. Since 2006, Tveitan has primarily devoted himself to solo albums and occasional guest appearances.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8e/Ihsahn_live.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ihsahn/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sigurd Wongraven]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sigurd-wongraven/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Satyr is the vocalist, lead and rhythm guitarist, bassist, and keyboardist for the Norwegian black metal band Satyricon.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4e/Satyricon_%40_Elbriot_2018_15.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sigurd-wongraven/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jari Mäenpää]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jari-mäenpää/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jari Mäenpää is a Finnish heavy metal multi-instrumentalist and songwriter. He is the founder of Wintersun for which he records all instruments. Before forming Wintersun, Mäenpää was best known for his role in the folk metal band Ensiferum, which he joined in 1996 after leaving his prior band named Immemorial. Wintersun was initially planned as a parallel project alongside Ensiferum, but in January, 2004 he was forced to leave Ensiferum due to clashes between their touring schedule and the studio recording time he had booked for Wintersun.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5a/Jari_M%C3%A4enp%C3%A4%C3%A4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jari-mäenpää/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>