<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Drum</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Drum</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:03:07 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brendon Urie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brendon-urie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brendon Boyd Urie is an American singer, songwriter, and musician, best known as the lead vocalist of Panic! at the Disco, of which he is the only member remaining.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fb/Panic_at_the_Disco_Im_Park_2016_%2811_von_11%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brendon-urie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Trent Reznor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Trent Reznor is an American singer, songwriter, musician, record producer, and film score composer. He is the founder, lead vocalist, and principal songwriter of the industrial rock band Nine Inch Nails, which he founded in 1988 and of which he was the sole official member until adding long-time collaborator Atticus Ross as a permanent member in 2016. His first release under the Nine Inch Nails name, the 1989 album Pretty Hate Machine, was a commercial and critical success. He has since released nine Nine Inch Nails studio albums. He left Interscope Records in 2007 and was an independent recording artist until signing with Columbia Records in 2012.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d5/Trent_Reznor-FEB2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ringo Starr]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ringo-starr/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Sir Richard Starkey, known professionally as Ringo Starr, is an English musician, singer, songwriter and actor who gained worldwide fame as the drummer for the Beatles. He occasionally sang lead vocals with the group, usually for one song on each album, including 'With a Little Help from My Friends', 'Yellow Submarine', 'Good Night', 'Boys', and their cover of 'Act Naturally'. He also wrote and sang the Beatles' songs 'Don't Pass Me By' and 'Octopus's Garden', and is credited as a co-writer of others, including 'What Goes On'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Ringo_Starr_and_all_his_band_%288470866906%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ringo-starr/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stuart Braithwaite]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stuart-braithwaite/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stuart Leslie Braithwaite is a Scottish multi-instrumentalist, singer and songwriter. He is the guitarist of post rock band Mogwai, with whom he has recorded nine studio albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/00/Stuart_braithwaite.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stuart-braithwaite/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Justin Bieber]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/justin-bieber/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Justin Drew Bieber is a Canadian singer-songwriter and actor. Encountered at 13 years old by talent manager Scooter Braun after he had watched the boy's YouTube cover song videos, Bieber was signed to RBMG Records in 2008. Bieber released his debut EP, My World, in late 2009. It was certified Platinum in the United States. With the EP, Bieber became the first artist to have seven songs from a debut record chart on the Billboard Hot 100.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/Justin_Bieber_in_2015.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/justin-bieber/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Luca Hänni]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/luca-hänni/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Luca Hänni is a Swiss singer, songwriter, dancer, model and television personality. He rose to fame in 2012 after winning the ninth season of Deutschland sucht den Superstar, the German version of the Idol franchise. He was the first non-German to do so and also the youngest ever winner of the show. Hänni's debut single, 'Don't Think About Me', topped the singles charts in Austria, Germany, and Switzerland. It was followed by the release of his debut album, My Name Is Luca (2012), which debuted atop the Austrian and Swiss Albums Charts and became a gold-seller in both countries. His second studio album, Living the Dream, released in 2013, became his second consecutive number-one album in Switzerland.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/01/2018-05-13_ZDF_Fernsehgarten_Luca_H%C3%A4nni-7826.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/luca-hänni/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Conor Oberst]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/conor-oberst/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Conor Mullen Oberst is an American singer-songwriter best known for his work in Bright Eyes. He has also played in several other bands, including Desaparecidos, The Faint, Commander Venus, Park Ave., Conor Oberst and the Mystic Valley Band, Monsters of Folk, and Better Oblivion Community Center. Oberst was named the Best Songwriter of 2008 by Rolling Stone magazine.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6e/Flickr_-_moses_namkung_-_Conor_Oberst_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/conor-oberst/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dan Hicks]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dan-hicks-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Daniel Ivan Hicks was an American singer-songwriter known for an idiosyncratic style that combined elements of cowboy folk, jazz, country, swing, bluegrass, pop, and gypsy music. He led Dan Hicks and His Hot Licks. He is perhaps best known for the songs 'I Scare Myself' and 'Canned Music.' His songs are frequently infused with humor, as evidenced by the title of his tune, 'How Can I Miss You When You Won't Go Away?' His album, Live at Davies (2013), capped over forty years of music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a3/DanHicks2009.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dan-hicks-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nikolai Noskov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nikolai-noskov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nikolai Ivanovich Noskov is a Russian singer and former vocalist of the hard rock band Gorky Park. Five-time winner of the Golden Gramophone. He was also a member of Москва (Moscow) ensemble in the early 1980s, in band Гран-при in 1988 just before joining Gorky Park, and much later in the 1990s in band Николай (Nikolai). Starting 1998 Noskov had a solo career releasing six solo albums. In 2015 he was jury in second season of reality TV series Glavnaya Stsena</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/32/%D0%9D%D0%B8%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%BB%D0%B0%D0%B9_%D0%9D%D0%BE%D1%81%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%B2_%D0%B2_2009_%284%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nikolai-noskov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shahram Shabpareh]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shahram-shabpareh/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shahram Shabpareh is an Iranian Pop singer and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0e/Shahramshabpare.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shahram-shabpareh/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>