<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Drum</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Drum</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:57:44 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stuart Braithwaite]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stuart-braithwaite/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stuart Leslie Braithwaite is a Scottish multi-instrumentalist, singer and songwriter. He is the guitarist of post rock band Mogwai, with whom he has recorded ten studio albums. He is also a member of the British alternative rock supergroup 'Minor Victories.'</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/00/Stuart_braithwaite.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stuart-braithwaite/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Conor Oberst]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/conor-oberst/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Conor Mullen Oberst is an American singer-songwriter best known for his work in Bright Eyes. He has also played in several other bands, including Desaparecidos, The Faint, Commander Venus, Park Ave., Conor Oberst and the Mystic Valley Band, Monsters of Folk, and Better Oblivion Community Center. Oberst was named the Best Songwriter of 2008 by Rolling Stone magazine.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6e/Flickr_-_moses_namkung_-_Conor_Oberst_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/conor-oberst/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Justin Bieber]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/justin-bieber/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Justin Drew Bieber is a Canadian singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. Discovered at age 13 by talent manager Scooter Braun after he had watched his YouTube cover song videos, Bieber was signed to RBMG Records in 2008. With Bieber's debut EP My World, released in late 2009, Bieber became the first artist to have seven songs from a debut record chart on the Billboard Hot 100.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/Justin_Bieber_in_2015.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/justin-bieber/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ellie Goulding]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ellie-goulding/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Elena Jane Goulding is an English singer and songwriter. Her career began when she met record producers Starsmith and Frankmusik, and she was later spotted by Jamie Lillywhite, who later became her manager and A&R. After signing to Polydor Records in July 2009, Goulding released her debut extended play, An Introduction to Ellie Goulding later that year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/71/Goulding%2C_Staples_Center%2C_Los_Angeles%2C_8th_April_2016_%2843%29-cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ellie-goulding/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dan Hicks]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dan-hicks-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Daniel Ivan Hicks was an American singer-songwriter known for an idiosyncratic style that combined elements of cowboy folk, jazz, country, swing, bluegrass, pop, and gypsy music. He led ″Dan Hicks and His Hot Licks″. He is perhaps best known for the songs 'I Scare Myself' and 'Canned Music.' His songs are frequently infused with humor, as evidenced by the title of his tune, 'How Can I Miss You When You Won't Go Away?' His album, Live at Davies (2013), capped over forty years of music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a3/DanHicks2009.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dan-hicks-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hank Williams Jr.]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hank-williams-jr./]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Randall Hank Williams, known professionally as Hank Williams Jr. or Bocephus, is an American singer-songwriter and musician. His musical style is often considered a blend of Southern rock, blues, and country. He is the son of country music legend Hank Williams.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6b/Hank_Williams%2C_Jr._%282006%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/hank-williams-jr./]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brendon Urie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brendon-urie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brendon Boyd Urie is an American singer, songwriter, and musician, best known as the lead vocalist of Panic! at the Disco, of which he is the only original member remaining.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fb/Panic_at_the_Disco_Im_Park_2016_%2811_von_11%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brendon-urie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Luca Hänni]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/luca-hänni/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Luca Hänni is a Swiss singer, songwriter, dancer, model and television personality. He rose to fame in 2012 after winning the ninth season of Deutschland sucht den Superstar, the German version of the Idol franchise. He was the first non-German to do so and also the youngest ever winner of the show. Hänni's debut single, 'Don't Think About Me', topped the singles charts in Austria, Germany, and Switzerland. It was followed by the release of his debut album, My Name Is Luca (2012), which debuted atop the Austrian and Swiss Albums Charts and became a gold-seller in both countries. His second studio album, Living the Dream, released in 2013, became his second consecutive number-one album in Switzerland.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/01/2018-05-13_ZDF_Fernsehgarten_Luca_H%C3%A4nni-7826.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/luca-hänni/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Trent Reznor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Trent Reznor is an American musician, singer, songwriter, record producer, and composer. He serves as the lead vocalist, multi-instrumentalist, and principal songwriter of the industrial rock band Nine Inch Nails, which he founded in 1988 and of which he was the sole official member until 2016. The first Nine Inch Nails album, Pretty Hate Machine (1989), was a commercial and critical success. Reznor has since released 11 more Nine Inch Nails studio albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c9/Trent_Reznor-FEB2008_%28cropped%2C_but_higher_quality%29_%282%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shahram Shabpareh]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shahram-shabpareh/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shahram Shabpareh is an Iranian Pop singer and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0e/Shahramshabpare.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shahram-shabpareh/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 12:40:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>