<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Ambient Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Ambient Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 21:22:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adrian Legg]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adrian-legg/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/81/Adrian_legg.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adrian-legg/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Bowie]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-bowie/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Robert Jones OAL, known professionally as David Bowie, was an English singer-songwriter and actor. A leading figure in the music industry, Bowie is regarded as one of the most influential musicians of the 20th century. He was acclaimed by critics and musicians, particularly for his innovative work during the 1970s. His career was marked by reinvention and visual presentation, with his music and stagecraft having a significant impact on popular music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e8/David-Bowie_Chicago_2002-08-08_photoby_Adam-Bielawski-cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-bowie/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Devin Townsend]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/devin-townsend/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Devin Garrett Townsend is a Canadian singer, songwriter, musician, and record producer. He founded extreme metal band Strapping Young Lad and was its primary songwriter, vocalist, and guitarist from 1994 to 2007. He has also had an extensive solo career and has released a total of 25 albums across all of his projects as of 2020.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e1/Devin_Townsend_Project_%E2%80%93_Wacken_Open_Air_2014_03.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/devin-townsend/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Daniel Lanois]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daniel-lanois/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Daniel Roland Lanois is a Canadian record producer, guitarist, vocalist, and songwriter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fe/DanielLanois_7878.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/daniel-lanois/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Helge Sten]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/helge-sten/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a8/Helge_Sten_Kongsberg_Jazzfestival_2019_%28194335%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/helge-sten/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jónsi]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jónsi/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jón Þór 'Jónsi' Birgisson is an Icelandic musician; he is the vocalist and multi-instrumentalist for the Icelandic post-rock band Sigur Rós. He is known for his use of a cello bow on guitar and his 'angelic' falsetto or countertenor voice. He is blind in his right eye from birth as a result of a broken optic nerve from the brain. Apart from Sigur Rós, Jónsi also performs together with his ex-partner Alex Somers as an art collaboration called Jónsi & Alex. They released their self-titled first book in November 2006, which was an embossed hardcover limited to 1,000 copies. The two also released the album Riceboy Sleeps, in July 2009. They announced their separation in 2019, after having been together for 16 years.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6d/J%C3%B3n_%C3%9E%C3%B3r_Birgisson_at_the_Roskilde_Festival_in_2006.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jónsi/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Erik Wøllo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/erik-wøllo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Erik Wøllo is a Norwegian composer and musician, guitarist and synthesist. He has a background in various genres in music. As a solo recording artist, he is most known for his electronic and ambient musical soundscapes. Music that can be classified in the genres of space, drone, new age, and electronic music. Through his many albums he has gained recognition for his unique sound and style. Using guitar as the primary instrument in a highly imaginary and emotional music, building a bridge between grand symphonic realms and gentle, minimalistic and serene atmospheres.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/12/Schallwelle_2012_Img07_-_Erik_Wollo_01.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/erik-wøllo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[RY X]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ry-x/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ry Cuming, better known by his stage name RY X, is an Australian singer-songwriter and musician. He was the first artist signed to the Stockholm-based label Dumont Dumont.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/03/Ry_X.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ry-x/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Trent Reznor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Trent Reznor is an American musician, singer, songwriter, record producer, and composer. He serves as the lead vocalist, multi-instrumentalist, and principal songwriter of the industrial rock band Nine Inch Nails, which he founded in 1988 and of which he was the sole official member until 2016. The first Nine Inch Nails album, Pretty Hate Machine (1989), was a commercial and critical success. Reznor has since released 11 more Nine Inch Nails studio albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c9/Trent_Reznor-FEB2008_%28cropped%2C_but_higher_quality%29_%282%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/trent-reznor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:37 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Oldfield]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-oldfield/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Gordon Oldfield is a British musician, multi-instrumentalist and songwriter best known for his debut studio album Tubular Bells (1973), which became an unexpected critical and commercial success and propelled him to worldwide fame. Though primarily a guitarist, Oldfield is known for playing a range of instruments, which includes keyboards and percussion, and doing vocals. He has adopted a range of musical styles throughout his career, including progressive rock, world, folk, classical, electronic, ambient, and new age music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/87/Mike_Oldfield_NOTP_2006.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-oldfield/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:37 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>