<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Noise Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Noise Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 19:23:24 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Yegor Letov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yegor-letov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Igor Fedorovich 'Yegor' Letov was a Russian poet, musician, singer-songwriter, audio engineer and conceptual art painter, best known as the founder and leader of the post-punk/psychedelic rock band Grazhdanskaya Oborona. He was also the founder of the conceptual art avant-garde project Kommunizm and psychedelic rock outfit Egor i Opizdenevshie. Letov collaborated with singer-songwriter Yanka Dyagileva and other Siberian underground artists as a record engineer and producer.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2e/Egor_Letov_2000-11-04_Nuernberg.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yegor-letov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lou Reed]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lou-reed/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lewis Allan Reed was an American musician, singer, songwriter and poet. He was the lead guitarist, singer and principal songwriter for the rock band the Velvet Underground and had a solo career that spanned five decades. The Velvet Underground was not a commercial success during its existence, but became regarded as one of the most influential bands in the history of underground and alternative rock music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c9/Lou_Reed_Malaga%2C_Spain_1.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lou-reed/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Lydon]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-lydon/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Joseph Lydon, also known by his stage name Johnny Rotten, is an English singer, songwriter and musician. He is best known as the lead singer of the late-1970s British punk band the Sex Pistols, which lasted from 1975 until 1978, and again for various revivals during the 1990s and 2000s. He is also the lead singer of post-punk band Public Image Ltd (PiL), which he founded and fronted from 1978 until 1993, and again since 2009. Since 2013, Lydon has held British, Irish and American citizenship.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6d/John_Lydon%2C_Primavera_Sound_Festival_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-lydon/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Buckethead]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Brian Patrick Carroll, known professionally as Buckethead, is an American multi-instrumental musician who has received critical acclaim for his innovative electric guitar playing. His music spans many genres, including progressive metal, funk, blues, bluegrass, ambient, and avant-garde music. He performs primarily as a solo artist, though he has collaborated extensively with a wide variety of high-profile artists such as Bill Laswell, Bootsy Collins, Bernie Worrell, Iggy Pop, Les Claypool, Serj Tankian, Bill Moseley, Mike Patton, Viggo Mortensen, That 1 Guy, Bassnectar, and was a member of Guns N' Roses from 2000 to 2004. He has released 306 studio albums, four special releases, and one EP. He has also performed on more than 50 other albums by other artists.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Neumos_seattle_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/buckethead/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Thurston Moore]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/thurston-moore/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thurston Joseph Moore is an American musician best known as a member of Sonic Youth. He has also participated in many solo and group collaborations outside Sonic Youth, as well as running the Ecstatic Peace! record label. Moore was ranked 34th in Rolling Stone's 2004 edition of the '100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time.' In May 2012, Spin published a staff-selected list of the top 100 rock guitarists, and ranked Moore and his Sonic Youth bandmate Lee Ranaldo together at number 1.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f9/Thurston_Moore_at_the_Brooklyn_Book_Festival.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/thurston-moore/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>