<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » World Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » World Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 23:18:55 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Asha Bhosle]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/asha-bhosle/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Asha Bhosle(née Mangeshkar; born 8 September 1933) is an Indian playback singer and entrepreneur. She is best known for her playback singing in Hindi cinema, although she has a wider repertoire. Bhosle's career started in 1943 and has spanned over seven decades. She has done playback singing for over a thousand movies. In addition, she has recorded several private albums and participated in numerous solo concerts in India and abroad. In 2006, Asha Bhosle stated that she had sung over 12,000 songs, a figure repeated by several other sources. In 2011, she was officially acknowledged by the Guinness Book of World Records as the most recorded artist in music history. The Government of India honoured her with the Dadasaheb Phalke Award in 2000 and the Padma Vibhushan in 2008. Bhosle is the sister of playback singer Lata Mangeshkar and belongs to the prominent Mangeshkar family.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7a/Asha_Bhosle_-_still_47160_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/asha-bhosle/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Manolito]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/manu-chao/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Manu Chao is a French-born Spanish musician. He sings in French, Spanish, English, Italian, Arabic, Catalan, Galician, Portuguese, Greek and occasionally in other languages. Chao began his musical career in Paris, busking and playing with groups such as Hot Pants and Los Carayos, which combined a variety of languages and musical styles. With friends and his brother Antoine Chao, he founded the band Mano Negra in 1987, achieving considerable success, particularly in Europe. He became a solo artist after its breakup in 1995, and since then tours regularly with his live band, Radio Bemba.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/35/Manu_Chao_Live_at_Princep_Ghat_02.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/manu-chao/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Stanley Jordan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stanley-jordan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stanley Jordan is an American jazz guitarist noted for his playing technique, which involves tapping his fingers on the fretboard of the guitar with both hands.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8e/Stanley_Jordan.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/stanley-jordan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jesse Cook]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jesse-cook/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jesse Arnaud Cook is a Canadian guitarist. He is a Juno Award winner, Acoustic Guitar Player's Choice Award silver winner in the Flamenco Category, and a three-time winner of the Canadian Smooth Jazz award for Guitarist of the Year. He has recorded on the EMI, E1 Music and Narada labels and has sold over 1.5 million records worldwide.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2a/Jesse_Cook_143_cropped.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jesse-cook/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Emmylou Harris]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emmylou-harris/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Emmylou Harris is an American singer, songwriter, and musician. She has released dozens of albums and singles over the course of her career and has won 14 Grammys, the Polar Music Prize, and numerous other honors, including induction into the Country Music Hall of Fame. In 2018, she was presented the Grammy Lifetime Achievement Award.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/55/Emmylou_Harris_with_guitar.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/emmylou-harris/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shakira]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shakira Isabel Mebarak Ripoll is a Colombian singer and songwriter. Born and raised in Barranquilla, Shakira has been referred to as the Queen of Latin Music and is noted for her versatility in music. She made her recording debut under Sony Music Colombia at the age of 13. Following the commercial failure of her first two albums, Magia (1991) and Peligro (1993), she rose to prominence in Hispanic countries with her next albums, Pies Descalzos (1995) and Dónde Están los Ladrones? (1998). Shakira entered the English-language market with her fifth album, Laundry Service (2001), which sold over 13 million copies worldwide. Buoyed by the international number-one singles 'Whenever, Wherever' and 'Underneath Your Clothes', the album propelled her reputation as a leading crossover artist. The BMI, the largest music rights organization in the United States, described Shakira as a pioneer who extended the global reach of Latino singers.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/86/Shakira_%26_Chris_Martin_-_Global_Citizen_Festival_Hamburg_04_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joni Mitchell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joni-mitchell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roberta Joan 'Joni' Mitchell is a Canadian singer-songwriter. Drawing from folk, pop, rock, classical, and jazz, Mitchell's songs often reflect on social and philosophical ideals as well as her feelings about romance, womanhood, disillusionment, and joy. She has received many accolades, including nine Grammy Awards and induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1997. Rolling Stone called her 'one of the greatest songwriters ever', and AllMusic has stated, 'When the dust settles, Joni Mitchell may stand as the most important and influential female recording artist of the late 20th century'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9f/2013_Joni_Mitchell_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joni-mitchell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul Simon]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-simon/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul Frederic Simon is an American musician, singer, songwriter and actor. Simon's musical career has spanned over six decades. He is widely regarded as one of the best songwriters in popular music history.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b6/Paul_Simon_at_the_9-30_Club_%28b%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-simon/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:38 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sam Bush]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sam-bush/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Charles Samuel Bush is an American mandolinist who is considered an originator of progressive bluegrass music. In 2020, he was inducted into the International Bluegrass Music Hall of Fame as a member of New Grass Revival.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/33/Sam_Bush_%282006%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sam-bush/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:37 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Oldfield]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-oldfield/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Gordon Oldfield is a British musician, multi-instrumentalist and songwriter best known for his debut studio album Tubular Bells (1973), which became an unexpected critical and commercial success and propelled him to worldwide fame. Though primarily a guitarist, Oldfield is known for playing a range of instruments, which includes keyboards and percussion, and doing vocals. He has adopted a range of musical styles throughout his career, including progressive rock, world, folk, classical, electronic, ambient, and new age music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/87/Mike_Oldfield_NOTP_2006.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-oldfield/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:37 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>