<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » World Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » World Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 01:11:11 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shakira]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Shakira Isabel Mebarak Ripoll is a Colombian singer, songwriter, dancer, businesswoman, and philanthropist. Born and raised in Barranquilla, she made her recording debut under Sony Music Colombia at the age of 13. Following the commercial failure of her first two Colombian albums, Magia (1991) and Peligro (1993), she rose to prominence in Spanish-speaking countries with her next albums, Pies Descalzos (1995) and Dónde Están los Ladrones? (1998). Shakira entered the English-language market with her fifth album, Laundry Service (2001). It sold over 13 million copies and spawned the international number-one singles 'Whenever, Wherever' and 'Underneath Your Clothes'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/Shakira_in_Toronto_2018.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/shakira/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Asha Bhosle]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/asha-bhosle/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Asha Bhosle, is an Indian playback singer. She is best known for her playback singing in Hindi cinema, although she has a wider repertoire. Bhosle's career started in 1943 and has spanned over six decades. She has done playback singing for over a thousand Bollywood movies. In addition, she has recorded several private albums and participated in numerous solo concerts in India and abroad. In 2006, Asha Bhosle stated that she had sung over 12,000 songs, a figure repeated by several other sources. In 2011, she was officially acknowledged by the Guinness Book of World Records as the most recorded artist in music history. The Government of India honoured her with the Dadasaheb Phalke Award in 2000 and the Padma Vibhushan in 2008. Bhosle is the sister of playback singer Lata Mangeshkar.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7a/Asha_Bhosle_-_still_47160_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/asha-bhosle/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Joni Mitchell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joni-mitchell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roberta Joan 'Joni' Mitchell is a Canadian singer-songwriter. Drawing from folk, pop, rock, and jazz, Mitchell's songs often reflect social and environmental ideals as well as her feelings about romance, confusion, disillusionment, and joy. She has received many accolades, including nine Grammy Awards and induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1997. Rolling Stone called her 'one of the greatest songwriters ever', and AllMusic has stated, 'When the dust settles, Joni Mitchell may stand as the most important and influential female recording artist of the late 20th century'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a9/1974_Joni_Mitchell.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/joni-mitchell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jesse Cook]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jesse-cook/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jesse Arnaud Cook is a Canadian guitarist, composer, and producer. Widely considered one of the most influential figures in 'nuevo flamenco' music today, he incorporates elements of flamenco rumba, jazz, & many forms of world music into his work. He is a Juno Award winner, Acoustic Guitar Player's Choice Award silver winner in the Flamenco Category, and a three-time winner of the Canadian Smooth Jazz award for Guitarist of the Year. He has recorded on the EMI, E1 Music and Narada labels and has sold over 1.5 million records worldwide.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2a/Jesse_Cook_143_cropped.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jesse-cook/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Paul Simon]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-simon/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Paul Frederic Simon is an American singer-songwriter and actor. Simon's musical career has spanned seven decades. He reached fame and commercial success as half of the duo Simon & Garfunkel, formed in 1956 with Art Garfunkel. Simon was responsible for writing nearly all of the pair's songs, including three that reached number one on the U.S. singles charts: 'The Sound of Silence', 'Mrs. Robinson', and 'Bridge over Troubled Water'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b6/Paul_Simon_at_the_9-30_Club_%28b%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/paul-simon/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[George Harrison]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-harrison/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>George Harrison was an English musician, singer-songwriter, and music and film producer who achieved international fame as the lead guitarist of the Beatles. Sometimes called 'the quiet Beatle', Harrison embraced Indian culture and helped broaden the scope of popular music through his incorporation of Indian instrumentation and Hindu-aligned spirituality in the Beatles' work. Although the majority of the band's songs were written by John Lennon and Paul McCartney, most Beatles albums from 1965 onwards contained at least two Harrison compositions. His songs for the group included 'Taxman', 'Within You Without You', 'While My Guitar Gently Weeps', 'Here Comes the Sun' and 'Something'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/42/George_Harrison_1974.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/george-harrison/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>