<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Blind Faith</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Blind Faith</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 14:35:13 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Winwood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-winwood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Stephen Lawrence Winwood is an English singer, songwriter, and musician whose genres include blue-eyed soul, rhythm and blues, blues rock, and pop rock. Though primarily a vocalist and keyboard player, Winwood proficiently plays other instruments, including drums, mandolin, guitars, bass, and saxophone.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/81/Steve_Winwood_scottfisher.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-winwood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Eric Clapton]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eric-clapton/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Eric Patrick Clapton, is an English rock and blues guitarist, singer, and songwriter. He is the only three-time inductee to the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame: once as a solo artist and separately as a member of the Yardbirds and of Cream. Clapton has been referred to as one of the most important and influential guitarists of all time. Clapton ranked second in Rolling Stone's list of the '100 Greatest Guitarists of All Time' and fourth in Gibson's 'Top 50 Guitarists of All Time'. He was also named number five in Time magazine's list of 'The 10 Best Electric Guitar Players' in 2009.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/49/Eclapton_cardiff.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eric-clapton/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ric Grech]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ric-grech/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Roman Grechko, better known as Ric Grech, was a British rock musician and multi-instrumentalist. He is best known for playing bass guitar and violin with Family as well as in the supergroups Blind Faith and Traffic. He also played with ex-Cream drummer Ginger Baker's Air Force.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6d/Blind_Faith_%281969%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ric-grech/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>