<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Hard Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Hard Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 14:32:18 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Geezer Butler]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/geezer-butler/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Terence Michael Joseph 'Geezer' Butler is an English musician and songwriter. Butler is best known as the bassist and primary lyricist of the heavy metal band Black Sabbath. He has also recorded and performed with Heaven & Hell, GZR, and Ozzy Osbourne. He currently serves as bassist of Deadland Ritual.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7a/Heaven_And_Hell_4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/geezer-butler/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Serj Tankian]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Serj Tankian is an Armenian-American musician, singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, poet and political activist. He is best known as the lead vocalist, songwriter, keyboardist, and occasional live rhythm guitarist of the band System of a Down, formed in 1994.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/69/Serj_Tankian_Spirit_of_Burgas_Bulgaria_2010_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Richard Fortus]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-fortus/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Fortus is an American guitarist. He is best known as a member of the hard rock band Guns N' Roses, with whom he has been a member since 2002, and with whom he has recorded one studio album. Fortus has also collaborated extensively with The Psychedelic Furs frontman Richard Butler and fellow Guns N' Roses bandmate Frank Ferrer. Aside from lead singer Axl Rose, and keyboardist Dizzy Reed, Fortus is the longest tenured member of Guns N' Roses, having been with the band continuously since 2002.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0c/Richard_Fortus_%288056234364%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-fortus/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Walter Giardino]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/walter-giardino/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Héctor Walter Giardino is an Argentine guitarist, songwriter and leader of the heavy metal and hard rock band Rata Blanca.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/95/Walter_giardino.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/walter-giardino/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Davey Johnstone]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/davey-johnstone/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David William Logan 'Davey' Johnstone is a Scottish rock guitarist and vocalist, best known for his work with Elton John.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b3/Davey_Johnstone_2008.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/davey-johnstone/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Duff McKagan]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/duff-mckagan/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Andrew 'Duff' McKagan, sometimes credited as Duff 'Rose' McKagan, is an American multi-instrumentalist, singer, songwriter and author. He is best known for his twelve-year tenure as the bassist of the hard rock band Guns N' Roses, with whom he achieved worldwide success in the late 1980s and early 1990s. McKagan rejoined the band in 2016, following their induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/77/Duff_McKagan_2012.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/duff-mckagan/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Doug Aldrich]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/doug-aldrich/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Doug Aldrich is a Los Angeles-based hard rock guitarist. He founded the band Burning Rain with Keith St. John in 1998 and has played previously with the bands Whitesnake, Dio, Lion, Hurricane, House of Lords, Bad Moon Rising and Revolution Saints. He is currently in the band The Dead Daisies. He has also released several solo albums. In 2015, Doug was touring as guitar player of former Deep Purple bassist and vocalist Glenn Hughes band. In early 2016 it was announced that he would be replacing Richard Fortus as guitarist of The Dead Daisies, as Fortus is leaving that band to perform with the Guns N' Roses reunion.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f4/Doug_Aldrich_%282006%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/doug-aldrich/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pat Travers]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pat-travers/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Patrick Henry Travers is a Canadian rock guitarist, keyboardist and singer who began his recording career with Polydor Records in the mid-1970s. Pat Thrall, Nicko McBrain, Clive Edwards, Mick Dyche, Tommy Aldridge, Peter 'Mars' Cowling, Barry Dunaway, Jerry Riggs, Gunter Nezhoda, Carmine Appice, Michael Shrieve, Rodney O'Quinn are some of the noted musicians who have been members of the Pat Travers Band through the years. Paul Gilbert has referred to Travers as a 'guitar god', and Kirk Hammett of Metallica has cited him as one of his favorite guitar players.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/67/9b.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/pat-travers/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Eric Bloom]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eric-bloom/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Eric Jay Bloom is an American singer, songwriter and musician. He is best known as the lead vocalist, guitar and keyboard/synthesizer player for the long-running band Blue Öyster Cult, with work on more than 20 albums. Much of his lyrical content relates to his lifelong interest in science fiction.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ed/EricBloom.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/eric-bloom/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 03:47:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>