<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Hard Rock</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Hard Rock</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:38:12 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Richie Faulkner]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richie-faulkner/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Ian Faulkner, is an English musician best known as one of the lead guitarists for the heavy metal band Judas Priest since 2011, replacing original member K. K. Downing. Faulkner has also performed with Lauren Harris, Christopher Lee, Voodoo Six, Dirty Deeds, and Ace Mafia.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/42/Richie_Faulkner.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richie-faulkner/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Steve Stevens]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-stevens/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Steve Stevens is an American guitarist and songwriter. He is best known as Billy Idol's guitarist and songwriting collaborator, and for his lead guitar work on the theme to Top Gun – 'Top Gun Anthem' – for which he won a Grammy in 1987: Best Pop Instrumental Performance. A session guitarist, he has played for Michael Jackson, Ric Ocasek, Robert Palmer and many others. Stevens was in Vince Neil's band in 1993, touring and recording on Neil's album Exposed. In 1995, Stevens and Idol were briefly members of the group Neurotic Outsiders. Stevens was a founding member of the supergroup Bozzio Levin Stevens, which released Black Light Syndrome in 1997 and Situation Dangerous in 2000. He brought Spanish flamenco guitar stylings to the song 'Pistolero' (1999) for the trance group Juno Reactor. During 2012–2016, Stevens appeared with Kings of Chaos. His 'Steve Stevens' group headlined the closing performance at the Musikmesse in Frankfurt, Germany, in April of 2016. He is also a television personality on the E! show Married to Rock, alongside his wife, Josie Stevens.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f8/Idolandstevens.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/steve-stevens/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mark Slaughter]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-slaughter/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Mark Allen Slaughter is an American singer and musician, and one of the founders of the hard rock band Slaughter.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bd/Mark_Slaughter.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mark-slaughter/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Geezer Butler]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/geezer-butler/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Terence Michael Joseph 'Geezer' Butler is an English musician and songwriter. Butler is best known as the bassist and primary lyricist of the heavy metal band Black Sabbath. He has also recorded and performed with Heaven & Hell, GZR, and Ozzy Osbourne. He currently serves as bassist of Deadland Ritual.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7a/Heaven_And_Hell_4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/geezer-butler/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Serj Tankian]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Serj Tankian is an Armenian-American musician, singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, record producer, poet and political activist. He is best known as the lead vocalist, songwriter, keyboardist, and occasional live rhythm guitarist of the band System of a Down, formed in 1994.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/69/Serj_Tankian_Spirit_of_Burgas_Bulgaria_2010_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nancy Wilson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nancy-wilson-(rock-musician)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nancy Lamoureaux Wilson is an American musician, singer, songwriter, producer, and film composer. She rose to fame alongside her older sister, singer Ann Wilson, as a guitarist and backing vocalist in the rock band Heart, which she joined in 1974.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d5/Nancy_Wilson_1998.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nancy-wilson-(rock-musician)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Richard Fortus]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-fortus/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Fortus is an American guitarist. He is best known as a member of the hard rock band Guns N' Roses, with whom he has been a member since 2002, and with whom he has recorded one studio album. Fortus has also collaborated extensively with The Psychedelic Furs frontman Richard Butler and fellow Guns N' Roses bandmate Frank Ferrer. Aside from lead singer Axl Rose, and keyboardist Dizzy Reed, Fortus is the longest tenured member of Guns N' Roses, having been with the band continuously since 2002.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0c/Richard_Fortus_%288056234364%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/richard-fortus/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Walter Giardino]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/walter-giardino/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Héctor Walter Giardino is an Argentine guitarist, songwriter and leader of the heavy metal and hard rock band Rata Blanca.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/95/Walter_giardino.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/walter-giardino/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Cornell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher John Cornell was an American musician, singer and songwriter. He was best known as the lead vocalist for the rock bands Soundgarden and Audioslave. Cornell was also known for his numerous solo works and soundtrack contributions since 1991, and as the founder and frontman for Temple of the Dog, the one-off tribute band dedicated to his late friend Andrew Wood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8d/Chris_Cornell_2007.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-cornell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jorge Salán]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jorge-salán/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jorge Salán is a Spanish rock lead guitarist, singer, producer and songwriter. He is most well known for being the lead guitar for the metal rock solo singer Jeff Scott Soto and the Jeff Scott Soto Band from 2009 till today, the lead guitar on Robin Beck's European Tour 2013, and for having collaborated with a long list of legendary rock musicians such as Fiona Flanagan or bass guitar player Bob Daisley.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/90/Jorgesalan.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jorge-salán/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>