<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Sampler</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Sampler</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 21:36:05 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gustavo Cerati]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gustavo-cerati/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Gustavo Adrián Cerati was an Argentine singer-songwriter, composer and producer, considered one of the most important and influential figures of Ibero-American rock. Cerati along with his band Soda Stereo, were one of the most popular and influential rock and pop groups of the 1980s and '90s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c8/Concierto_Gustavo_Cerati_%284120623383%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/gustavo-cerati/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chris Martin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-martin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher Anthony John Martin is an English singer, songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, producer, and philanthropist. He is the lead singer, primary songwriter, and co-founder of the alternative rock band Coldplay. Born in Exeter, Devon, Martin went to University College London, where he formed a rock band with Jonny Buckland, Guy Berryman, and Will Champion in 1996 called Starfish, which was eventually renamed Coldplay in 1998.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/61/Chris_Martin_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/chris-martin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Shinoda]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Kenji Shinoda is an American musician, rapper, singer, songwriter, record producer, and graphic designer. He co-founded Linkin Park in 1996 and is the band's lead vocalist, as well as rhythm guitarist, keyboardist, primary songwriter and producer. Shinoda later created a hip-hop-driven side project, Fort Minor, in 2004. He has also served as a producer for tracks and albums by Lupe Fiasco, Styles of Beyond and the X-Ecutioners.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/Mike_Shinoda_4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Serj Tankian]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Serj Tankian is an Armenian-American-Lebanese singer, musician, songwriter, record producer, and political activist. He is best known as the lead vocalist, primary lyricist, keyboardist, and occasional rhythm guitarist of heavy metal band System of a Down, which was formed in 1994.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3e/Serj_Tankian_in_Artsakh_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/serj-tankian/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Rick Rubin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rick-rubin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Frederick Jay 'Rick' Rubin is an American record producer and former copresident of Columbia Records. Along with Russell Simmons, he is the cofounder of Def Jam Recordings and also established American Recordings. With the Beastie Boys, LL Cool J, Public Enemy, Geto Boys, and Run-DMC, Rubin helped popularize hip hop music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/43/RickRubinSept09.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/rick-rubin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>