<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » Soulfly</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » Soulfly</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 14:45:06 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marc Rizzo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marc-rizzo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Marc Rizzo is an American musician, best known as the lead guitarist of metal band Soulfly. He has featured on eight Soulfly albums: Prophecy, Dark Ages, Conquer, Omen, Enslaved, Savages, Archangel, and Ritual. He has also released four solo instrumental albums: Colossal Myopia, The Ultimate Devotion, Legionnaire, and Rotation. Rizzo is also a member of Cavalera Conspiracy, a side project with the co-founders of Sepultura, Max and Igor Cavalera. The band released their debut album Inflikted in 2008, Blunt Force Trauma in 2011 and Pandemonium in 2014. In March 2015, it was announced that Rizzo was playing guitar for Misfits. His only show with the band so far took place at Dutch Comic Con. In June 2016, he joined Dead by Wednesday as a second guitarist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a8/Cavalera_Conspiracy_%40_McCallum_Park_%285_2_2012%29_%286971313373%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marc-rizzo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Max Cavalera]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/max-cavalera/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Massimiliano Antonio 'Max' Cavalera is a Brazilian singer, guitarist, and songwriter who currently plays in heavy metal bands Soulfly, Cavalera Conspiracy, and Killer Be Killed. In 1984, he co-founded the death metal/thrash metal band Sepultura with his brother Igor Cavalera and was the band's lead singer and rhythm guitarist until 1996. Cavalera was also involved in a short-lived side project called Nailbomb.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/43/Soulfly_With_Full_Force_2018_03_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/max-cavalera/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Logan Mader]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/logan-mader/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/34/Logan_Mader.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/logan-mader/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>