<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Clarinet</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Clarinet</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 13:58:34 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Matt Bellamy]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/matt-bellamy/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Matthew James Bellamy is an English singer, musician, and songwriter. He is the lead vocalist, guitarist, pianist, and primary songwriter of the rock band Muse. He is recognised for his eccentric stage persona, wide tenor vocal range and musicianship. Bellamy has released solo compositions, and plays bass in the supergroup the Jaded Hearts Club; he produced their debut album, You've Always Been Here (2020).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/36/MuseO2140919-25_%2848736144762%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/matt-bellamy/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sven-Erik Magnusson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sven-erik-magnusson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Knut Sven-Erik Magnusson was a Swedish singer and musician known for being the lead singer of the band Sven-Ingvars that during their sixty-year history played many different types of popular music, and was at times regarded as a dansband. The band had its last tour during the summer of 2016 with their last show on 21 August that year in Blekinge.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/05/Sven-Erik_Magnusson_2016.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/sven-erik-magnusson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Boz Boorer]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/boz-boorer/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/86/Bozboorer.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/boz-boorer/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Phil Ochs]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/phil-ochs/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Philip David Ochs December 19, 1940 – April 9, 1976) was an American protest singer and songwriter who was known for his sharp wit, sardonic humor, political activism, often alliterative lyrics, and distinctive voice. He wrote hundreds of songs in the 1960s and 1970s and released eight albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/4e/20111015_174748_phil-ochs.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/phil-ochs/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[John Jorgenson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-jorgenson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John Richard Jorgenson is an American musician. Although best known for his guitar work with bands such as the Desert Rose Band and The Hellecasters, he is also proficient on the mandolin, mandocello, Dobro, pedal steel guitar, piano, upright bass, clarinet, bassoon, and saxophone. While a member of the Desert Rose Band, he won the Academy of Country Music's 'Guitarist of the Year' award three consecutive years.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/02/John_Jorgenson_at_Kentucky_Coffee_Tree_Cafe.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/john-jorgenson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:43 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ellie Goulding]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ellie-goulding/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Elena Jane Goulding is an English singer and songwriter. Her career began when she met record producers Starsmith and Frankmusik, and she was later spotted by Jamie Lillywhite, who later became her manager and A&R. After signing to Polydor Records in July 2009, Goulding released her debut extended play, An Introduction to Ellie Goulding later that year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/71/Goulding%2C_Staples_Center%2C_Los_Angeles%2C_8th_April_2016_%2843%29-cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ellie-goulding/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Roy Wood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-wood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Roy Wood is an English singer-songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. He was particularly successful in the 1960s and 1970s as member and co-founder of the Move, Electric Light Orchestra and Wizzard. As a songwriter, he contributed a number of hits to the repertoire of these bands. Altogether he had more than 20 singles in the UK Singles Chart under various guises, including three UK No. 1 hits.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0f/Roy_Wood_TopPop.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/roy-wood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nick Drake]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nick-drake/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nicholas Rodney Drake was an English singer-songwriter and musician known for his acoustic guitar-based songs. Though he never found a wide audience during his lifetime, his work has gradually achieved wider notice and recognition. Drake signed to Island Records when he was 20 years old and a student at the University of Cambridge. He released his debut album, Five Leaves Left, in 1969. He recorded two more albums—Bryter Layter (1970) and Pink Moon (1972). Neither sold more than 5,000 copies on initial release. His reluctance to perform live, or be interviewed, contributed to his lack of commercial success. There is no known video footage of the adult Drake; he was only ever captured in still photographs and in home footage from his childhood.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/61/Nick_Drake_%281971%29.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nick-drake/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marcus Miller]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marcus-miller/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Henry Marcus Miller Jr. is an American film composer, jazz composer, record producer, arranger, and multi-instrumentalist, best known as a bassist. He has worked with trumpeter Miles Davis, pianist Herbie Hancock, singer Luther Vandross, and saxophonist David Sanborn, among others.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8f/Marcus_Miller_-_Leverkusener_Jazztage_2017-7051.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marcus-miller/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:41 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lewis Brian Hopkin Jones was an English musician and composer, best known as the founder and original leader of the Rolling Stones. Initially a slide guitarist, Jones went on to play a wide variety of instruments on Rolling Stones recordings and in concerts, including rhythm guitar, lead guitar, sitar, dulcimer, various keyboard instruments such as piano and mellotron, marimba, wind instruments such as harmonica, recorder, saxophone, as well as drums, vocals and numerous others.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6b/Brian_Jones%2C_Statesboro%2C_Georgia%2C_May_4%2C_1965_%28377872218%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>