<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » J Pop</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » J Pop</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:38:12 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Toshi]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/toshi/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Toshimitsu Deyama , known exclusively by his stage name Toshi, is a Japanese singer and songwriter. He is best known as the lead vocalist and a co-founder of the rock band X Japan, who rose to prominence in the late 1980s and early 1990s and are credited as founders of the Japanese visual kei movement. Toshi began an extensive solo career in 1992 before leaving X Japan at the end of 1997. By his own admission, Toshi was 'brainwashed' by a group called Home of Heart, whose leader would control his musical output for the next 12 years. In 2007, X Japan reunited and began a world tour. Toshi severed ties with Home of Heart in January 2010 and renewed his solo career. His distinctive, impassioned tenor vocals have been compared to those of Steve Perry. In Japan, he also uses the stage name Ryūgentoshi (龍玄とし).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/05/Deadpool_2_Japan_Premiere_Red_Carpet_Toshl_%2841555176645%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/toshi/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Masayoshi Yamazaki]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/masayoshi-yamazaki/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Masayoshi Yamazaki  is a Japanese singer-songwriter who plays guitar-driven blues, rock, and pop music, though he has also recorded piano ballads. Though he primarily plays the guitar, he has played the drums, piano, percussion, saxophone, and glockenspiel on some albums.</p>]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/masayoshi-yamazaki/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Takahiro Matsumoto]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tak-matsumoto/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Takahiro 'Tak' Matsumoto  is a Grammy Award-winning Japanese guitarist, producer, arranger, composer, singer and songwriter. In addition to being the guitarist and lead composer for the rock duo B'z, the best-selling music act in their native Japan, he has also had a successful solo career. He is only the fifth guitarist in the world to have his own Gibson signature model guitar. The instrumental album Take Your Pick (2010) made in collaboration with Larry Carlton won an award for the Best Pop Instrumental Album at the 53rd Grammy Awards.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/B%27Z_at_Best_Buy_Theater_NYC_-_9-30-12_-_22.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tak-matsumoto/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tetsuya Komuro]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tetsuya-komuro/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Tetsuya Komuro  is a retired Japanese musician, singer-songwriter, composer and record producer. He is recognized as the most successful producer in Japanese music history and introduced dance music to the Japanese mainstream. He was also a former owner of the disco Velfarre located in Roppongi, Tokyo. He is widely regarded as one of the most influential figures in pop throughout the 1990s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/70/MTV_VMAJ_2014_Tetsuya_Komuro_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/tetsuya-komuro/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Yui]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yui-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Yui, stylized as YUI or yui, is a Japanese singer-songwriter, multi-instrumentalist, and actress. Born and raised in Fukuoka prefecture, she played live at various locations in her hometown before being noticed by Sony Music Japan when she was 17 years old, and released her debut single months later. Her singles, however, were only met with moderate success until the breakout 'Good-bye Days', which charted for 44 weeks on Oricon and marked her as one of the Japanese music industry's rising stars.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b3/Yui_the_MTV_Music_Awards_2006.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yui-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:11 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Haruichi Shindō]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/haruichi-shindō/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Haruichi Shindō  is a Japanese musician, lyricist, composer, record producer and author who is affiliated with Amuse, Inc. He is a guitarist for Porno Graffitti and THE Yatou. His artist name at his debut was Haruichi (ハルイチ), and he formed a band named No Score with his classmates at high school. Originally he was the lead vocalist, but since Akihito Okano joined, he became the lead guitarist and provided backing vocals. His wife is actress Kyōko Hasegawa.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/8/8f/Porno_Graffitti_at_Anime_Expo_2013.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/haruichi-shindō/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:11 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Masaharu Fukuyama]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/masaharu-fukuyama/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Masaharu Fukuyama  is a Japanese musician, singer-songwriter, multi-instrumentalist and actor from Nagasaki. He debuted in 1990 with the single 'Tsuioku no Ame no Naka'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/2d/Fukuyama_Masaharu_in_Taipei%2C_2013_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/masaharu-fukuyama/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:11 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marty Friedman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marty-friedman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Martin Adam 'Marty' Friedman is an American guitarist, known for his tenure as the lead guitarist for heavy metal band Megadeth which spanned nearly the full decade of the 1990s. He is also known for playing alongside Jason Becker in Cacophony until 1989, as well as his 13 solo albums and tours. Friedman has resided in Tokyo, Japan since 2003, where he has appeared on over 700 Japanese television programs such as Rock Fujiyama, Hebimeta-san, Kouhaku uta gassen and Jukebox English. He has released albums with several record labels, including Avex Trax, Universal, EMI, Prosthetic and Shrapnel Records.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/76/Marty_Friedman_13.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marty-friedman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 23:37:09 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>