<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Hip Hop Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Hip Hop Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:04:36 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ed Sheeran]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ed-sheeran/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Edward Christopher Sheeran, is an English singer, songwriter, guitarist, record producer, and actor. In early 2011, Sheeran independently released the extended play, No. 5 Collaborations Project. After signing with Asylum Records, his debut album, +, was released in September 2011. It topped the UK and Australian charts, reached number five in the US, and has since been certified eight-times platinum in the UK. The album contains the single 'The A Team', which earned him the Ivor Novello Award for Best Song Musically and Lyrically. In 2012, Sheeran won the Brit Awards for Best British Male Solo Artist and British Breakthrough Act. 'The A Team' was nominated for Song of the Year at the 2013 Grammy Awards, where he performed the song with Elton John.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/55/Ed_Sheeran_2013.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ed-sheeran/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Shinoda]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Kenji Shinoda is an American musician, singer, songwriter, rapper, record producer, and graphic designer. He co-founded Linkin Park in 1996 and is the band's rhythm guitarist, primary songwriter, keyboardist, producer, and co-lead vocalist. Shinoda later created a hip-hop-driven side project, Fort Minor, in 2004. He has also served as a producer for tracks and albums by Lupe Fiasco, Styles of Beyond and the X-Ecutioners.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/Mike_Shinoda_4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Meshell Ndegeocello]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/meshell-ndegeocello/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michelle Lynn Johnson, better known as Meshell Ndegeocello, is an American singer-songwriter, rapper, and bassist. She has gone by the name Meshell Suhaila Bashir-Shakur which is used as a writing credit on some of her later work. Her music incorporates a wide variety of influences, including funk, soul, jazz, hip hop, reggae and rock. She has received significant critical acclaim throughout her career, and although she has never won a Grammy Award, she has been nominated ten times. She has been credited for helping to have 'sparked the neo-soul movement.'</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/62/Meshell_Ndegeocello_Wikipedia.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/meshell-ndegeocello/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Nelly Furtado]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nelly Kim Furtado is a Canadian singer and songwriter. Furtado first gained fame with her debut album, Whoa, Nelly! (2000), which was a critical and commercial success that spawned two top 10 singles on the Billboard Hot 100, 'I'm Like a Bird' and 'Turn Off the Light'. The first of the two singles won her a Grammy Award for Best Female Pop Vocal Performance. In 2003, she released her second album, Folklore, which was preceded by the lead single, 'Powerless '.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/aa/Nelly_Furtado_at_Radio_Regenbogen_Award_2017_%286%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/nelly-furtado/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Justin Bieber]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/justin-bieber/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Justin Drew Bieber is a Canadian singer-songwriter and actor. Encountered at 13 years old by talent manager Scooter Braun after he had watched the boy's YouTube cover song videos, Bieber was signed to RBMG Records in 2008. Bieber released his debut EP, My World, in late 2009. It was certified Platinum in the United States. With the EP, Bieber became the first artist to have seven songs from a debut record chart on the Billboard Hot 100.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/Justin_Bieber_in_2015.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/justin-bieber/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Post Malone]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/post-malone/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Austin Richard Post, known professionally as Post Malone, is an American rapper, singer, songwriter, and record producer. He has gained acclaim for blending musical genres including hip hop, pop, trap, and rock, his introspective songwriting, and his laconic vocal style. Born in Syracuse, New York and raised in Grapevine, Texas, Post first attained recognition in 2015 following the release of his debut single 'White Iverson', which peaked in the top 20 on the US Billboard Hot 100. He subsequently earned a recording contract with Republic Records.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/94/Post_Malone_2018.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/post-malone/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[will.i.am]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/will.i.am/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Adams, known professionally as will.i.am, is an American rapper, singer, songwriter, record producer, DJ, actor and television personality. He is the founding and lead member of the hip hop group The Black Eyed Peas.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/38/Will.i.am_in_2012.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/will.i.am/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:02:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>