<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Hip Hop Music</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Hip Hop Music</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 22:51:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adam Yauch]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adam-yauch/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Adam Nathaniel Yauch, better known under the stage name MCA, was an American rapper, bass player, filmmaker and a founding member of the hip hop group Beastie Boys.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f9/Adam_Yauch_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/adam-yauch/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kool Keith]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kool-keith/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Keith Matthew Thornton, better known by his stage name Kool Keith, is an American rapper and record producer from The Bronx, New York known for his surreal, abstract and often profane or incomprehensible lyrics. Kool Keith has recorded prolifically both as a solo artist and in group collaborations. Kool Keith is generally considered to be one of hip-hop's most eccentric and unusual personalities.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b1/Kool-Keith-2009.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kool-keith/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Franti]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-franti/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Franti is an American rapper, musician, poet, activist, documentarian, and singer-songwriter, known for his participation in many musical projects, most with a political and social emphasis, including the Beatnigs and the Disposable Heroes of Hiphoprisy. He is the creator and lead vocalist of his current independent project, Michael Franti & Spearhead, a band that blends hip hop with a variety of other styles including funk, reggae, jazz, folk, and rock. He is also an outspoken supporter for a wide spectrum of peace and social justice issues, and he is especially an advocate for peace in the Middle East.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/31/Michael_Franti_and_Spearhead_%40_Fremantle_Park_%2817_4_2011%29_%285648770710%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-franti/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lauryn Hill]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lauryn-hill/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lauryn Noelle Hill is an American singer, songwriter, rapper, record producer and actress. She is often regarded as one of the greatest rappers of all time, as well as being one of the most influential singers of her generation. Hill is credited for breaking barriers for female rappers, popularizing melodic rapping and for bringing hip hop and neo soul to popular music. She is known for being a member of Fugees and her solo album The Miseducation of Lauryn Hill, which became one of the best-selling albums of all-time. Hill has won many awards, including eight Grammy Awards, the most for a female rapper.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ad/LaurynHill.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lauryn-hill/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Post Malone]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/post-malone/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Austin Richard Post, known professionally as Post Malone, is an American rapper, singer, songwriter, record producer, and actor. Known for his tattoos, introspective songwriting, and laconic vocal style, Malone has gained acclaim for blending a range of genres including hip hop, R&B, pop, trap, rap rock, and cloud rap. He first attained recognition in 2015 following the release of his debut single 'White Iverson'. He subsequently signed a recording contract with Republic Records. His stage name is derived from his last name and from a rap name generator.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/99/Post_Malone_in_Chicago_2020.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/post-malone/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Andre 3000]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andré-3000/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>André Lauren Benjamin, better known as André 3000, is an American rapper, singer, songwriter, actor, and record producer. He is best known for being a part of southern hip hop duo Outkast alongside fellow rapper Big Boi. Many publications, such as Billboard and Showbiz Cheatsheet have listed André 3000 as one of the top 10 rappers of all time. As an actor, Benjamin has made appearances in several films and television series, including Families, The Shield, Be Cool, Revolver, Semi-Pro, Four Brothers, and in the lead role of Jimi Hendrix in All Is by My Side. He currently plays Fredwynn on the AMC anthology series, Dispatches from Elsewhere.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b4/Andre_Benjamin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/andré-3000/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ed Sheeran]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ed-sheeran/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Edward Christopher Sheeran is an English singer, songwriter, record producer, musician, actor, and businessman. After first recording music in 2004, he began gaining attention through YouTube. In early 2011, Sheeran independently released the extended play, No. 5 Collaborations Project. He signed with Asylum Records the same year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c1/Ed_Sheeran-6886_%28cropped%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ed-sheeran/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Shinoda]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Kenji Shinoda is an American musician, rapper, singer, songwriter, record producer, and graphic designer. He co-founded Linkin Park in 1996 and is the band's lead vocalist, as well as rhythm guitarist, keyboardist, primary songwriter and producer. Shinoda later created a hip-hop-driven side project, Fort Minor, in 2004. He has also served as a producer for tracks and albums by Lupe Fiasco, Styles of Beyond and the X-Ecutioners.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/39/Mike_Shinoda_4.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-shinoda/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Justin Bieber]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/justin-bieber/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Justin Drew Bieber is a Canadian singer, songwriter and multi-instrumentalist. Discovered at age 13 by talent manager Scooter Braun after he had watched his YouTube cover song videos, Bieber was signed to RBMG Records in 2008. With Bieber's debut EP My World, released in late 2009, Bieber became the first artist to have seven songs from a debut record chart on the Billboard Hot 100.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/Justin_Bieber_in_2015.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/justin-bieber/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Miguel]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/miguel-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Miguel Jontel Pimentel is an American singer, songwriter, record producer, and actor. Raised in San Pedro, California, he began pursuing a music career at age thirteen. After signing to Jive Records in 2007, Miguel released his debut studio album, All I Want Is You, in November 2010. Although it was underpromoted upon its release, the album became a sleeper hit and helped Miguel garner commercial standing.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fb/Miguel_2019_by_Glenn_Francis.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/miguel-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>