<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Group » The Highwaymen</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Group » The Highwaymen</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 13:58:33 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kris Kristofferson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kris-kristofferson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kristoffer Kristofferson is an American retired singer-songwriter and actor. Among his songwriting credits are the songs 'Me and Bobby McGee', 'For the Good Times', 'Sunday Mornin' Comin' Down', and 'Help Me Make It Through the Night', all of which were hits for other artists. Kristofferson composed his own songs and collaborated with Nashville songwriters such as Shel Silverstein.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d2/Kris_Kristofferson_SXSW_2006_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kris-kristofferson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Willie Nelson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Willie Hugh Nelson is an American musician, actor, and activist. The critical success of the album Shotgun Willie (1973), combined with the critical and commercial success of Red Headed Stranger (1975) and Stardust (1978), made Nelson one of the most recognized artists in country music. He was one of the main figures of outlaw country, a subgenre of country music that developed in the late 1960s as a reaction to the conservative restrictions of the Nashville sound. Nelson has acted in over 30 films, co-authored several books, and has been involved in activism for the use of biofuels and the legalization of marijuana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/WillieNelson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Waylon Jennings]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/waylon-jennings/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Waylon Arnold Jennings was an American singer, songwriter, and musician. He is best known as one of the founding pioneers of the Outlaw Movement in country music.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b9/Waylon_Jennings_RCA_cropped.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/waylon-jennings/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:42 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Johnny Cash]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/johnny-cash/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>John R. Cash was an American singer, songwriter, musician, and actor. Much of Cash's music contained themes of sorrow, moral tribulation, and redemption, especially in the later stages of his career. He was known for his deep, calm bass-baritone voice, the distinctive sound of his Tennessee Three backing band characterized by train-like chugging guitar rhythms, a rebelliousness coupled with an increasingly somber and humble demeanor, free prison concerts, and a trademark all-black stage wardrobe which earned him the nickname 'The Man in Black'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/75/At_San_quentin_1969_2014-05-04_00-14.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/johnny-cash/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>