<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Neo Soul</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Neo Soul</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 20:58:33 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lauryn Hill]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lauryn-hill/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lauryn Noelle Hill is an American singer, songwriter, rapper, record producer and actress. She is often regarded as one of the greatest rappers of all time, as well as being one of the most influential singers of her generation. Hill is credited for breaking barriers for female rappers, popularizing melodic rapping and for bringing hip hop and neo soul to popular music. She is known for being a member of Fugees and her solo album The Miseducation of Lauryn Hill, which became one of the best-selling albums of all-time. Hill has won many awards, including eight Grammy Awards, the most for a female rapper.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ad/LaurynHill.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lauryn-hill/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:46 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[James Morrison]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-morrison-(singer)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Morrison Catchpole is an English singer, songwriter and guitarist from Rugby, Warwickshire. In 2006, his debut single 'You Give Me Something' became a hit in Europe, Australia, Japan and Iran, peaking in the top five in the UK and claiming the No. 1 spot in New Zealand. His debut album, Undiscovered, debuted at the top of the UK Albums Chart. In 2007, Morrison won the Brit Award for Best British Male.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/30/James_Morrison_-_Higher_than_Here_Tour_-_2016_-_81510008_-_Leonhard_Kreissig_-_Canon_EOS_5D_Mark_II.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/james-morrison-(singer)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:20:37 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>