<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Electric Blues</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Electric Blues</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 01:11:11 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kid Ramos]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kid-ramos/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kid Ramos is an American electric blues and blues rock guitarist, singer and songwriter. Ramos has released four solo albums since 1995 on Black Top and Evidence Records. He has worked with James Harman, Roomful of Blues, the Big Rhythm Combo, The Fabulous Thunderbirds, The Mannish Boys, Bobby Jones and Los Fabulocos.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0f/Kid-Ramos-2008-SF.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kid-ramos/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lightnin' Hopkins]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lightnin'-hopkins/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Samuel John 'Lightnin'' Hopkins was an American country blues singer, songwriter, guitarist and occasional pianist, from Centerville, Texas. Rolling Stone magazine ranked him number 71 on its list of the 100 greatest guitarists of all time.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/bb/LightningHopkins.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/lightnin'-hopkins/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:13 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jimi Hendrix]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jimi-hendrix/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Marshall 'Jimi' Hendrix was an American rock guitarist, singer, and songwriter. His mainstream career lasted only four years, but he is widely regarded as one of the most influential guitarists in history and one of the most celebrated musicians of the 20th century. The Rock and Roll Hall of Fame describes him as 'the greatest instrumentalist in the history of rock music'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/ae/Jimi_Hendrix_1967.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jimi-hendrix/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Billy Gibbons]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billy-gibbons/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Frederick Gibbons, professionally known as Billy Gibbons, and The Reverend Billy F. Gibbons, is an American musician, singer, songwriter, record producer, and actor, best known as the guitarist and lead singer of American rock band ZZ Top. He began his career in the Moving Sidewalks, who recorded Flash (1968) and opened four dates for the Jimi Hendrix Experience. Gibbons formed ZZ Top in late 1969 and released ZZ Top's First Album in early 1971.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3a/ZZ_Top.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/billy-gibbons/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:12 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>