<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Instrument » Acoustic Guitar</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Instrument » Acoustic Guitar</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 19:54:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dave Alvin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Albert Alvin is an American singer-songwriter, guitarist, music producer and poet. He is a former and founding member of the roots rock band the Blasters. Alvin has recorded and performed as a solo artist since the late 1980s and has been involved in various side projects and collaborations. He has had brief stints as a member of the bands X and the Knitters.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d3/Dave_Alvin.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/dave-alvin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Willie Nelson]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Willie Hugh Nelson is an American musician, actor, and activist. The critical success of the album Shotgun Willie (1973), combined with the critical and commercial success of Red Headed Stranger (1975) and Stardust (1978), made Nelson one of the most recognized artists in country music. He was one of the main figures of outlaw country, a subgenre of country music that developed in the late 1960s as a reaction to the conservative restrictions of the Nashville sound. Nelson has acted in over 30 films, co-authored several books, and has been involved in activism for the use of biofuels and the legalization of marijuana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/2/21/WillieNelson.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/willie-nelson/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ville Valo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ville-valo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ville Hermanni Valo is a Finnish singer, songwriter and musician, best known as the lead vocalist of the gothic rock band HIM. Influenced by the likes of Black Sabbath and Type O Negative, Valo began his career playing bass and drums in various bands around his hometown of Helsinki. In 1991, he formed HIM, which would go on to become one of the most successful Finnish bands of all time, and the first to receive a gold record in the United States. He performed as the band's lead singer and chief songwriter from their inception until their dissolution in 2017. Valo is also credited as the creator of the heartagram, the band's trademarked symbol which nonetheless has achieved great popularity outside of the band's fanbase.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/93/Ville_Valo_2011.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ville-valo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Justin Hayward]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/justin-hayward/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Justin David Hayward is an English musician best known as songwriter, lead singer, and guitarist of the rock band The Moody Blues. Hayward became the group's principal lead guitarist and vocalist over the 1967–1974 period, and the most prolific songwriter and composer of several international hit singles for the band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/a/a5/JustinHayward3.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/justin-hayward/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Facundo Cabral]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/facundo-cabral/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Facundo Cabral was an Argentine singer, songwriter and philosopher.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/9a/Facundo_Cabral.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/facundo-cabral/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Brian Jones]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Lewis Brian Hopkins Jones was an English musician, best known as the founder and original leader of the Rolling Stones. Initially a slide guitarist, Jones would go on to play a wide variety of instruments on Rolling Stones recordings and in concerts, such as rhythm and lead guitar, sitar, dulcimer, various keyboard instruments such as piano and mellotron, marimba, wind instruments such as harmonica, recorder, saxophone, as well as drums, vocals and numerous others.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6b/Brian_Jones%2C_Statesboro%2C_Georgia%2C_May_4%2C_1965_%28377872218%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/brian-jones/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Janis Joplin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/janis-joplin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Janis Lyn Joplin was an American rock, soul and blues singer-songwriter, and one of the most successful and widely known rock stars of her era. After releasing three albums, she died of a heroin overdose at the age of 27. A fourth album, Pearl, was released in January 1971, just over three months after her death. It reached number one on the Billboard charts.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/79/Janis_Joplin_in_1969_%28cropped%29.png" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/janis-joplin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Svetlana Surganova]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/svetlana-surganova/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Svetlana Yakovlevna Surganova is a Russian rock musician, singer and poet. She was a founding member of the popular Russian rock band Nochnye Snaipery, providing vocals and playing violin. Presently she is a founding member of 'Surganova i Orkestr' band.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/74/Swetlana_Surganowa.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/svetlana-surganova/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Iggy Pop]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/iggy-pop/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>James Newell Osterberg Jr., better known as Iggy Pop, is an American singer, songwriter, musician, record producer, and actor. Designated the 'Godfather of Punk', he was the vocalist of influential proto-punk band the Stooges, who were formed in 1967 and have disbanded and reunited multiple times since.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/7a/Iggy_Pop_-_pinkpop87.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/iggy-pop/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Yuri Antonov]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yuri-antonov/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Yuri Mikhailovich Antonov is a Soviet and Russian composer, singer and musician, People's Artist of Russia (1997). He is also the Distinguished performer of arts of the Russian Federation (Russia) and the Distinguished artist of the Chechnya-Ingushetia ASSR (1983).</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/6/6d/Yuri_Antonov_%28musician%29_%282015-12-10%29_04.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/yuri-antonov/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>