<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Jazz</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Jazz</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 01:11:11 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Amy Winehouse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amy Jade Winehouse was an English singer and songwriter. She was known for her deep, expressive contralto vocals and her eclectic mix of musical genres, including soul rhythm and blues, and jazz. Winehouse's debut album, Frank (2003), was a critical success in the UK and was nominated for the Mercury Prize. Her follow-up album, Back to Black (2006), led to five 2008 Grammy Awards, tying the then record for the most wins by a female artist in a single night, and made her the first British woman to win five Grammys, including three of the General Field 'Big Four' Grammy Awards: Best New Artist, Record of the Year and Song of the Year.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cf/Amy_Winehouse_f4962007_crop.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/amy-winehouse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kyle Eastwood]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kyle-eastwood/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kyle Eastwood is an American jazz bass musician. He studied film at the University of Southern California for two years before embarking on a music career. After becoming a session player in the early 1990s and leading his own quartet, he released his first solo album, From There to Here, in 1998. His album, The View From Here, was released 2013 by Jazz Village. Eastwood plays fretted and fretless electric bass guitar and double bass.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e6/Kyle_Eastwood.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/kyle-eastwood/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mike Stern]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-stern/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Mike Stern is an American jazz guitarist. After playing with Blood, Sweat & Tears, he worked with drummer Billy Cobham, then with trumpeter Miles Davis from 1981 to 1983 and again in 1985. He then began a solo career, releasing more than a dozen albums.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/12/Mike_Stern_Kongsberg_Jazzfestival_2018_%28225558%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/mike-stern/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[k.d. lang]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/k.d.-lang/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Kathryn Dawn Lang, known by her stylized stage name k.d. lang, is a Canadian pop and country singer-songwriter and occasional actress.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/76/Kd_lang_-_AIS_Arena%2C_Canberra_-_7_Nov_11%283%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/k.d.-lang/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Victor Wooten]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/victor-wooten/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Victor Lemonte Wooten is an American bass guitarist, record producer, educator, and recipient of five Grammy Awards. He has been the bassist for Béla Fleck and the Flecktones since the group's formation in 1988 and a member of the band SMV with two other bassists, Stanley Clarke and Marcus Miller. Since 2017 he has played bass for the metal band Nitro.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/5c/Victor_Wooten_Cosmopolite_2018_%28213614%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/victor-wooten/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jarek Śmietana]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jarek-śmietana/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jarosław 'Jarek' Śmietana was a Polish jazz guitarist, composer and band leader.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/02/Jarek_smietana.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jarek-śmietana/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Kollar]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-kollar/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Kollar is a Slovak experimental guitarist and composer. He was born in Prešov into a musical family. He began his career at the end of the nineties in various amateur groups. He studied with guitarist Andrej Šeban. His first album called Free Your Minds was released in 2005. He is also film and stage music composer. In 2014 he did a tour with American drummer Pat Mastelotto and Italian trumpeter Paolo Raineri. Kollar appears on the 2017 Steven Wilson album To the Bone, playing on two tracks, 'Song of I' and 'Detonation'.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d2/David_Kollar.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-kollar/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[David Gilmore]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-gilmore/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Gilmore is an American jazz guitarist.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/9/96/David_Gilmore2011.JPG" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/david-gilmore/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bill Frisell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-frisell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>William Richard Frisell is an American guitarist, composer and arranger. One of the leading guitarists in jazz since the late 1980s, Frisell came to prominence as a stalwart for ECM Records. He went on to work in a variety of contexts, notably as a member of the New York City Downtown Scene where he formed a long partnership with John Zorn. He was also a longtime member of Paul Motian's groups from the early 1980s until Motian's death in 2011. Since 2000, Frisell's eclectic output as a bandleader has emphasized folk, country music, and Americana.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/46/Bill_wiki.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/bill-frisell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Anjani]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anjani/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Anjani Thomas is an American singer-songwriter and pianist, best known for her work with singer-songwriter Leonard Cohen, as well as Carl Anderson, Frank Gambale, and Stanley Clarke. She became a solo artist in 2000.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/0d/Anjani-Thomas-Blue-Alert-Cover-Art-No-Text.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/anjani/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 01:44:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>