<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Neo Classical Metal</title>
    <link>https://guitarstreams.com</link>
    <description>Genre » Neo Classical Metal</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 23:53:43 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Michael Angelo Batio]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-angelo-batio/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Angelo Batio, also known as Mike Batio or MAB, is an American heavy metal guitarist and columnist from Chicago, Illinois. He was the lead guitarist for the Los Angeles-based glam metal band Nitro in the late 1980s and early 1990s.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/ea/Michael_Angelo_Batio_playing_a_guitar_-_2.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/michael-angelo-batio/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Luca Turilli]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/luca-turilli/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Luca Turilli is an Italian musician and songwriter. He is one of the founders of the symphonic power metal band Rhapsody of Fire. He also worked on a trilogy of solo albums as Luca Turilli, and released one album under the name of Luca Turilli's Dreamquest, a project he worked on alongside Dominique Leurquin. In 2008, Luca began an online guitar course titled Luca Turilli's Neoclassical Revelation. The course takes its name from his neoclassical playing style.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/f5/Luca_Turilli_Live.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/luca-turilli/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:26 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Jani Liimatainen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jani-liimatainen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Jani Allan Kristian Liimatainen is a Finnish musician, songwriter and backing vocalist. He is the former guitarist and one of the founding members of the power metal band Sonata Arctica. He has also performed with Cain's Offering, Altaria and Stratovarius vocalist Timo Kotipelto.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/5/50/Insomnium_John_Smith_2019_%284%29.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/jani-liimatainen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ritchie Blackmore]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ritchie-blackmore/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Richard Hugh Blackmore is an English guitarist and songwriter. He was one of the founding members of Deep Purple in 1968, playing jam-style hard rock music which mixed guitar riffs and organ sounds.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/78/Ritchie_Blackmore_-_Barcelona.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/ritchie-blackmore/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Marty Friedman]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marty-friedman/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Martin Adam 'Marty' Friedman is an American guitarist, known for his tenure as the lead guitarist for heavy metal band Megadeth which spanned nearly the full decade of the 1990s. He is also known for playing alongside Jason Becker in Cacophony until 1989, as well as his 13 solo albums and tours. Friedman has resided in Tokyo, Japan since 2003, where he has appeared on over 700 Japanese television programs such as Rock Fujiyama, Hebimeta-san, Kouhaku uta gassen and Jukebox English. He has released albums with several record labels, including Avex Trax, Universal, EMI, Prosthetic and Shrapnel Records.</p><img src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/7/76/Marty_Friedman_13.jpg" alt="Preview">]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://guitarstreams.com/musician/marty-friedman/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 22:32:25 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>